<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">242</hilo><total_tweets type="int">18</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. On Twitter, @POTUS only goes after the ones he KNOWS are guilty. https://t.co/KTLfYkYNQC 
 2. https://t.co/vU8yMVAk8S 
 3. James Comey was once a good man. He became very corrupted in the Hillary probe and began to lie. One lie covered another. He never liked Trump or trusted him. https://t.co/r8bKTuijoz 
 4. He made the decision not to prosecute Hillary before he ever talked to her. He did not have witnesses present in interviews. No recordings, No swearing under oath. Just lies. https://t.co/rHSbhveXPH 
 5. https://t.co/T2eyK0L7GZ 
 6. He was not always this way. He crumbled under pressure and was only looking at his career and future. He blew it all. He will be known as a liar and crook. https://t.co/w8l2iG1Pt1 
 7. Sometimes good people allow themselves to be used like puppets. They take the wrong path and eventually it is impossible to turn back. https://t.co/k7j0TavX4m 
 8. They all lied because THEY NEVER THOUGHT SHE WOULD LOSE. POTUS knows ALL because his Friends know ALL. https://t.co/AR4bMmvWKL 
 9. https://t.co/NbJuAO31le 
 10. This was retaliation. They operate like the Mafia. https://t.co/vcNnGZUc7H 
 11. Previously. https://t.co/AVYJHF9z0b 
 12. Imagine a world where truth is presented as fiction. https://t.co/CA5bLC4fus 
 13. The most vocal opponents of POTUS in DC are the ones with the most to hide. DC Circle in which HRC is high priestess. Sacrifice and blood rituals. Most regular people could not believe the whole truth if they heard it. https://t.co/dpzB18hvYb 
 14. Some of them are desperate and running out of options. https://t.co/gF2TuyuKQ4 
 15. This is about more than politics. Sick people. The circle of trust is broken. Anything could happen. https://t.co/DKpKjG3x30 
 16. Robert Mueller actually wants to take down Hillary, Obama and others. He is not a good person though. Like Comey, Mueller pretends to be innocent to save himself. He&apos;s swamp. 
 17. There are wheels in motion. There are still many good people. https://t.co/XA73ffHxa0 
 18. TRUST there is a plan. State of the Union was a turning point. #greatawakening #qanon #sotu https://t.co/rUsq943z83</texto><total_retweets type="int">2128</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">6190</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">125</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">854483338530349056</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">21385</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">300</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">8730</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.2448028715197252</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>