<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">197</hilo><total_tweets type="int">19</total_tweets><texto type="str">THREAD: As you might know, I&apos;m a #FormerGOP . I voted Republican loyally for over 30 years. But when Trump won the Primary, I was able to see the true and dispicably UGLY face of my party, and I have never gone back again. https://t.co/F5p5dn3siQ 
 Many wonderful people in #TheResistance have taken me in, educated me, and helped me to become a much better person. They have helped me to realize that so many of my hard-core, basic beliefs were incompatible with voting Republican. I owe you all so many thanks for that! https://t.co/Sc1uHEYYvQ 
 Today, I learned something else... When I first saw the #Rose 🌹 symbol in various profiles, I googled it and also asked some people who were using it, what it meant. I was told it was just a symbol of #Resistance, &amp;amp; I thought it was no different than the #Omega / #Ohm symbol. 
 Well, my daughters middle name is Rose, and I just like roses anyway, so I chose to put that in my profile. https://t.co/HiwrNPZ3pj 
 One wonderful person today explained some of my recent confusion. Apparently, Bernie supporters have taken to using 🌹 as their symbol, &amp;amp; I was unknowingly aligning myself w/ a #Resistance faction. My tweets for unity, therefore, seemed disingenuous to some Hillary supporters. 
 I have nothing against Bernie or ANY of his supporters, but I do not wish to sow division or disunion, so I will be removing that symbol. I do not wish to align myself with ANY factions, &amp;amp; I truly think it is VITAL that everyone in #TheResistance stands united against the GOP. https://t.co/z0vm5HLVMy 
 At this point in my thread, it&apos;s important for you to know that I watched the Democratic Primaries in 2016 as someone who was very recently &quot;politically homeless.&quot; I had no horse in the race, and I was simply looking at options. https://t.co/DNEQsURm9F 
 I was worried to later hear of the scandal surrounding @SenSanders treatment by the DNC. Knowing how Trump worked, I was afraid he would use that repeatedly against Hillary. 
 I needn&apos;t have worried, it seems, because Trump let his pal Putin do that for him on social media. Putin, we now know, stoked the pre-existing flames of discontent among many who were--and still are-- @SenSander&apos;s followers. 
 Putin used social media like a crowbar, to turn the crack that originally existed between the &quot;Bernie&quot; &amp;amp; &quot;Hillary&quot; camps, into a chasm. We CANNOT let that happen again! https://t.co/BdE7CPR4U4 
 Recently, #TheResistance has discovered a large number of bot accounts in their midst, placed there by possible Russian operatives (based on the @ names). No matter who has created them, their purpose is clearly malicious. https://t.co/rxUbJvsYIB 
 Now, with #Mueller&apos;s indictments, we see the evidence that Putin was trying to divide the Left from day one, as far back as 2014. I truly believe that THIS is the main purpose of these new bot accounts. https://t.co/uMsUkFeBch 
 With the upcoming 2018 elections, and as new Presidential candidates arise, Putin wishes to influence-- nay, MANIPULATE-- us once again, and once more try to have his own PUPPET American government. We CANNOT let that happen! https://t.co/wAnjQ6eWTm 
 Unblock each other, re-friend each other, LIKE each other&apos;s posts &amp;amp; tweets, and be especially careful to check profiles. Ignore ANY words of more division &amp;amp; bitterness, and work instead towards unity &amp;amp; peace in #TheResistance. https://t.co/i1FfK9XnkM 
 Too many districts are Red, and we NEED to #FlipBlue. Too many of those CAN be flipped, but we will have to work hard. We will have to get EVERY possible Blue vote to the polls-- no matter if they were once voters for &quot;Bernie&quot; or &quot;Hillary&quot; or &quot;none of the above.&quot; #BlueWave https://t.co/S3F6PUFvqg 
 Ours is a great &amp;amp; powerful Democracy, one that has been tarnished &amp;amp; humiliated by the stain of the corrupt &amp;amp; blood-soaked #GOP, and by Putin&apos;s manipulations. https://t.co/fgDdguXUH9 
 But we CAN, and we WILL, shine once more. We CAN, and we WILL, be a proud nation once more. We CAN, and we WILL, embrace hope once more. PEACE, my fellow #Resistance! https://t.co/Aze4On61Lt 
 Let us find our redemption in our resolve, and find our pride in the power of our unity. Let us be a beacon in this wonderful nation, and bring HOPE to it once more. Let us NEVER surrender to the forces of darkness and division. https://t.co/Yyga1YhVyW 
 We are #TheResistance . And we MUST co-exist in PEACE. 🕊️✌️🕊️☮️🕊️✌️🕊️ https://t.co/s63lUfd1l1</texto><total_retweets type="int">364</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1110</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">50</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">10</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1535595181</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">8531</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">9080</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">27746</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7928489032198671</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>