<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">316</hilo><total_tweets type="int">25</total_tweets><texto type="str">🚨This was &amp;amp; still is President Barack Obama&apos;s Shadow Government /Deep State known publicly if you look hard enough as the Senior Executive Service (SES) Thread w details follows!🚨 #DeepState #SeniorExecutiveService #DOJCorruption #FBICorruption #ObamaGate #ObamaSpyRingScandal https://t.co/e6loMiVRzC 
 What or Who is the Senior Executive Service You Ask? The SES is a Deep State is group of over 9,000 appointed &apos;Mangers&apos; in 75 Federal agencies that control the executive bureaucracy &amp;amp; tell new political appointees what they can and cannot do. https://t.co/kEFe9BcDXp https://t.co/l1ETFsJLXO 
 American Intelligence Media has done a great piece on the ins &amp;amp; outs of the organization and I have included it below. They are rarely talked about but known amongst themselves by this lapel pin. If you see this pin, they are most likely bad news! https://t.co/Zs1QNO0Ibo https://t.co/a9JYBnZW7a 
 These Deep State groups are all about their symbology &amp;amp; this one is no exception. They explain the meaning behind the #Keystone on the OPM website. #QAnon https://t.co/cVjKAeSQyJ https://t.co/701qWQTGyk 
 When we look at the &apos;Who&apos; think of those who have obstructed @realDonaldTrump &amp;amp; his administration to include his transition team. Evelyn Farkas was Obama&apos;s Deputy Assistant Secretary of Defense for Russia/Ukraine 👇 https://t.co/EDJVk8nJIp https://t.co/u1ULy59e9b 
 How do I know she is or anyone else is a Senior Executive Service (SES) member is all based on the pay scale and coding for each position. NA &amp;amp; TA are reserved for these SES personell. 👇 https://t.co/LS5f91UpGv 
 Evelyn Farkas was Obama&apos;s Deputy Assistant Secretary of Defense for Russia/Ukraine &amp;amp; had alot to say about what they actually did while she was part of the SES while in Office on @MSNBC in March of 2017. What they did to @realDonaldTrump &amp;amp; how they did it is now very clear. 👇 https://t.co/9vFb4AA3IU 
 The SES goes into 75 departments of the government to include the Department of Justice &amp;amp; The FBI. We start seeing this now that we have the #Key to find the players. One of them just so happens to be Bruce Ohr, who&apos;s wife works for #FusionGPS https://t.co/G2jB0SPhns https://t.co/g33IjKHHVO 
 Here is the backstory on Bruce Ohr / Christopher Steele for those that are just tuning in or just starting to pay closer attention to detail. https://t.co/6j1BcatJYE 
 Just to show you how the Special Counsel is comprised, Robert Mueller&apos;s top gun prosecutor is none other than Andrew Weissman. He is also part of the SES as listed in the Federal Registry along with David Rybicki. https://t.co/VilInVVBch https://t.co/Pck1RcRor3 
 https://t.co/Xk050SggGL 
 Mary McCord, George Toscas &amp;amp; David Laufman are also listed in the Federal Registry as part of the National Security Division of the SES in 2015. Toscas &amp;amp; Laufman remained as of Dec 2017 in the Federal Registry. https://t.co/JQM4cjD1Aa https://t.co/UEBRgDa4DP 
 George Toscas was in a pinch over the revelation of the Anthony Weiner laptop that included Hillary Clinton&apos;s emails with Huma Abedin. He&apos;s also mentioned as part of the crew in the Page &amp;amp; Strozk texts released by @ChuckGrassley &amp;amp; @DevinNunes https://t.co/FP7NeP43CK 
 The Lisa Page &amp;amp; Peter Strzok texts &amp;amp; emails start painting a bigger picture as to what exactly Evelyn Farkas disclosed on MSNBC in 2017. https://t.co/Oq8bwECbXo https://t.co/IpW9Z7zT1u 
 This starts putting the pieces of the puzzle together and who the remaining well known players are in the SES at the FBI &amp;amp; DOJ. These people have also stepped down over this debacle! Michael Kortan &amp;amp; James Baker both are out! https://t.co/u6REU7FsPt https://t.co/WEgWlmPxK7 
 FBI/DOJ Co-Conspirators Just Lost Biggest Asset – FBI Director Wray Kicks Out James Baker https://t.co/3IdDcwza0F 
 Other players at the FBI National Security Branch include Bill Priestap &amp;amp; Carl Ghattas. https://t.co/9VaEfrGnDu https://t.co/sy6ZmDKhA3 
 We know that many have stepped down from their posts to include Rachael Band &amp;amp; Currie Gunn. Gun may have also been part of the SES after the 2016 report was released or personnel were promoted &amp;amp; this may be why Band had to step down. https://t.co/G2jB0SPhns https://t.co/Zg0KwYwYsd 
 Rachel Band resignation....👇 https://t.co/YPDREWqxXl https://t.co/UYAEj5mehN 
 This goes all the way back to the top according to Julie Zebrak who has insight into the FBI &amp;amp; an advocate for Moms4HRC https://t.co/PJUT6iCfGI She claims Andrew McCabe is career SES &amp;amp; they can&apos;t get rid of him so easily. Andrew McCabe as you can see is claimed to be Career SES. https://t.co/E6623BiRQ1 
 And by TOP I mean Evelyn Farkas &amp;amp; the rest of the Coup D&apos;état crew in the FBI &amp;amp; DOJ got marching orders from Barack Obama himself! #ObamaGate https://t.co/WqhZTD3skp https://t.co/linOFEpRkQ 
 I encourage each and every one of you citizen journalist &amp;amp; investigators to dig through the names &amp;amp; departments of the Senior Executive Service (SES) I provided &amp;amp; connect more dots to this Treasonous Puzzle. We need to shut down this program because it is the Heart of The Swamp!! 
 @threadreaderapp unroll please!! #ChopChop 
 @Thomas1774Paine @Imperator_Rex3 @thebradfordfile @TruthinGov2016 @DaveNYviii @TheLastRefuge2 @RealMattCouch 
 Going to add another link for those that want an easily searchable &amp;amp; amazing research tool thanks to Americans for Innovation that you can use to identify Senior Executive Services members. https://t.co/Mh9zzyIWT6 https://t.co/MuFdd9H5OM</texto><total_retweets type="int">3909</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">4397</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">180</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">11</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">924462918988632064</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">17635</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">12035</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">55066</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8358261953264522</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>