<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">279</hilo><total_tweets type="int">24</total_tweets><texto type="str">A few notes on Vannevar Bush&apos;s amazing essay, &quot;As We May Think&quot;, from the 1945(!) @TheAtlantic : https://t.co/epxmwiaB0n 
 &quot;As We May Think&quot; is part of a tiny genre: a grand vision document that&apos;s extremely insightful, and which becomes incredibly influential. It&apos;s tempting to say prescient, but the essay actually helped create its imagined future. 
 &quot;As We May Think&quot; seems to me like the writings of Locke or Montesquieu: a set of ideas that decisively influenced major parts of our cultural operating system. In one case, the US Constitution (&amp;amp; the many others influenced), in the other, the web &amp;amp; computer software more broadly 
 It&apos;s fun to consider &quot;As We May Think&quot; as part of a line of successful grand vision documents: Engelbart on &quot;Augmenting Human Intellect&quot; (https://t.co/YBme2bkLuP ), Alan Kay on &quot;A Personal Computer for Children of All Ages&quot; (https://t.co/jLL7XbhLPR ) ... 
 ... Stallman on free software (the GNU manifesto and the GPL), @timberners_lee on &quot;Information Management: a Proposal&quot; (https://t.co/Spw3UdTKe4), and perhaps Satoshi on Bitcoin (https://t.co/iJZv8FYxfg ) - time will tell. 
 One thing that stands out: managing information overload is a recurring obsession. Bush has his Memex (memory extender), with which he hoped to improve in some ways on the associative operation of the human mind, especially in permanence and clarity: https://t.co/kxidXPXnVh 
 In particular, Engelbart, Kay, and @timberners_lee all return to the theme of information overload, in different ways. @timberners_lee&apos;s title is &quot;Information Management: A Proposal&quot;. 
 Of course, information overload is intrinsically an insoluble problem. Understanding is so valuable that we will always push ourselves to our limits in managing information, no matter how good our tools become, &amp;amp; feel uncomfortable as we push up against them. 
 Better tools expand the limits of the information we can manage, but do little to change our desire to go still further, because that desire is only very weakly a function of the quantity of information we can currently manage. 
 I say information overload is &quot;insoluble&quot;, but that&apos;s a pessimistic way of framing it. A much better way is that it&apos;s an open-ended problem: we can always do better. I won&apos;t be surprised if many grand vision documents of the future will also focus on that problem. 
 It&apos;s not clear how many of the authors had ambitions to write influential grand vision documents. Mostly, I think, they were obsessed with important fundamental problems whose time was nearly ripe - so obsessed that they stumbled on some very good ideas, which they then developed 
 More recurring themes: not just information management, but also memory, note-taking, association of ideas, and problem-solving. None of these problems have yet been solved well, IMO. 
 Satoshi stands out as different, being much more focused on co-ordination problems. 
 Another striking difference: all the later vision documents eventually led to working systems, and that was a big part of their success (especially the web and Bitcoin). Bush&apos;s vision did not. And yet it was hugely influential anyway. 
 Back to Bush: it&apos;s fun to see how many ideas still haven&apos;t entirely come to fruition. Here he is on sharing entire lines of thought and investigation, a sort of super-@pinboard or -@pinterest. Keep in mind, this is 1945: https://t.co/WuOg4NYQcZ 
 Here&apos;s Bush describing so much of the web and wikidom (again: 1945): https://t.co/IWODC7JnPK 
 Here&apos;s Bush on neural interfaces: https://t.co/yNN3VtuAre 
 It&apos;s fascinating that he&apos;s imagining this all through the lens of analog machines. In fact, Bush never really got into digital computing. It passed him by. But hardware aside, he was thinking about the right problems and at a great level of design abstraction. 
 Anyways, there&apos;s much, much more in the article. Well worth reading! 
 More fun things: see @hyfen&apos;s project to build a memex: https://t.co/TkvuS3QvA3 
 And @TrevorFSmith&apos;s memex: https://t.co/PE34AhekSl 
 Just a small appendix. Reading back over my thread, it&apos;s got too much of the &quot;gee-whiz, wasn&apos;t that a clever insight of a giant of the past&quot; trope about it. 
 Yes, Bush was clever. But that&apos;s not so interesting. I think it&apos;s more interesting to think about the big, broad fundamental questions he was addressing, and how far we are from really solving them. 
 How to manage information overload? What are the real bottlenecks? How can we make vastly better computer note taking systems? Why haven&apos;t we gone beyond the file metaphor? How can we build better personal memory systems? Better collective memory systems? So many great problems!</texto><total_retweets type="int">112</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">593</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">68</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">15626406</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">42261</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3010</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">17847</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0328753737869556</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>