<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">143</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) #NicolasSarkozy was #France’s president 2007-2012, was arrested &amp;amp; is being questioned about his illegally financed campaign by #Gaddafi in #Libya, some backstory. How did Sarkozy go from accepting #illegal cash to advocating overthrow? #QAnon #Corruption @POTUS #FRA #LeMonde https://t.co/tzaWUZv68L 
 2) A total of $50m was funneled. And it wasn&apos;t done via wire transfer. Franco-Lebanese businessman Ziad Takkiedine claims he carried suitcases full of cash in 2006 and 2007. $50m is double the legal campaign limit in France. https://t.co/UGAzz55pTJ #QAnon #TheStormIsHere 
 3) This story is not new. Here is an article from it back in 2014. https://t.co/QJKzWCELhz #Sarkozy is a corrupt #swamp rat. He&apos;s been dogged by corruption claims forever. A simple search will show a laundry list. #qanon #DrainTheSwamp #France #Corruption 
 4) For example Sarkozy was charged in 2013 for allegations his party took envelopes stuffed w cash from #France&apos;s richest woman, L&apos;Oreal heiress Liliane Bettencourt. Those charges were dropped. Remind you of anyone? #Hillary? These #elites seem to all get away with everything. 
 5) #HillaryClinton. Again. Always seems to circle back to the queen of the #DeepState. Both #Clinton &amp;amp; #Sarkozy were the 2 biggest advocates for overthrow around 2011. Again, you take a guy&apos;s money then advocate overthrow? Why? #qanon #GreatAwakening @POTUS #TheStormHasArrived 
 6) There was pay for play going on between #Lybia and #France. Qaddafi traveled to France in December &apos;07, immediately after Sarkozy&apos;s first election as president for a 5 day visit to make a $200 million arms deal. So this is what #Gaddafi was after, and who knows what else. 
 7) The Sidney Blumenthal emails show a confusing picture of France&apos;s about face on Libya. The cover story was a pan-African gold backed currency, but it seems a bit less sophisticated... control of Libyan oil. #qanon #Oil @POTUS #TheStormIsUponUs #Africa 
 8) France wanted #Qaddafi out: #newspaper #Libération published a leaked letter from Libya&apos;s rebel-backed National Transitional Council promising 35 percent of the country&apos;s crude oil to France in return for its &quot;total and permanent support.&quot; #BOOM #QAnon #Libya #Corruption 
 9) So French intelligence service DGSE held secret meetings w Libyan opposition &amp;amp; started funding them. The French promised that as soon as the National Transitional Council was set up, they&apos;d recognize it as government of Libya. Recognition = new chapter in corruption. #Qanon 
 10) So #Sarkozy turned on #Qaddafi for the oil. How does this relate back to the #USA&apos;s interests, and the #Hillary #StateDept? Here is where we speculate a bit. Yes, there were &quot;stated&quot; reasons for #US intervention, but they are never true. What was the real reason? #QAnon 
 11) The long standing rumor is that #Kadhafi was taken out because they discovered where his cash was hidden. The #Clinton #StateDept in cahoots with the #Cabal and #CIA all saw an opportunity to grab it. Remember that Red Cross cash video? #QanonPosts https://t.co/mZRTFSf0Hj 
 12) Events like the Libyan overthrow happen for complex reasons. Ghaddafi&apos;s desire to split from central banking is true, he wanted an African gold backed currency. Who runs central banking? #Rothschilds Nobody would have been allowed to do this without their green light. #Qanon 
 14) All the nations that toppled Libya had different interests, and so did bankers and globalists. A bunch of lies were crafted for the public to consume, and the #Cabal moves another step forward implementing the #NWO. @POTUS #UN #DeepState #Banking #ARMS #Oil #plunder #Qanon 
 15) Today Libya is a complete mess, garbage #Government, thriving #slavery trade, #organisedcrime is rampant, mass #MigrationEU, #drugdealers &amp;amp; #terrorist groups. All a direct result of #Obama&apos;s foreign policy, #Hillary&apos;s corruption, #Sarkosy, and the #cabal. #Qanon #EU @POTUS</texto><total_retweets type="int">78</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">138</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">22</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">53</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1623794972</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">11222</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">39</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">10786</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.5565009939878032</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>