<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">365</hilo><total_tweets type="int">30</total_tweets><texto type="str">#BreakingNews #Exclusive Iraq&apos;s International Federal Police confiscates 31 boxes containing hundreds of thousands of dollars in cash en route from #Iran to #Iraq in support of Hadi al-Ameri, head of the Tehran proxy Badr Organization. https://t.co/OxVNgYillC 
 #Iraq activists say this is outside the country&apos;s parliament only days before the May 12th general election People chanting: &quot;#Iran, out, out&quot; &amp;amp; something against IRGC Quds Force chief Qassem Suleimani (Can anyone provide more info? Thanks in advance) https://t.co/hJhaVgGBh2 
 #Iraq general election posters (scheduled for Saturday) put up in Isfahan, #Iran. Millions are living in poverty across Iran, and yet the regime spends money on such ridiculous causes for another country. Shows how Tehran&apos;s influence in Iraq is considered vital for the mullahs. https://t.co/mFl4C6bXyz 
 (1) Following yesterday’s general elections, clashes have erupted among various Kurdish groups in Sulaymaniyah, northern #Iraq, sources say. Iraqi Kurdistan Regional Gov PM Nechirvan Barzani is calling for calm. Talks between two Kurdish parties continue. #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/qxe1zPV5Au 
 (2) Further reports indicate the Patriotic Union of Kurdistan Party (with close relations to #Iran) are accused of fraud by the Gorran Movement (Change Party. Armed PUK forces attacked Change Party HQ following these allegations. #Iraq #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/WpA6Grlxt5 
 (3) This led to various clashes in Sulaymaniyah, Halabja &amp;amp; other cities, continuing late into Saturday night local time. #Iraq #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/mDnvIiSaIv 
 #BREAKING (1) More than $80 mn from #Iran failed to influence #Iraq’s elections. Tehran-backed Popular Mobilization Front, taking part under the Fat’h Coalition framework, lost in these polls. #IraqiElections2018 https://t.co/s1N5xT9Klk 
 (2) Initial #IraqiElections2018 results show the Nasr Coalition led by the incumbent PM Haydar Abadi gained the most votes &amp;amp; the Saeroon coalition, associated to Muqtada Sadr, came in second. #IraqiElections2018 https://t.co/LkScJwguSD 
 (3) Abadi is attempting to depict an independent image of himself. Sadr, despite growing up in #Iran, has in the past two years described Tehran’s influence in his country as destructive &amp;amp; called for no meddling in Iraq by Ali Khamenei. #IraqiElections2018 
 #Iraq PM Haider Al Abadi calls for Iraqi Kurdistan elections recount Patriotic Union of Kurdistan (with close ties to #Iran) is rejecting this request Fmr. PM Ayad Alawi calls for a recount of ballot boxes across the country Iran&apos;s regime stands accused of tampering &amp;amp; fraud https://t.co/rzzoeS1ZV2 
 Early polls show Muqtada Sadr, the Shiite cleric with anti-Iranian regime viewpoints, is leading #Iraq&apos;s general election vote count. #Iran&apos;s money &amp;amp; influence is failing to advance Tehran&apos;s agenda in its western neighbor. https://t.co/AwP1UzpsS3 
 Early #Iraq general election results (Asharqiya TV): Of 328 seats Nasr (PM Haider Al Abadi) - 65 seats Saeroon (Sadr coalition) - 52 seats Wataniya (Alawi coalition) - 29 seats Fat&apos;h (Al Ameri coalition) - 25 seats Kurdish parties - 25 seats Hekma (Hakim coalition) - 10 seats https://t.co/Me4t8wnbqz 
 Al Hadath TV: Scenes of people celebrating in Baghdad after Iraq&apos;s general election results. Demonstrators heard chanting: &quot;Iran, out, out&quot; or &quot;Iran, get lost&quot; Are these signs of #Iran&apos;s influence failing in #Iraq? If so, this is a major development. https://t.co/Xet1zH9pDZ 
 #Iran&apos;s own media are reporting anti-Tehran policy coalitions in #Iraq have received more votes in Saturday&apos;s general elections. Scenes show Iraqi people celebrating. &quot;Bye bye, Nouri Maliki, bye bye&quot; Former Iraqi PM Nouri Maliki is a known puppet of #Iran&apos;s regime in Iraq. https://t.co/hN5zjjg2Cf 
 (1) In #Iraq’s general elections, most eligible voters remained at home &amp;amp; only 44% of the population took part. Analysts believe this is a sign of major disappointment in the country&apos;s political leaders &amp;amp; concerns over widespread government corruption. #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/xBiY77o17w 
 (2) The electronic voting system malfunctioned many times, causing much disarray. Former Iraqi PM Ayad Allawi is calling for new elections, believing the low voter turnout will result in a weak government unable to resolve the country’s issues. #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/gjvefWVrK9 
 (3) Analysts argue none of Iraq’s main political parties will be able to establish a government &amp;amp; forming a coalition government to launch the country’s reconstruction process will be extremely difficult. #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/NXqGE3CxdF 
 (4) 24 million eligible Iraqi voters were asked to choose between around 7,000 candidates for 329 parliamentary seats. Nearly 13 million eligible voters refused to go to the polls. This is also considered a failure of #Iran&apos;s influence in #Iraq. #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/e3dKGaYipM 
 This is a behind-the-scenes look at #Iraq&apos;s &quot;elections vote count,&quot; (if you can actually describe such a scene as a legitimate vote count)... God knows the scope of the alleged vote rigging. In one scene it appears a small boy&apos;s fingerprints are being used... #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/GPsaLAQzCc 
 Supporters of Muqtada Sadr in Baghdad celebrating his coalition&apos;s victory in #Iraq&apos;s recent elections and seen here chanting: &quot;Iran, out, out (Iran get lost), Baghdad forever free&quot; #Iran #IraqElections2018 https://t.co/rtbIldvu8v 
 (1) Muqtada Sadr after #IraqElections2018: &quot;We in the Saeroon, Hikma &amp;amp; Al Wataniya parties will be the voice of our people to establish a new generation aimed at witnessing change towards reform. Our decision will be Iraqi to raise the flag of victory &amp;amp; Baghdad is our capital.&quot; https://t.co/aLawjwptVS 
 (2) Muqtada Sadr after #IraqElections2018: &quot;Our movement will be democratic &amp;amp; we shall establish a technocratic government without partisanship.&quot; If carried out correctly, this can deliver a severe blow to #Iran&apos;s meddling in #Iraq &amp;amp; across the region. #TuesdayThoughts https://t.co/j9r94xe54a 
 #BREAKING Increasing reports indicate #Iran&apos;s IRGC Quds Force chief Qassem Suleimani being in Baghdad after Tehran-backed coalitions suffered a crushing defeat in #IraqElections2018. The mere fact that Khamenei scrambles Suleimani to Baghdad indicates the dire status quo. https://t.co/ku0hklgXzJ 
 Sadr, winning #Iraq’s elections, says will not ally w/ the Fat’h slate (linked to #Iran-backed Popular Mobilization Force), State of Law (linked to fmr PM Maliki, known as Iran&apos;s puppet) or Patriotic Union of Kurdistan (w/ a history of close relations w/ Iran). #TuesdayThoughts https://t.co/Au17UMMDfm 
 Local media are reporting #Iran&apos;s IRGC Quds Force chief Qassem Suleimani is in Baghdad with a mission to prevent Muqtada Sadr, who&apos;s party won the most seats in #IraqElections2018, to determine the country&apos;s next prime minister. This is Tehran&apos;s meddling at work. https://t.co/01XSB6jAEi 
 #BREAKING Unconfirmed reports indicate Muqtada Sadr, whose party won the most seats in #Iraq&apos;s recent general election, has issued a 48-hour deadline to #Iran&apos;s IRGC Quds Force chief Qassem Suleimani to leave Iraq. https://t.co/JEso6caTDY 
 Muqtada Sadr political office chief: &quot;We seek to establish a government without Iran&apos;s presence &amp;amp; far from any alliance with Hadi Al Ameri &amp;amp; Nouri Al Maliki.&quot; https://t.co/UUzJPSDhZx This is a severe blow to #Iran&apos;s intentions in #Iraq. https://t.co/fN0ELGUqmU 
 Following the 48-hour deadline for #Iran&apos;s IRGC Quds Force chief Qassem Suleimani to leave #Iraq, Muqtada Sadr holds a meeting with the ambassadors of all of Iraq&apos;s neighbors, instead of Tehran. #GameOver for Iran in Iraq. https://t.co/gjMybOek2s 
 Muqtada Sadr-linked media reporting #Iran&apos;s IRGC Quds Force chief Qassem Suleimani left Baghdad Friday night &amp;amp; entered Sulaymaniyah in #Iraq&apos;s Kurdistan. This area is controlled by the PUK, known to have close relations with Tehran. #GameOver for Iran in Iraq... https://t.co/0I6vQCioP1 
 #BREAKING Unconfirmed sources indicate warplanes from an unknown origin plan to target #Iran&apos;s IRGC positions in the city of Sulaymaniyah in northern #Iraq. Emphasis: This is an unconfirmed report. Seeking further info in this regard. Situation very fluid. https://t.co/Gtq68p0sQl</texto><total_retweets type="int">4153</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">4594</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">349</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">2554131522</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">33786</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">237</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">51069</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.3412250599955906</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>