<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">302</hilo><total_tweets type="int">22</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) This is my #Qanon update for April 14. Q posts can be found here: https://t.co/yeNLF0baB0 https://t.co/rjRgcHS7yO https://t.co/6JJUIpek07 My theme for this series: Sparrow Red - Missiles Only https://t.co/lt1C5faZ6L 
 2) #Qanon posted a Tweet by the President and asked why the misspelling wasn&apos;t corrected. https://t.co/vzdx0aFyD7 
 3) #Qanon said: Misspellings matter. So do memes. Why? Jack &amp;amp; Zuck use AI to detect ideologies that need to be censored Memes convey ideologies in a way that can&apos;t be detected by artificial intelligence. Memes confound censors. https://t.co/EkdjCZlGkB 
 4) #Qanon reposted this from an anon. https://t.co/dQ7MAGJL0D 
 5) This is the crumb the anon referred. It was posted by #Qanon in February https://t.co/6HjSS3u4yJ 
 6) #Qanon (again) posted about the problems Rod #Rosenstein is having. Rumors abound that #Trump is considering firing him. Some reports say that Rosenstein is preparing for it but there&apos;s little evidence to suggest it will happen. https://t.co/I3LL6Ev7j0 
 7) Here&apos;s the link #Qanon posted. https://t.co/7ggtDMxzXj 
 8) #Qanon posted this. (I&apos;m not sure what it means.) https://t.co/WzP2G8up7u 
 9) #Qanon posted this last night after the President authorized air strikes to destroy chemical weapons manufacturing and storage facilities in #Syria Note: Q told us there would be no troop invasion. It would be missiles (and bombs) only. https://t.co/FxhUxvedwg 
 10) #Qanon knew there would be concern that last night&apos;s military action would be taken as a sign of a protracted war in Syria. Not a good look, especially since there&apos;s debate about who used chemical weapons. 
 11) On the 7th, #Qanon posted this. The use of bombs (B-17) and missiles (sparrow red) had been authorized, but they would not be LAUNCHED unless irrefutable proof emerged that Assad had used chemical weapons on his own people. https://t.co/OlauoDrWFf 
 12) #Qanon Let&apos;s decode B19-2 B19-2 = B 17 I believe it&apos;s simply a reference to bombers. Although B-1 bombers were used in last night&apos;s offensive, Q chose the B-17 as the reference point. https://t.co/bICYOK3tW7 
 13) #Qanon Let&apos;s decode Sparrow Red The sparrow is an anti-aircraft &amp;amp; anti-ship missile While tomahawks &amp;amp; standoff bombs were used in last night&apos;s offensive, for some reason Q chose the term &quot;sparrow&quot; to refer to missiles. (Note that Ratheon&apos;s branding includes the color red) https://t.co/uFY1CpkFJY 
 14) Another possible interpretation of #Qanon&apos;s reference to Sparrow Red. https://t.co/abVHAVf1MF 
 15) Investigators have been assessing the situation in #Syria since the 7th. They&apos;ve been interviewing witnesses and analyzing the evidence. On the 9th, #Qanon posted this update. They were looking into false flag reports but had to verify eveything before making a decison. https://t.co/xdjdBouzUy 
 16) If you believe the use of chemicals in Syria was a false flag, the next question is: How good is your intel? The FF videos and reports we&apos;ve all seen only show a small part of the picture. The Defense Department has better intel than any of us. #Qanon 
 17) The decision to greenlight the air strikes was not made quickly. Trump waited until he had all the data he needed. The wait gave Syria, Iran and Russia time to remove personnel and assets from the area if they wanted to. They took advantage of it to minimize loss of life. 
 18) #Qanon said they had good intel on which they based their decision. Everything possible was done to minimize casualties. The President and Secretary Mattis confirmed they do not anticipate a long engagement. Trump still plans to remove our troops from Syria. 
 19) POTUS doesn&apos;t need us to KNOW the details of the plan. He needs us to TRUST that he has a plan and that he has our best interest at heart. It&apos;s easy to trust the plan when things go the way we expect. It&apos;s harder when things don&apos;t look like we think they should, #Qanon https://t.co/zfSFAynxYS 
 20) It&apos;s hard to trust the plan sometimes. If it was easy, they&apos;d call it snowboarding #Qanon https://t.co/upaGVdytIi 
 21) #Qanon posted this. Note: [SHOWERS] in brackets Reference to missiles and bombs? https://t.co/Jk4cvNEUIg 
 A closeup of #Qanon&apos;s image Note: B1 bomber and B19-2 are underlined (Confirming decode of B-17 bomber) Q asked us to check the date of the original post against the day we watched it (the bombing) happen Original post was on the 8th We saw it happen on the 13th *Iran is next https://t.co/GC7yAPKGJS</texto><total_retweets type="int">1729</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">3914</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">209</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">4</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">83932539</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">184948</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">58009</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">45917</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.913862994504708</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>