<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">122</hilo><total_tweets type="int">15</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) The Queen of #DARPA From last night&apos;s amazing events on #Q research boards, a familiar name re-emerged: Regina Dugan. 19th Director of the Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency (DARPA). In March 2012, she left for #Google. #QAnon #QArmy #WWG1WGA #TheStormIsHere @POTUS https://t.co/3IepACdYnW 
 2) There, she led the Advanced Technology and Projects (ATAP) group at Motorola Mobility (Google owned) and worked on Skip... &quot;exploring digital tattoos and pills&quot; Kinda odd? #redpill #Crumbs #WakeUp #MakeItRain #Corruption #QAnon #AprilShowers https://t.co/U3T0ii9mKe 
 3) While at #Google, she also worked on Tango. This woman sure is interested in tracking you, isn&apos;t she? #DrainTheSwamp #DeepStateinPanic #DrainTheDeepState #DeepState #DeepStateAgenda #IBOR #InternetBillofRights https://t.co/lABpz8j1wD 
 4) Further bouncing around Silicon Valley over the past few years she landed at Facebook. See #Q post. Building 8. China. #Qanon @POTUS #MAGA #Trump @realDonaldTrump #GreatAwakenening #TheStorm #TheStormIsHere #WeThePeople #FollowTheWhiteRabbit #GreatAwakeningWorldwide https://t.co/0eXd6Wtkpd 
 5) What was being worked on? &quot;science fiction-like brain scanning technology&quot; #QAnon #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA #redpilled https://t.co/tjp3rEDkPY 
 6) Whatever her real intentions were at #Facebook, she got her tentacles in quickly, leaving after only 18 months. Now working on an undisclosed endeavor. Wanna bet it&apos;s connected? #QAnon #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA https://t.co/8uNHQ16gzD 
 7) So what is #DARPA for, really? My view is that it&apos;s a pipeline. DARPA &amp;gt; Find a stooge &amp;gt; Form company &amp;gt; Pull strings, fund &amp;gt; Make company appear legit &amp;gt; Go public, get rich &amp;gt; Deep state control &amp;gt; Rinse and repeat #QAnon #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA @POTUS https://t.co/NWawXyiaA0 
 8) See my tweet from yesterday. #LifeLog became #Facebook. &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a fantasy. #QAnon #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA https://t.co/K41Gfvk8mL 
 9) Google? #DARPA https://t.co/cZII5WRxCB 
 10) Eric Schmidt who left #Alphabet (#Google parent company)? Bell Labs, a cutout of #DARPA. https://t.co/iG87EaCIwa 
 11) The #CIA sure seems active in the business of funding companies using DARPA resources, doesn&apos;t it? When did it become commonplace for an agency with a very specific mission to take on such a role? #QAnon #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA https://t.co/PpcEzk2mhh 
 12) Look at the list for yourself, draw inferences on what types of intentions exist for this list, and how it sure does look like an all encompassing and complete surveillance state based in #SiliconValley. https://t.co/MkOSNumaqe 
 13) My theory is #Palantir is lynchpin. See highlighted. What can tie all these social media platforms together into a complete picture of every individual, look again at #LifeLog. The goal here should be obvious. #Zuckerbergtestimony was very uncomfortable when asked about it. https://t.co/ZAE78UpaLb 
 14) Since #PatriotAct, we&apos;re in surveillance overdrive. The limitations of laws on spying agencies are ignored by creating public companies to do it completely outside of the government. Now do you see why tech remains unregulated &amp;amp; tons of money flows into congress in lobbying? 
 15) Regina Dugan is not unique. There&apos;s an army of these people running around, and it&apos;s growing. Things like the Math Olympics are recruiting grounds for finding and positioning new people. All these companies are involved. This is quite a web. #QAnon #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA #CIA https://t.co/sAJA93sdPP</texto><total_retweets type="int">291</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">370</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">34</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">37</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1623794972</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">11222</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">39</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">10786</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.5565009939878032</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>