<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">401</hilo><total_tweets type="int">30</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) This is my #Qanon thread for May 21, 2018. Q posts can be found here: https://t.co/yeNLF0baB0 Q Drops for iOs: https://t.co/k0wewV8QGI Q Alerts for Android: https://t.co/CjL6Rqkc5K My theme: Meet The New Q - Same As The Old Q 
 2) There&apos;s been speculation that #QAnon has been compromised, has been subverted by the deep state or that the current Q is not the same Q who posted in October-November of last year. This thread will hopefully put those fears to rest. https://t.co/qpJUfQYSeI 
 3) Once again, #Qanon posted a link to the Breitbart article explaining why allowing John Huber to conduct his investigation under Jeff Sessions is a better option than appointing a second Special Counsel. Link: https://t.co/z58QSiVeUy https://t.co/TTopWNiTOD 
 4) #Qanon&apos;s post is a response to the well-meaning but misguided House Republicans who pushed for the appointment of a second Special Counsel. https://t.co/h6itM5vPjo 
 5) #Qanon asked if we&apos;ve seen the interview with Paul Ryan. I assume he speaking of this one, where he admits that President Trump&apos;s request to have the Justice Department IG look into politicization is warranted. [Future proves past] https://t.co/Hq2d312zr1 
 6) An anon posted a screenshot from @TheLastRefuge2 about Nellie Ohr&apos;s HAM radio license. Nellie is Bruce Orh&apos;s wife. Both were heavily involved in the creation and dissemination of the Steel Dossier. https://t.co/cEmQYzeKym 
 7) Background info on Bruce and Nellie Orh and their HAM radio license. #Qanon https://t.co/plNfPWQgZk 
 8) #Qanon said Ohr&apos;s use of the HAM radio was an attempt to evade the NSA. https://t.co/xrDFuhImqO 
 9) An anon caught the reference #Qanon made previously about &quot;Rapid Fire&quot; and &quot;Flood is coming.&quot; https://t.co/b7BNNwtV4h 
 10) #Qanon responded. https://t.co/T9fAlEONqR 
 11) On November 9th, while POTUS was visiting Asia, #Qanon posted this image on 4chan. Note the filename and metadata: _AF1_5A_2.png, 988KiB, 720x1280 The implication is that Q travels with or has access to the President while he&apos;s on Air Force 1 Link: https://t.co/KEbStuIchP https://t.co/eg0PMFcx6T 
 12) Today, due to speculation that #Qanon is not the original Q who posted in October and November, he posted two pictures that seem to be taken just seconds apart. The one on the left is the original image posted in November. The one on the right has the filename: _AF1_5A_3.png https://t.co/MHAVHzCxaD 
 13) An anon made these observations. (How could a phony #Qanon have a second image like the one that was posted in November? https://t.co/UPK4fLYptB 
 14) Another anon made this observation. #Qanon https://t.co/IRbMlffX1t 
 15) #Qanon said the second photo was provided as proof if identity because he and the team know attacks are coming and they will intensify. https://t.co/ATRoJR4Sm2 
 16) An anon felt bad for not correcting his spelling, not knowing thousands of people would see his post. (Sorry, mate.) 👍🏼😎 https://t.co/q3aLXO3Kya 
 17) #Qanon remined the anons, we&apos;re seeking unity, not division. He posted a link to a news article about Thursday&apos;s meeting concerning the Inspector General investigatigation of the Russia probe. He noted that Rod Rosenstein would not be there but Ed O&apos;Callaghan would. *Pain https://t.co/sgmBxRrEsL 
 18) An anon apologized for those who are still causing division. #Qanon https://t.co/h7ObFNEl11 
 19) Info on the meeting that #Qanon referenced. https://t.co/VTTUqmbVgd https://t.co/jRcbg6AwI1 
 20) Info on Ed O&apos;Callaghan [TRUST O&apos;Callaghan] #Qanon https://t.co/5HSeq5gWNz https://t.co/J5YpL6tev5 
 21) An anon put together this graphic of the &quot;Pain in -23&quot; post. #Qanon https://t.co/xHrLVnRg1k 
 22) To my fellow healthcare providers: Remember, pain is an important vital sign that should always be documented. #Qanon https://t.co/63h4ZysBXG 
 23) Enjoy the show. #Qanon https://t.co/cKbzMxnChX 
 24) I had 3 dreams last night about the mission we&apos;re on with #Qanon. I&apos;d like to share one dream with you now. In the dream, I saw the takedown of global corruption from a 40,000 ft view. It took many people working together to accomplish this incredible task. 
 25) I saw not just people like @LisaMei62, @paul_serran &amp;amp; @tracybeanz but also people like Sundance (@TheLastRefuge2). While Sundance doesn&apos;t necessarily follow Q, he does incredible investigative work that many of us rely on. 
 26) It&apos;s easy to overlook people who don&apos;t post about #Qanon but we ought to include them in our prayers and we should support them on social media. 
 27) If Q and his team are who we believe them to be, we&apos;ll be standing at the end of this journey alongside many who did not follow #QAnon&apos;s crumbs. We may have a little better idea today of where it&apos;s all going, but on that day we will acknowledge all who made contributions. 
 28) Since the takedown of global corruption is the goal for many who do not follow #Qanon why not embrace all who are working toward that goal, whether they embrace Q or not? 
 29) What have we gained if we manage to eradicate evil from the face of the earth but have not removed it from our own hearts? #Qanon 
 #Qanon https://t.co/39Y6WPY7PZ</texto><total_retweets type="int">3545</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">11500</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">300</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">83932539</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">184948</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">58009</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">45917</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.913862994504708</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>