<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">71</hilo><total_tweets type="int">8</total_tweets><texto type="str">Steve Bannon and the Mercers &quot;invested millions&quot; into a company that &quot;specialized in military intelligence and psychological warfare.&quot; Bannon became a Vice President. https://t.co/9Te7xGoGtX 
 &quot;In June 2016, the Trump campaign was flailing... the Mercers... offered Trump a huge cash injection, but they insisted he hire Steve Bannon and their company #CambridgeAnalytica&quot; 
 .@Channel4News reveals how Trump, Bannon and the Mercers conspired to abuse the post-#CitizensUnited &quot;dark money&quot; electoral system: &quot;Positive messages went through the candidate&apos;s official campaign, but the nasty stuff was pushed through outside organizations&quot; 
 Channel 4: &quot;Coordination between a candidate and these groups is ILLEGAL under US election law.&quot; With the #Mercers funding both Trump and outside SuperPACs, #CambridgeAnalytica&apos;s activities &quot;broke the rules&quot; #CrookedDonald 
 Cambridge Analytica&apos;s intensive psy ops campign &quot;directly targeted Bernie Sanders voters to prevent them from voting&quot; for Hillary Clinton -- and overran search engines, making real information harder to find. #FakeNews #Propaganda 
 In addition to the Cambridge Analytica campaign, Russia targeted the same voters with similar messaging that reached 126 million Americans #TrumpRussia #TrumpColluded https://t.co/9Te7xGoGtX 
 CEO Alexander Nix claims that the #GOP was barely interested in investigating #CambridgeAnalytica&apos;s blatant crimes: &quot;The Republicans asked 3 questions. 5 minutes, done... they don&apos;t understand how it works... the candidate is never involved&quot; 
 Undercover reporter: &quot;So the candidate is the puppet?&quot; #CambridgeAnalytica CEO Alexander Nix: &quot;Always.&quot; https://t.co/jYrZrZfek5</texto><total_retweets type="int">1443</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1732</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">42</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">179732982</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">182245</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">132018</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">73609</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8594952596275024</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>