<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">134</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">House Democrats introduce bill prohibiting sale of semi-automatic weapons. Please realize what this means. The Democrats are trying to take our guns! #NeverGetOurGuns Spread this hashtag #AssaultWeaponsBan #ShallNotBeInfringed #DefendtheSecond #NRA @POTUS /1 https://t.co/YrdTnU9hke 
 House Democrats have introduced a bill banning semi-automatic firearms in the wake of the Feb. 14 shooting at a high school in Parkland, Fla. /2 #NeverGetOurGuns @realDonaldTrump 
 Rep. David Cicilline, D-R.I., announced Monday he is introducing the Assault Weapons Ban of 2018. More than 150 Democrats have signed on in support of the legislation, Rep. Ted Deutch, D-Fla., said. /3 #NeverGetOurGuns 
 &quot;Today I joined @RepCicilline &amp;amp; 150+ of my colleagues to introduce the assault weapons ban. It’s time for Congress to listen to the will of a majority of Americans &amp;amp; pass sensible legislation to get these weapons of war off our streets. #NeverAgain #MSDStrong,&quot; Deutch tweeted. /4 https://t.co/1RkmEOkNx7 
 The bill prohibits the “sale, transfer, production, and importation” of semi-automatic rifles and pistols that can hold a detachable magazine, as well as semi-automatic rifles with a magazine that can hold more than 10 rounds. Folks, that’s all handguns minus revolvers. /5 
 Additionally, the legislation bans the sale, transfer, production, and importation of semi-automatic shotguns with features such as a pistol grip or detachable stock, and ammunition feeding devices that can hold more than 10 rounds. /6 
 Cicilline’s legislation names 205 specific firearms that are prohibited, including the AK-47 and AR-15. “Assault weapons were made for one purpose,” Cicilline said in a statement. “They are designed to kill as many people as possible in a short amount of time. /7 
 They do not belong in our communities.” We knew this was what all these school “shootings” were about. This will not stand. They will not take our 2nd Amendment and our 1st Amendment Rights away. /8 #SupportNRA #IAmTheNRA https://t.co/aqxI90WflC 
 Democrats are all about control. Once they pass this law there will be no going back. It will be much easier to get rid of all guns after this. We must not allow this to happen. These are our rights they are trampling on. /9 
 The Second Amendment to our Constitution is clear. The right of the people to keep and bear Arms shall not be infringed upon. Period. The Second Amendment guarantees a fundamental right that belongs to all law-abiding Americans. /10 
 The Constitution doesn’t create that right – it ensures that the government can’t take it away. Our Founding Fathers knew, and our Supreme Court has upheld, that the Second Amendment’s purpose is to guarantee our right to defend ourselves and our families. /11 
 This is about self-defense, plain and simple. It’s been said that the Second Amendment is America’s first freedom. That’s because the Right to Keep and Bear Arms protects all our other rights. /12 
 I don’t share this often but it is important now. I was raped, beaten and left for dead at the tender age of 15. I will never feel that vulnerable again. I will never be unarmed and unable to defend myself and my family. /13 https://t.co/m623UDfWT6 
 Let’s make this hashtag go viral. /end #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns #NeverGetOurGuns</texto><total_retweets type="int">2666</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2630</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">497</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1249831310</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">57737</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">45195</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">125873</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8419765762236604</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>