<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">13</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">All you need to know about &quot;Bill Kristol&quot;: -he supported Obama -he voted for #CrookedHillary -he fears Donald Trump -his favorite president was George W. Bush If you think ANY of those things make him a hero, you might be a Communist. Don&apos;t believe me? Read on. https://t.co/YQuc4JcbIg 
 &quot;Between Obama’s mother, grandfather, Kenyan father, and Frank Marshall Davis, those are some pretty extreme political influences.&quot; https://t.co/8VLlmFSoY5 
 &quot;He came to me to make sure I was supporting his sound policies. Of course, since his sound policies are more like the policies people like me have been advocating for quite a while, I’m happy to support them. He’s a born-again neo-con.&quot; https://t.co/xKCasN97Ya 
 &quot;(FBI) files obtained by Judicial Watch reveal that the dad, maternal grandpa and father-in-law of President Obama’s trusted senior advisor, Valerie Jarrett, were hardcore Communists under investigation by the U.S. government.&quot; https://t.co/rAW8youQXS 
 Remember, in this context, the &quot;status quo&quot; is the leadership of Barack Obama and his Globalist administration: https://t.co/qDgR2n4IaY 
 And then there&apos;s the company he keeps on the &quot;Right&quot;, a veritable who&apos;s-who of political cronyism and corruption, eagerly greasing the wheels of the Globalist war &amp;amp; destabilization machine: https://t.co/nMt9IsYsXg 
 &quot;The neoconservative founders included James Burnham, Max Shactman, Leo Strauss, Suzanne LaFollette, Willmoore Kendall, and IRVING KRISTOL. When you go over the histories of these men, one uncovers that they all came from communist, specifically Trotskyist, backgrounds.&quot; https://t.co/NNFKqZsLAz 
 &quot;...Trotsky ... argued that a bureaucracy would only empower the middle-class and oppress the workers. Instead he argued that an empowered FEUDALIST STATE at the expense of the middle class would lead to communism.&quot; https://t.co/qRTdfgkG40 
 So there you have it: Neoconservatism = Globalism = Trotskyism = NeoFeudalism #NotOnMyWatch #NeverAgain https://t.co/h7qv4fZHRg 
 @threadreaderapp unroll please</texto><total_retweets type="int">60</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">105</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">15</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">787318013817155584</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">8427</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">9170</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">50645</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7910912705337847</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>