<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">206</hilo><total_tweets type="int">17</total_tweets><texto type="str">#IamReading https://t.co/dssLUvxa2h 
 #Aurangzeb lived 91 years. In death wrote will dividing the empire among three sons. Bahadurshah who was given 12 provinces killed other two but died in another 12 years #History 
 Bahadurshah’s son Jahandaar Shah killed his brothers and became #Mughal emperor in 1712, and his mistress, Lal Kunwar ruled by proxy. She was paid 2 Cr per Annum. The first NAC Of Delhi 😂🤦‍♂️ 
 Jahaandar Shah was beheaded by his nephew in 1713, and 6 years of turmoil ended with Jahaandar Shah’s Son, Muhammad Shah’s ascendancy in 1719. #Mughal 
 Nadirshah arrived with defeated Muhammad Shah on 7th March. Nadirshah left Delhi, re-appointing Muhammad Shah on 5th May, 1737, taking entire Afghanistan in ransom. #History #Mughal 
 Portuguese annexed Goa in 1510. The first European colony was established in #India 16 years before Babur entered India to establish #Mughal empire. 
 There is not one scientific innovation or invention could be attributed to the entire duration of #Mughal rule. 
 In the war between Dara and Aurangzeb, Dara was supported by 49 Muslim kings and 14 #Rajput, #Aurangzeb had 9 Rajputs, 10 Maratha and 2 other #Hindu kings supporting him #History 
 The #British diluted the power of Muslim landowners, took law n order from them, made their position non-hereditary and opened administrative roles for #Hindus causing animosity 
 For the first time ever, under the British, #Muslims saw #Hindus as challenge to Islamic supremacy 
 One reason for sudden rise in the #Hindu stake in British administrative structure could be because while in population Hindus were 2:1 to #Muslims, in education proportion was 19:1 (William Adams report 1835,36 and 38) 
 Lord Bishop Heber wrote - it needs to be consistently reminded to the #Hindus that we (British) haven’t enslaved them, they already were conquered (1824) 
 While structured education for Muslims began 10 year before #Hindus, first #Hindu college began 10 years before Muslim college in Aligarh. English education was brought in at the behest of Bengali Intellectuals 
 While from #Hindus a prominent voice of Raja Ram Mohan Roy pleaded with British to bring in modern English education, #Muslims never volunteered 
 Between 1858 to 1878, 57 #Muslims Graduated, while 3155 #Hindus did 
 Before #Hindus readily took to the #British education, their liberal mind already had allowed them to learn Persian when it was the language of administration. Muslims had earlier opposed Sanakrit as they later opposed English 
 In the Mutiny of 1857, #Hindus were unsuspecting tools for #Muslims who fought to bring Islamic rule back. #Instructions we’re coming from the mosques. Jama Masjid was closed for five years.</texto><total_retweets type="int">24</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">25</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">20</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">11</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">67835392</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">15612</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1100</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">159285</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0375326628459471</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>