<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">362</hilo><total_tweets type="int">30</total_tweets><texto type="str">Did your invitation to Windsor Castle get lost in the mail? If so, @JarrieBradshaw has you covered with our #RoyalWedding coverage! https://t.co/Ml5palbnCU 
 #DYK Colleen Harris, the Former Press Secretary to Princes Charles, William and Harry, was the first black royal press secretary #RoyalWedding https://t.co/FO9BMonBix 
 Oprah whipped together a last minute dress because the one she ordered was entirely too white for the #RoyalWedding. Her and Idris have arrived to celebrate #HarryandMeghan https://t.co/jgbfRaTPnd 
 Here’s a first look at the setting for today’s #RoyalWedding of #HarryandMeghan in St. George’s Chapel https://t.co/xRrdlzdtuT 
 Windsor Castle is almost 1,000 years old. 🗣YOU LOOK GOOD! #RoyalWedding https://t.co/x38v7k10Be 
 .@GayleKing is giving your favorite church auntie a run for her money and says she’ll be changing hats every hour on the hour to celebrate the #RoyalWedding. https://t.co/DL2aBaD7Sk 
 .@Oprah is out here in her Sunday’s best giving us #EasterSunday lewks! #RoyalWedding https://t.co/6XTGcrIgnn 
 Prince Harry’s ex girlfriend is at the wedding? #RoyalWedding https://t.co/6dn5GCcg0k 
 This is fine. Everything’s fine. Nothing to see here. Prince Harry’s ex #RoyalWedding https://t.co/hJN0j8cBdZ 
 I heard, that you&apos;re settled down That you’ve found a girl and you&apos;re, getting married now... #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/6Zng9cYQ9k 
 .@serenawilliams, a casual slay #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/3Im0e4LaOe 
 “Wait, Meghan pushed things back 15 minutes? Look at her bringing CP time to the monarchy.” - @onlychyld #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/KBO0HG53zs 
 “God is love, and all who live in love live in God, and God lives in them.” #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/6D4zws9u8K 
 May all your future husbands look at you like Harry looks at Meghan. #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMehgan https://t.co/tJqHOt16n6 
 Does anyone object to this union?? #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/sNdkw4MYWC 
 “I wonder if there will be fish and chips at the reception.” #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/jGzEbrU8oD 
 “We must discover the power of love, the power, the redemptive power of love.” #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/ngpm8sEKDa 
 There’s a black pastor quoting MLK and mentioning negro spirituals at the #RoyalWedding https://t.co/GhEzmwsN3k 
 When love is the way there’s plenty good room for all of God’s children because when love is the way, we actually treat each other like we’re actually family. When love is the way, we know that God is the source of us all. #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/hIhEIPtb2d 
 “Dr King was right when he said we must discover the redemptive power of love.” #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/hZii9LrvwD 
 Wait, we just had a black preacher talk about slavery and MLK and now we’re getting Ben E. King’s “Stand By Me” Meghan Markle done brought the Black church to Windsor Castle. #RoyalWedding https://t.co/2H4HbyXo42 
 Look. At. These. Facts. #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/arvsqQwA8W 
 “In the presence of God, I make this vow.” #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/MGFDLU3TNP 
 What God has joined together, let no man put asunder. #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/cxgDtvmN3c 
 I now pronounce you husband and wife. #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/VuRn1xlkV8 
 Now black cellist, Sheku Kanneh-Mason?!?! #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/I2g4gAGKMi 
 Reminder: Knowing someone does not automatically grant you an invitation to their wedding. https://t.co/DuwSMzN2qW #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/jSd3uXKl1c 
 Wait... this little light of mine?! This wedding was so black that they’ll probably have pound cake and do the wobble/electric slide at the reception. #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/pa9CksqaPz 
 Hello 911, it’s me, Susan.. I’m at Windsor Castle and it’s very ethnic. There’s a black preacher, a black choir and Officer I think a black man with some form of instrument. I fear they’re about to start the wobble. I don’t feel safe: https://t.co/sobLaQMegO #RoyalWedding https://t.co/C2kcyj1CSn 
 Hello officer, it’s me, Susan. There’s a prince marrying a black woman... this cannot be right. I don’t feel safe. https://t.co/sobLaQMegO #RoyalWedding #HarryAndMeghan https://t.co/Q49FLOKjqm</texto><total_retweets type="int">10053</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">34197</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">173</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">23995748</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">492923</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14479</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">118895</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.103087630420912</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>