<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">313</hilo><total_tweets type="int">24</total_tweets><texto type="str">Attention. Priority: #TheResistance Counter-Intelligence briefing. This briefing is long, in-depth, and has two parts: 1) Counter-Intel History. 2) Adaptations to Social Media. #Resistance #Resist #ResistanceUnited https://t.co/ai3tinms3f 
 I rarely snap my fingers and demand attention, but this is very important, and I would kindly ask that you share this thread if you feel that I have earned it. #ImpeachTrump #TrumpRussia #RefusePolarization #ResistTogether #UniteBlue https://t.co/ihS2JnCvR4 
 Clearly the US is under a counter-intel (CI) attack. But what is CI and how does it function? Let&apos;s look at the overall picture, and some specific case-studies. #RussianPropaganda on social media is a form of offensive CI, which #TheResistance intends to counter. https://t.co/iU1dgD0Isx 
 Looking at history, one of the most successful CI strategies is referred to as “Sharpening Contradiction.” From Bolsheviks to I.S. Terrorist groups, rebels, and states alike use this method. https://t.co/Wj7suYesCy https://t.co/XJZR3e3H0S 
 “Sharpening Contradiction” is not always used violently, though. In politics, we have what are called “wedge issues,” and these issues are used almost in the same manner as a terrorist attack: Divide. Isolate. Ostracize. Recruit. https://t.co/Vbx8cToZM0 
 For example: If wished to divide HRC supporters from Bernie supporters, I would pose as a Berner, then relentlessly attack HRC supporters as being weak-minded and corporatist. This agitates #WithHer folks not just against me, but against what I claim to represent. https://t.co/byayrNEdY6 
 The above example occurred demonstrably both before and after the 2016 primary. Of course, there were also unfair attacks against Bernie folk, too. This is not about pointing fingers, this is about illustrating how easy some CI techniques are to execute. 
 Doing so “sharpens contradiction” between the two sides of any debate, and soon, the CI agent will no longer have to act at all. As their bad-faith actions are transformed into avatars in the collective mind of the opposing side. https://t.co/8bfC7UJGIo 
 I realize the above example may open fresh wounds for some. So, let&apos;s take a look at a case study from history, shall we? Hopefully we can examine this rationally: The Case of Samuel Dickstein. https://t.co/7qZmlyRhlH https://t.co/qwtoOl9LAD 
 Pretend I am a bright Stalin-era Soviet CI agent, and I wish to sharpen contradictions in the US. I would recruit a US Congressman, then have him found an anti-Communist committee. This committee would investigate both real communists and innocents. 
 The committee would grow over time and charge hundreds of innocent people, all while sharpening contradiction and feeding me real info on potential recruits. I use this to create networks of real spies, while American Politics is in chaos. https://t.co/xDINFPuv8B 
 And descends into the darkness and paranoia of the McCarthy and HUAC years. All while no one suspects my real agent was the impetus of it all. And indeed, my real agent will still have a plaza named after him in NYC. https://t.co/JzDe5HZXrq https://t.co/CIWVNjoS3j 
 The Dickstein case is arguably the most successful CI operation of the Cold War. But there were countless others. More commonly, the CIA and KGB would publish books, editorials, and even produce radio and TV programs throughout the world. 
 Most notably in Latin America and Eastern Europe, the propaganda from both sides could be intense, and these CI operations often coincided with traditional Ops, like the funding of the Contras and the Pinochet coup d&apos;etat in Chile. https://t.co/L3prs6h55D https://t.co/zYBdEw2th4 
 The US also had CI operations against its own citizens, most notably the FBI&apos;s CoIntelPro, aimed at many targets, left and right, it remains one of our greatest moral failures of the century. https://t.co/nlnvLL1nFW 
 COINTELPRO, run by the openly racist J Edgar Hoover, did significant damage to the civil rights movement. All in an era of communist paranoia, increasing lies about Vietnam, and looming nuclear war. https://t.co/AtGQb3IxWn 
 At this time, the head of CIA&apos;s CI, James Jesus Angleton, was slipping further and further into a spiral of paranoia, jumping at shadows and seeing enemies at every turn, even within the CIA. And the CIA itself became involved in Contras and Coups. https://t.co/ffmow7vWYC 
 Nixon committed treason before even entering office. LBJ knew this, Intel operations caught Nixon telling South Vietnam to scuttle peace talks in 1968, to give him a better postition in the election. https://t.co/sV9nTK1VKz https://t.co/6wzh6L9wiT 
 We had a government with more holes than a seive, racist attacks on civil rights, war in Vietnam, paranoid, traitorous and corrupt leaders, JFK and RFK assassinated, specter of nuclear war, CI attacks against democracy. . . and we still won. 
 We smashed the Nazi war machine. We passed the Civil Rights Act. We passed the 24 Amendment. We defeated McCarthyism. We ended the Vietnam War. We forced Nixon to resign. We defeated the USSR. And we ushered in an era of prosperity that lasted more than 40 years. https://t.co/ky9JLrhOrS 
 And our opponents now? Trump, a septigenarian braggard. Bannon, an alcoholic anti-semite. A shirtless Putin, and his meme-slinging frogs. Don&apos;t make me laugh. Let&apos;s show them the forces of Democracy, Liberty, and Equality are not so easily cowed. 
 So, come! Shout it to the rooftops with me! #RiseUp ! “When you&apos;re livin&apos; on your knees you rise up! Tell your brother that he&apos;s gotta rise up! Tell your sister that she&apos;s gotta rise up! https://t.co/fB2BBWWbZh 
 This ends the first part of the thread. Part two will tackle how CI Ops have adapted to social media, and how they are being used against #TheResistance. Thank you for listening. #HappyNewYear https://t.co/AtpYIg19UV 
 Part 2, Adaptations to Social Media, may be found here: https://t.co/AYx8HkXaC7</texto><total_retweets type="int">1202</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2217</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">98</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">13</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">392212735</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">22961</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">20014</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">7984</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.822621617229562</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>