<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">249</hilo><total_tweets type="int">17</total_tweets><texto type="str">OK. Time to help, again, with the narrative. Here is what happened: 1. Soviet Union collapses, Russia becomes a &quot;Mafiya State.&quot; This means: organized crime took over everything from FSB (🇷🇺FBI) to Presidency. Putin = OC mixed w/ Kremlin in tactics. This history is undisputed. 
 2. The primary, and highest profile, whistle-blower was Alexander (&quot;Sasha&quot;) Litvinenko: an FSB officer in the ORGANIZED CRIME division. https://t.co/OKESnfccpq 
 3. AT THE SAME TIME that Russian Mafia was taking over Russian state, they were also coming HERE. Where they rolled over La Cosa Nostra, and took over key operations - as well as committed their own crimes/scams. https://t.co/yHRjRwFiEA 
 4. Bob Levinson, former FBI who specialized in La Cosa Nostra, was the whistle-blower 4 this take-over. He was also an expert trial witness for one of the more dangerous Russian mafia capos, who lived/worked out of Trump properties. https://t.co/H2yaWrYGIA https://t.co/VhNGcYoY56 
 5. Both men continued 2 hunt down Russian OC. Litvinenko w/MI6 in London (where he was in exile, b/c Putin was after him), &amp;amp; Bob as consultant for CIA Financial Crimes Div (b/c &quot;Follow The Money&quot;). Russian OC is a complicated octopus. But it had a brain at this point in history. https://t.co/acOiSzd9eR 
 6. You can see Semion/Semyon Mogilevich, aka the &quot;Brainy Don&quot;, here at Putin&apos;s 2000 election campaign HQ. He turns to the camera at 1:15. https://t.co/7F9W9p8MCE As Litvinenko said, RUSSIA IS A MAFIA STATE. 
 7. That same &quot;Boss of Bosses&quot;, Semion Mogilevich, is who was sending his lieutenants to U.S. shores. They rolled over La Cosa Nostra, and found their home in Trump properties. https://t.co/lZBxKdWWKO THIS IS WELL-DOCUMENTED and UNDISPUTED. 
 8. You just have 2 gather all the court documents, FBI/ Intel reports, &amp;amp; investigative reporting over 3+ decades. We did this. It was a massive under-taking, but the history &amp;amp; record do not lie. Which is Y we provide all the data for U 2 read thru as well. https://t.co/Xr257KDqhv 
 9. When you combine this understanding with all of Trump Org&apos;s ties to La Cosa Nostra - from the time of Fred Trump, the picture is crystal clear. Donald Trump is a money-laundering front for organized crime. And always has been. https://t.co/DIi0ueAqTj 
 10. All that we&apos;re witnessing - everything that has seemed unnatural &amp;amp; confusing about Donald &amp;amp; his agenda is due to this. He was raised by mobsters &amp;amp; relied on them 4 his &quot;empire.&quot; He speaks like them. He behaves like them. He&apos;s owned by them. NOW, as President... 
 11. He is enabling their transnational empire. HE IS PROTECTING THEM. Even when you&apos;re reading about Chris Steele - and the flares he was sending up about Trump as an &quot;asset&quot; of Russia, remember what Russia is: A MAFIA STATE. The Kremlin = The Mob. Got it? 
 12. In 2005, Alexander Litvinenko&apos;s work w/ MI6 had resulted in a significant arrests of Russian organized crime bosses in Spain (this work also led to more arrests in 2008). It was a kick in the teeth to associates of Semion&apos;s. https://t.co/tLeIBCtr9f 
 13. At that same time, Bob Levinson was working with an informant of his from within Semion&apos;s circle - on a hunt for CIA financial crimes division. That informant was BORIS BIRSHTEIN. The father-in-law of Donald&apos;s business partner in Trump Tower Toronto. https://t.co/Pc5zkINPuN https://t.co/5iccBPaQzd 
 14. Birshtein sent Bob to IRAN to meet someone, who Birshtein had convinced Bob could help him in his hunt. He never came home. In 2006, within months of each other, Litvinenko was fatally poisoned with polonium, and Bob Levinson was kidnapped in Kish, Iran. - END - https://t.co/RtdpwhXMBt 
 CODA. A chart for you. https://t.co/4aE6QXWvCU 
 CODA #2 - VERY IMPORTANT. See that Birshtein meeting described in the screenshot above - tweet #13 in this thread? That&apos;s the meeting that our Intel community knew about. It was instrumental in generating this FBI report on SEMION&apos;S EMPIRE (CONTINUED...) https://t.co/0mq4Y93Vl7 
 BOB knew all about that report. He gave it to Tom Mangold, a British journalist, who got one of the only interviews with Semion on record. Here&apos;s a clip. https://t.co/es4Gix4Olt Here&apos;s the full interview/ report - turned into a special for Panorama. https://t.co/irDZwXBex9</texto><total_retweets type="int">7187</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">12417</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">153</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">536904693</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">75307</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">710</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">43065</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.2660971474761018</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>