<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">6</hilo><total_tweets type="int">8</total_tweets><texto type="str">REALITY CHECK: Pruitt has spent $3 MILLION on security and travel in just over a year. His security detail is three times as large as his predecessors, yet the AP found no court records of cases of anyone being arrested for threatening Pruitt. #BootPruitt https://t.co/HfbjejphZ6 
 REALITY CHECK: Here&apos;s where you could stay in DC for the rent Pruitt was paying his fossil fuel lobbyist landlord (though his rent was late, so the landlord changed the locks). Spoiler alert; These aren&apos;t super fancy like Pruitt&apos;s luxury condo #BootPruitt https://t.co/faCKPh0iti 
 REALITY CHECK: While Pruitt is a dangerous threat to the health of our families, his sloppy and careless legal work is undermining his ability to even implement his extreme pro-polluter agenda in several key cases. #BootPruitt https://t.co/lZKNC2kUjf 
 REALITY CHECK: Trump is defending a guy who regularly defies him....#BootPruitt https://t.co/FfsB2TKhOZ 
 ....over and over again. #BootPruitt https://t.co/JGA39bmuuj 
 REALITY CHECK: Trump is also defending the guy who called him an &quot;empty vessel.&quot; https://t.co/ovfQIUUssn #BootPruitt 
 REALITY CHECK: To top it all off, Pruitt&apos;s spending and behavior is because, according to many, he wants “to be treated like he was the president.” #BootPruitt https://t.co/OJxkNFsYDT 
 Pruitt is a danger to the public, yet is losing in the courts while conning @realDonaldTrump into saving his job...all while defying &amp;amp; insulting his boss. Perhaps Trump is the empty vessel Scott Pruitt said he is. That would explain how Pruitt so easily conned him. #BootPruitt</texto><total_retweets type="int">514</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">686</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">32</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">34113439</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">349243</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">5015</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">119606</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.17929943006988</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>