<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">352</hilo><total_tweets type="int">30</total_tweets><texto type="str">&amp;lt;INTEL TECHNIQUE THREAD&amp;gt; If the Steele Dossier is going to get used by media to drive suspicion, then let&apos;s talk about how HUMINT tradecraft works. https://t.co/S6kXs55UYf 
 NOTE: WHEN WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THIS STUFF IN PUBLIC, IT MEANS THINGS ARE VERY WEIRD. That said, it&apos;s 2017, and we&apos;re discussing how &quot;HUMINT&quot; gets verified. Huh? 
 HUMINT is spook jargon for Human Intelligence - the information derived from people. &quot;We know a guy. He said X.&quot; This is in contrast to IMINT, Image Intelligence, or SIGINT, Signals Intelligence. 
 Satellite pix, etc: IMINT (Or GEOINT, don&apos;t @ me @NGA_GEOINT) Radio, email, phone calls, etc: SIGINT Talking to folks: HUMINT Steele Dossier is &quot;raw&quot; HUMINT. 
 BTW, I rarely drag out creds on this, but I started as a HUMINT collector in competitive intelligence (for business) 20 years ago. My company now teaches these subjects, if you&apos;re interested and/or bored. 😎 https://t.co/BZVi9pc7Ll 
 Collecting information out of people (and knowing when they&apos;re running a play on me): Why yes? In fact, that&apos;s right up my alley! (Thanks to all you fun people in my DMs) 😀 
 SO. BACK TO THE STEELE DOSSIER. Christopher Steele was the subcontractor to Fusion GPS. The project? What Is Up With Trump and Russia? He collected a HUMINT &quot;dossier.&quot; https://t.co/K6wvQO7Wgq 
 BTW - another quick tangent - like many things, referring to them in French makes them Fancy. Dossier is French for &quot;file folder.&quot; THE STEELE MANILA FILE FOLDER doesn&apos;t sound like nearly the spy novel, does it? https://t.co/bcnEdaMpve 
 So, speaking as someone asked to put together HUMINT networks and projects based off them, here&apos;s what a &quot;raw HUMINT dossier&quot; really is. YOU GUYS READY? OMG SO EXCITING! 
 *This is going to get so sexy. OMG. HUMINT. SPYING. MARTINIS. SEX WITH BIKINI CHICKS IN MONACO!* HUMINT: You get some people who&apos;ll tell you stuff. WHOA, RIGHT https://t.co/rXbUovjrAp 
 Well, let me hip you to a slightly more realistic (but nevertheless important) image of the SEXXXYNESS OF HUMINT. See pic attached! https://t.co/e4ynJrhyv2 
 Popular conception: You dress up as the President of Peru and infiltrate a U.N. gathering and suck out the juiciest info from other heads of state to save the day! Reality: You have dudes you know. Or you have people who know some dudes. Or whatever. 
 And you get what you can that week, and put it in a report. BTW, in a lot of agencies, the collector only knows what he/she knows. Only the analysts back home can process it. 
 So you float around and have conversations. Chats. You relaxedly say, &quot;Hey, Nicholas, what&apos;s new, man?&quot; And (with well-trained skills) you try to &quot;elicit&quot; a juicy bit without much notice. 
 FUN FACT: There&apos;s a U-shaped curve for collector effectiveness. At first, you don&apos;t really know what you&apos;re doing, so you don&apos;t give off a weird vibe. Then, you seem a little weird. Then, later, you DGAF. 🤣 
 SO. I&apos;m reading the book COLLUSION (page turner, fun book, read it, not paid to say so, it&apos;s great) and it tells Steele&apos;s story. He used two or three degrees of separation for the Dossier. 
 This means - totally understandably, given his experience - he sure didn&apos;t dress up like a housekeeper and roam around Moscow. He had a network. 
 He had people who knew people - who didn&apos;t know Steele. Pros and cons here. Pro: You and your clients are protected. Con: Who the hell gave us this? 
 If your subcontractors are any good, they don&apos;t tell YOU everything, either. They want you protected, and their special value preserved. 
 SO, Steele tells us that he set up a network with a lot of deniability - which may not have worked great since Putin had a bunch of people killed connected to this. 
 That means two things: Steele got stuff he never could on his own. (Nobody knows everyone useful in any area.) Steele couldn&apos;t himself verify, precisely, the quality of the output. 
 SO, we&apos;re a year plus later. There&apos;s a BOOK out about Steele&apos;s experience. And TrumpCo is in major hot water. OMG BUT WHUT ABOUT THE DOSSIER? NO VERRIFICCATIONNS? 
 Well...of course not! I&apos;m going from personal experience here: nobody&apos;s gonna reproduce your work. If you admit all your sources, they&apos;re burned - and when it&apos;s national security THEY ARE DEAD DEAD DEAD. Especially with Russia. 
 ERGO, when you read &quot;THEY COULDN&apos;t *GASP* VERIFY THE DOSSIER!&quot; Of course not, you ninny. Steele&apos;s not going to give you his sources so Putin can jam them in a woodchipper. 
 Verification, in the sense of a NatSec or counterintel investigation, is a pretty high bar. IT&apos;S NOT A WORD THAT IS USED *ahem* 
 Instead, think: &quot;This guy Steele comes over with his work, we realized we&apos;re way behind, then the USIC and allies get to work.&quot; Steele was private. They have WAY MORE TOOLS. 
 So of course they don&apos;t bother &quot;verifying&quot; the &quot;unverified&quot; dossier. You verify with 80 other analysts and sources and allies and SIGINT and pictures from space and all the rest. 
 The IC gets its ass in gear, since apparently...something in the US counterintelligence apparatus...was a little slow. (This is a big deal) 
 In the meantime, you can release the Dossier to the public as a slightly-inaccurate teaser of what is to come. But don&apos;t get confused. 
 The Dossier ain&apos;t got nothing to do with all NATO/#FVEY allies working in concert. Nothing on Congress. NOTHING on Mueller. Strap in. &amp;lt;/THREAD&amp;gt;</texto><total_retweets type="int">2516</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">10393</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">222</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">16912124</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">179530</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1603</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">81854</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.2494373626610946</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>