<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">111</hilo><total_tweets type="int">12</total_tweets><texto type="str">Angela Merkel&apos;s Communist Background https://t.co/kJmXQR7xl3 
 2. Merkel&apos;s dad&apos;s pro-Communist attitude helped Angela go to college, when other children of clergy were routinely refused. The teenage Merkel, like virtually all of her contemporaries, joined the Freie Deutsche Jugend (FDJ) communist youth org. #QAnon #Q https://t.co/3tmDAb2fQD 
 3. Communists are communists: Coercion, confiscation, intimidation, and, eventually, genocide. No new ideas. &quot;Coincidence? #Q&quot; #QAnon https://t.co/IyG9fJog3V 
 4. Christ &quot;hailed&quot;? No, not Christ. Christ, rather, answers your knock: He gave it all for you, &quot;despised and rejected by men, a man of suffering, and familiar with pain. Like one from whom people hide their faces...we held him in low esteem. https://t.co/oI6ECdCe91 #QAnon #Q https://t.co/JfNBVwOKFz 
 5. #QAnon posts historical roots of Communist #Antifa flag. #Soros. &quot;Maxine Stupid&quot; -#Q https://t.co/60UNm4L7YS 
 6. &quot;We are all connected in this fight. PATRIOTS UNITE. We are winning BIG. Watch the speech. God bless.&quot; #Q #QAnon https://t.co/M9RK2bjYx5 
 7. #QAnon posts tonight: &quot;The WORLD is helping. &amp;lt;-------------- We are not alone... Watch the speech. &amp;lt;-------------- God bless.&quot; #Q President #Trump ended tonight&apos;s speech with: &quot;The whole WORLD..remember that..They&apos;re all watching..&quot; https://t.co/kMupFpnuCH 
 8. #QAnon tonight: &quot;You witnessed a strength test tonight. Speech promoted here/POTUS to gauge response. Net slowed. Protections in place. #Q&quot; #Trump: &quot;The whole WORLD..remember that..They&apos;re all watching..&quot; 
 9. #QAnon said tonight: &quot;We went too deep. Attempted a pullback. Not ready. #Q&quot; Either in response to NWO meaning &quot;Natürliche Wirtschaftsordnung&quot; = Natural Economic Order or regarding Merkel&apos;s family? Meanwhile, re 2nd, this&apos;s far as I got. Thoughts? https://t.co/a7oa1idnwP 
 10. Tonight #QAnon posted: &quot;This is not about religions or party affiliation. EVIL is everywhere. There are no drawn lines. No boundaries. Good vs Evil. #Q&quot; Tonight @POTUS said in Pittsburgh: https://t.co/M9RK2bjYx5 
 11. I saw #QAnon&apos;s post about Evil about an hour before the President&apos;s speech remark about the evil in Washington, although #Q had put it up while I was (oh my Goodness) doing other things earlier this afternoon. (see 10.) 
 12. @threadreaderapp please unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">37</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">57</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">16</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">5</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>