<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">186</hilo><total_tweets type="int">19</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. Todays Q posts are here threaded: #QAnon drop exhorts us all to stay together and FIGHT the censorship, reminding us that they are with us! - #Q https://t.co/b0as9E8s2z 
 2. South Africa‘s parliament has passed a motion to seize land from farmers without compensation based on their race https://t.co/BmtBHxc9d3 
 3. #QAnon asks when is there efficacy of a &quot;class action lawsuit&quot; in context of a &quot;censorship algorithm&quot; embedded the &quot;SAME across multiple platforms&quot;, reminding us, &quot;Why did Eric Schmidt leave Google?&quot; the day @POTUS signed executive order to confiscate corruption $$. https://t.co/oL9j8JkCu6 
 4. #QAnon asks us &quot;Where is @Snowden?&quot; -#Q 
 5. #QAnon points to modern (#MKUltra/#mockingbird) mind &quot;control&quot; done, at least in part, through #MSM &quot;creating emotional conflicts&quot; to &quot;destabilize certain minds to become &apos;suspectable&apos; to outside control&quot;, today&apos;s incident outside WH being a &quot;demonstration&quot;, &quot;a direct THREAT&quot;. https://t.co/0tuUSp28B4 
 6. #QAnon reminds us that &quot;WE ARE WINNING&quot; and to &quot;NOT TRUST WHAT YOU READ&quot; because it is &quot;MIND WARFARE&quot;. -#Q https://t.co/L2G0DqXzJE 
 7. One anon tonight suggests &quot;#Q&apos;s team killed the bridge HRC sold access to. Clowns no longer have access.&quot; #QAnon 
 8. #QAnon had most recently left a mysterious post about &quot;Stanislav Lunev. The BRIDGE.&quot; suggesting at the time that it was &quot;Payback for today.&quot; Tonight, #Q refers to Bridge again, preceding discussion about Google/YouTube, Facebook, Podesta&apos;s, #UraniumOne, North Korea, &amp;amp; more. https://t.co/3ViXptXAuI 
 9. #QAnon tells us that &quot;Misspellings matter&quot; in his posts. Note that #Q talks of #MSM &quot;creating emotional conflicts to destabilize certain minds to become &apos;suspectable&apos; to outside control&quot;. As in patsy? https://t.co/TV9fsaJjTA 
 10. #QAnon had b4 told us to &quot;TRUST SESSIONS&quot;. Now he points to Sessions key role, w corrupt #DeepState criminals in DOJ. MSM has 2stage narrative now w/o leaks. SAP = Special Access Programs JP = John Podesta TP = Tony Podesta U1 = Uranium One SR = Seth Rich YT = YouTube #Q https://t.co/jQgbdHMBuc 
 11. #QAnon: Did @Jack&apos;s crew write censorship algorithm used across platforms (Twitter, YouTube, FB, etc.) for Clowns? NK is out of the news cycle thanks to the FL school shooting. Las Vegas didn&apos;t work cuz things went wrong, &amp;amp; mostly Trump supporters killed. Kids killed in FL #Q https://t.co/c5TpmDt3QX 
 12. #QAnon: &quot;Watch the news this week&quot;. -#Q https://t.co/d7xxVo0x69 
 13. &quot;You are SHEEP to them. Pawns to be sacrificed.&quot; #QAnon points out that clown #MockingbirdMedia will mock the truth as crazy conspiraces, as more TRUTH comes out. But TRUTH is TRUTH! Never back down!! Boom. #Q https://t.co/DLe1LHxTAf 
 14. #QAnon: Sessions&apos;s role playing. #CrookedHillary betrayed us w open source unclassified server via John &amp;amp; Tony Podesta (&amp;amp; highest levels of BHO admin). U1, SAP, NK nuke tech, etc. Russia likely broadcasting its nuke capabilities as warning to #DeepState not to mess with them https://t.co/RzCoLZAX10 
 15. #QAnon tonight reminds us to &quot;Listen carefully: https://t.co/zcVlHIYbl6 … TRUST. WE are FIGHTING for YOU. GOD BLESS YOU ALL. #Q&quot; 
 16. #QAnon asks: &quot;DO YOU THINK ANTIFA WAS GROWN ORGANICALLY? Purpose? Watch the news this week. #Q&quot; https://t.co/PJuDIIMujX 
 17. #QAnon &quot;We are everywhere.&quot; BOOM. #Q https://t.co/FaEPXSznIU 
 18. Op orders: &quot;Bring the thunder&quot; https://t.co/aGfZMyrYXF 
 19. Puppies and kittens: Sp0nsors Att@cked in Fr55 Sp55ch Cr@ckdown ... https://t.co/XQfIIDeZGL #QAnon</texto><total_retweets type="int">57</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">78</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">22</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>