<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">227</hilo><total_tweets type="int">18</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ #QAnon #Fal$eFlag Consider: 1. #Trump says he wants out of #Syria. 2. #Assad has essentially won. Why create an event to draw a response? 3. Immediately after Trump tweets about leaving Syria, there is a #ChemicalAttack. 4. #Israel attacks Syria last night. Ask WHY?? 
 2/ Anyone who has been following things can see that the #DeepState wants #War. WHY? Military-industrial complex. Oil. and worse (depopulation). Too hard to believe? Look at the patterns (now and in the past)...do they fit? 
 3/ #Trump works out a deal w/#NK (back in November)...after our October bombing took out their major nuclear facility and 200 scientists. As background, the #DeepState was using #NK as a puppet regime to hold us hostage...they wanted #WAR. https://t.co/oFUvQv1JwG 
 4/ Knowing how the media will react, #Trump directs provocative tweets at #KimJongUn during this time frame. The #LSM take the bait and predictably call for Trump to tone it down and create peace. They essentially side w/#NK, known at the time to be an unstable, nuclear threat. 
 5/ Now that #Trump has effectively brokered a deal to denuclearize the Korean peninsula, the #LSM should be heaping praise upon #POTUS. After all, this is what they said they wanted. Wrong. It&apos;s hard to find positive media coverage of this. Google: https://t.co/awrNDFyKF6 
 6/ Isn&apos;t this win in #NK a win for the #US that must be celebrated? Not according to the #DeepState and the #MockingBird Media. The #LSM has two key talking points in their narrative: 1. Trump MUST fail...never shown to have success. 2. We MUST go to #WAR! 
 7/ With #NK off the table, the last hope of the #DeepState is a #WAR in the #MiddleEast. They focus on #Syria as the epicenter. The problem is that #Trump tweeted that we are pulling out. Something MUST be done...hence the #FF #ChemicalAttack we just saw over the weekend. 
 8/ Trump KNEW they would take the bait and do exactly what they did. He&apos;s exposing their evil, so he tweets the following right after this event, with this key phrasing in part 2 of the tweet: &quot;Open area immediately for medical help and verification.&quot; https://t.co/fHBJePgbbm 
 9/ With his tweet, #Trump has neutered the media. #Trump knows that they CANNOT provide verification that #Assad is behind the #ChemicalAttack. It was done by bad actors associated w/ the #DeepState that wants war. 
 10/ At the center of much of this and the US-created #ISIS is #NoName #Traitor #McCain. Those who moved off of the #LSM have known about McCain&apos;s connection to ISIS for some time. The #DeepState is now scrambling. 
 11/ Snopes (a leftist propoganda arm) had labeled a McCain-ISIS connection &quot;FALSE&quot; in the past. I had personally visited the page, &amp;amp; the picture they showed was different than the one they show now. They&apos;re so sloppy they have yet to clean the following reference to the picture. 
 12/ Snopes tried to clean its tracks in the archiving systems, so there were NO archives available for this page. I just created one (below): https://t.co/4VmnLuoruv 
 13/ Snopes is scrambling, so they have not cleaned the page fully. Clearly, the phrasing doesn&apos;t match the actual picture: &quot;A photograph taken in Syria in 2013 shows Senator John McCain posing with a commander of a Syrian opposition group, not ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi.&quot; 
 14/ Here are some of the incriminating pictures showing #McCain meeting w/ #ISIS leaders, such as leader al-Baghdadi. https://t.co/pjoKG9YNxF https://t.co/aoTZP9Syd0 
 15/ Back to the original question: WHY did #Israel bomb #Syria last night? I see two possible reasons that seem logical now: 1. To try to escalate things to pull us into a war w/ #Syria. 2. To destroy evidence of their (#Mossad) involvement in the #ChemicalAttack (speculative).. 
 16/ With this as background for those not following things closely...or getting their &quot;news&quot; from a lying media...now you can learn more from a deep-inside source that has been highly reliable yet mocked by the #LSM, namely #QAnon. https://t.co/eSrLGwR5GJ 
 17/ Now read this #QAnon post: Apr 8 2018 00:48:59 (EST) Q !xowAT4Z3VQ ID: d6f611 947065 They are trying to start a war. Deflection. Public interest shift. Pullout announcement. Chem attack. Coincidence? These people are sick. #Q Happy Hunting! /END https://t.co/4uSa1LGm4N 
 @threadreaderapp unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">51</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">79</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">20</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">24</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">749684424</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">3785</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3969</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">6802</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7780699304231409</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>