<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">202</hilo><total_tweets type="int">18</total_tweets><texto type="str">3 of 3 long threads to cover (see my tweets/replies for 1st/2nd ones) https://t.co/20zN0xBxte … … @TrumpArmyDawn @christianllamar @USNJack @dbongino @KevinJacksonTBS @charliekirk11 @chuckwoolery @Imperator_Rex3 @workbench59 @DJLugoff @mitchellvii @Harris9Milt @PrisonPlanet https://t.co/k2v5Dx5gMl 
 41) 1,244 of the emails reference NUCLEAR ENERGY. The full collection includes emails to/from Hillary Clinton. April &apos;15 NYT published story about a company called “#UraniumOne” which was sold to Russian government-controlled interests, giving Russia effective control https://t.co/JAxWN2yEAv 
 42) of one-fifth of ALL uranium production capacity in the United States. Since uranium is considered a strategic asset, w/implications for production of nuclear weapons, the deal had to be approved by a committee composed of representatives from a number of US govt agencies. 
 43) Among the agencies that eventually signed off the deal was State Department, then headed by Secretary Clinton. The Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States (#CFIUS) comprises, among others, secretaries of Treasury, Defense, Homeland Security, Commerce &amp;amp; Energy. 
 44) As Russian interests GRADUALLY TOOK CONTROL of #UraniumOne millions of dollars were donated to the Clinton Foundation between 2009 &amp;amp; 2013 from individuals directly connected to the deal INCLUDING the CHAIRMAN of #UraniumOne, #IanTelfer. Although Mrs Clinton had an agreement 
 45) w/the Obama White House to publicly identify all donors to the Clinton Foundation, the contributions from the Chairman of Uranium One were NOT PUBLICLY DISCLOSED by the Clintons. [The foundation admission] When the NYT article was published the https://t.co/Cc5B5TCeQn 
 46) Clinton campaign spokesman, Brian Fallon, strongly rejected the possibility that then-Secretary Clinton exerted any influence in the US govt’s review of the SALE of #UraniumOne, describing this possibility as “baseless”. 
 47) Mr Fallon promptly sent a memo to the NYT w/rebuttal of the story (Podesta Email ID 1489). In this memo, Mr Fallon argued: “Apart from the fact that the State Department was 1 of just 9 agencies involved in #CFIUS, it is also true that w/n State Dep, the #CFIUS approval 
 48) process historically does not trigger the personal involvement of the Sec of State. The State Dept’s principal REPRESENTATIVE to #CFIUS was Assistant Secretary of State for Economic, Energy &amp;amp; Business Affairs. During the time period in question, that position was held by 
 49) Jose Fernandez. As you are aware, Mr Fernandez has personally attested that “Secretary Clinton never intervened with me on any #CFIUS matter.” 
 50) What Clinton campaign spokesman FAILED to DISCLOSE, however, was the FACT that a few days before sending his rebuttal to the NYTimes, Jose Fernandez WROTE ON THE EVENING OF the 17 April 2015 TO #JohnPodesta following a phone call from Mr Podesta (Email ID 2053): 
 51) “John, It was good to talk to you this afternoon, and I appreciate your taking the time to call. As I mentioned, I would like to do all I can to support Secretary Clinton, and would welcome your advice and help in steering me to the right persons in the campaign”. 
 52) 5 days after this email (22 April 2015), Clinton spokesman Brian Fallon wrote a memo to the NYT, declaring that “#JoseFernandez has personally attested that ‘Sec Clinton never intervened with me on any #CFIUS matter’,” but Fallon failed to mention that Fernandez was hardly 
 53) a neutral witness in this case, considering that he had agreed with John Podesta to PALY A ROLE in the Clinton campaign. Emails show that the contacts between John Podesta and Jose Fernandez go back to the time of internal Clinton campaign concern about the then- 
 54) forthcoming book and movie “Clinton Cash” by Peter Schweizer on the financial dealings of the Clinton Foundation. In an email dated 29 March 2015 (Email ID 2059), Jose Fernandez writes to Podesta: https://t.co/4ePGZQvv75 
 55) “Hi John, I trust you are getting a brief rest after a job well done. Thanks no doubt to your recommendation I have joined the CAP [Center for American Progress] board of trustees, which I’m finding extremely rewarding.” 
 The Timelines, public documents clearly show the #ObamaAdministration was in on the #deal to sell 20% (including the land) of #America&apos;s #NationalSecurity to #RosAtom/Russia. This is the epitome of #TREASON! #Iran #Hezbollah are a proxy of Russia. #TickTock🔥💣 https://t.co/ROb9vgqtVl 
 @threadreaderapp &quot;unroll&quot;</texto><total_retweets type="int">63</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">63</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">21</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">14</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">15117196</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">12069</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">11535</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">51017</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8063340028170753</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>