<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">28</hilo><total_tweets type="int">9</total_tweets><texto type="str">Thread. Few things about the Ryan Seacrest situation. First, here @Variety reporter @gdanielholloway&apos;s first story on the years of alleged abuse RS subjected a woman to. She told her story using her name. Her job ended after she reported him to HR in 2013 https://t.co/KSdYqV5cBF 
 Second: This is for people saying &quot;But it was investigated and nothing was found.&quot; Incorrect. Two important facts: 1. His employer hired another firm to do the investigation. Not a truly independent third party. Investigator&apos;s payment came from E!, where Seacrest is a big deal. 
 As for firm that did the Seacrest investigation: Their finding was “insufficient evidence” of wrongdoing. Whatever that means. As for corroboration, @gdanielholloway talked to many other sources &amp;amp; another employee told NBC he witnessed alleged abuse https://t.co/XWMNkGqwzs 
 As @soniasaraiya wrote in a must-read opinion column, E! put together an &quot;investigation that has no mandate or incentive to be impartial.&quot; Yes, I agree, due process matters. But so far all the survivor got was E&apos;s HR inquiry &amp;amp; an inquiry by a firm *they* hired. 
 Ryan Seacrest has many platforms from which to defend himself &amp;amp; give his side (incl to Variety). He has said he was asked for money. As @gdanielholloway story notes, &quot;Seacrest’s reps provided no evidence to Variety that such a monetary request was made.&quot; https://t.co/XWMNkGqwzs 
 Speaking generally, not about any individual, as as for the defense that &quot;I just don&apos;t believe this person could do that because of X or Y,&quot; know that anyone is capable of abuse and harassment. It&apos;s about power, full stop. 
 Will link to @soniasaraiya&apos;s column again: &quot;He’s deliberately and repeatedly attacking the character of his accuser.&quot; This is why many were demoralized that E! put Seacrest on the red carpet. My respect for anyone who talked to him today has declined https://t.co/1ZSMUivk6i 
 Finally, for those saying, &quot;How dare this mob angrily demanding he lose 1 or 2 of his 87 jobs!&quot; Huhwut? Not Topic A, that I&apos;ve seen. A debate worth having, sure. Regardless, it&apos;s *extremely* questionable he is a core public face of @enews today. Disrespectful to #MeToo imho. Fin. 
 If you&apos;re in my mentions trying to start an argument with me, I&apos;m not looking at them tonight. Whatever I wanted to say was in this thread. Enjoy your evening. https://t.co/LxKzstce4m</texto><total_retweets type="int">775</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1996</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">75</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">10111462</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">65506</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">597</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">110243</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.275263113502756</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>