<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">207</hilo><total_tweets type="int">17</total_tweets><texto type="str">Read and share the highlights of Pruitt&apos;s long list of wrongdoings. (Thread) #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt paid below-market rent for a condo co-owned by the wife of an energy lobbyist. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt made a costly trip to Morocco to promote his lobbyist landlord’s client’s work. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt spent $58,000 on charter and military flights. #BootPruitt 
 ◦EPA spent $45,000 to fly aides to Australia in advance of a Pruitt trip that was later canceled. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt spent $90,000 taxpayer dollars on first-class flights and other travel in one week. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt broke government rules to fly luxury business class on a foreign airline. #BootPruitt 
 ◦EPA staff looked into the possibility of leasing a private jet for $100,00 a month for Pruitt’s travel. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt&apos;s 24/7 security team (which is larger than any previous EPA administrator’s) drew staff away from criminal investigations. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Taxpayers paid for Pruitt’s 24/7 security detail during his personal trips to Disneyland and the Rose Bowl. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt spent about $43,000 on a private soundproof booth, violating federal spending law. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt lied to senators about his use of a private email account. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt gave a Superfund job to a failed banker whose bank had given loans to Pruitt. #BootPruitt 
 ◦The White House told Pruitt he could not give two of his closest aides a pay raise, but he used a loophole to do it anyway. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt reassigned and demoted EPA officials who questioned his spending. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt asked to use vehicle siren to make dinner reservations, reassigned staffer who objected. #BootPruitt 
 ◦Pruitt upgraded to larger vehicle with bulletproof seat covers. #BootPruitt</texto><total_retweets type="int">2038</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">4818</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">209</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">26642006</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">3577160</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">4036</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">56970</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.4228082713988874</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>