<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">195</hilo><total_tweets type="int">17</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) Today&apos;s story is called The Brink. They never thought she&apos;d lose, now we understand the #NWO plan to destroy America, see 1991 Bush I vid. Obama took over the process from Bush II and embarked on an 8 year wrecking ball. #QAnon #GreatAwakening @POTUS https://t.co/iSkLLD5doz 
 2) For years rogue operatives have been getting installed. Shadow government/#DeepState. All centers of #Government. Controlled by the wealthiest on the planet, most rogue was the CIA. Goal was complete control to dismantle. Check Out Barry&apos;s Book: Post American World #QAnon https://t.co/sXrG0HRgob 
 3) The systematic leaking of classified intel was everywhere, so was exposure of #military assets. Instead if de-funding military (bad optics), you starve thru corruption. Notice #Mattis has a massive audit of DOD? Think why. https://t.co/7JzwtiOevr https://t.co/ZYlC9ZMpGP 
 4) Once population properly pacified, you can start to de-fund #Military. In between you subtly destroy structure &amp;amp; morale so the best leave. Slow and subtle weakening. @POTUS well aware, and then starts the removal of the good guys. (Look at DOJ / FBI) https://t.co/lo0XFYF46x 
 5) #DOD Special Access Program gets sold out so safeguards on highly classified information can be disseminated and leaked. Q says #Snowden leaks were devestating re #Prism and Keyscore. 
 6) Shift domestically. Destroy the anti-#Globalists conservative base. #IRS targets conservative groups. #MSM (#OperationMockingbird) overt #bias. Meth, #OpiodCrisis, &quot;fly over&quot; states, gutting manufacturing base, destroy #Heartland. Pacify. Control #SiliconValley message. 
 7) #OpenBorders flood in #IllegalAliens for #Democrat votes. #Hezbollah, #ISIS, #MS13 funded and installed for fear, targeted removals, false flag. ALL INTENTIONAL. EVERY citizen must read: https://t.co/QXPccc1Nw5 
 8) Blind-eye to #NorthKorea. Intentional. Allowing them to build #nuclear capabilities. Blind-eye to #Iran who were funded with cash and supplied with #uranium via #UraniumOne (some ended up in NK). #Traitor #QAnon @POTUS 
 9) Q bombshell incoming... Stage SC [AS [187]] Stage the murder of AS (Antonin Scalia)??? Wow. See attached. Install team players into #SCOTUS for legal wins. Scalia: no autopsy. No security. Out of the 1800s. #QAnon @POTUS #GreatAwakening #truecrime https://t.co/7rlaTzbW1a 
 10) Destroy #NASA. A nation without (or intentionally private) space capabilities is weakened in the modern world, dominated. Bad actors can take down #Military satellites, destroy #GPS, communications systems, survellence equipment. #SpaceX #QAnon @POTUS https://t.co/nMRs9ExIh3 
 11) Q suggests #HillaryClinton&apos;s 8 year marching orders was to start a war. Lose a war? HRC [8] WWIII [death &amp;amp; weapons real/WAR FAKE &amp;amp; CONTROLLED][population growth control/pocket billions] In the process all remaining good actors in gov would be eliminated. @POTUS #QAnon 
 12) After all this weakening, the final step was to kill of the most powerful economy in the world. We&apos;d be ready for the #NewWorldOrder. Mass poverty and government dependence. #UnitedNations #Elite https://t.co/WKKfXMRlUf 
 13) Here then comes #OpenBorders and a revision to the constitution. Ban the sale of #firearms. Then you can remove the #ElectoralCollege and use the popular vote (no #VoterID so rampant #VoterFraud with #IllegalAliens) to win elections. #QAnon @POTUS 
 14) We circle back to the #Military - with things this deeply locked up, you can de-fund the military and with that comes closing bases around the world. 
 15) From here you complete the cleanup of the #MSM and all opposing viewpoints. War on whites with garbage like #whiteprivilege #Antifa #SJW #BLM #Mansplaining #LGBTPOWER #WhiteGenocide 
 16) Q stops here. But my viewpoint is that the incredibly corrupt #UnitedNations would take over security worldwide, becoming the apex of the cronyism of the military industrial complex. Governments around the world would intentionally be weakened. 
 17) This is where the corporate slave-masters would take over. Our subservience would be complete with an uneducated population pacified with drugs, devices, and yet another superhero movie. Please see source Q post attached. #QAnon @POTUS #TheAwakening #psychopath #NWO https://t.co/QezPf6JB5a</texto><total_retweets type="int">55</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">69</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">24</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">53</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1623794972</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">11222</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">39</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">10786</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.5565009939878032</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>