<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">72</hilo><total_tweets type="int">8</total_tweets><texto type="str">This is such a shocking story in its details. We shrug off #DataPrivacy because we think it&apos;s basically inconsequential to our real lives. But the impact of #CambridgeAnalytica just began to be felt in 2015 and spread to 50 MILLION or 1 in 6 Americans. 1/ https://t.co/GPUtcPExEF 
 The panoply of ways Trump used his cachet w/ billionaire supporters like the Mercers should concern everyone, including those on the right &amp;amp; left who just eyeroll these investigations as about #HillaryClinton when that&apos;s tangential to our national security &amp;amp; honest elections. 2/ https://t.co/OJ73CmluIB 
 Every American should want to know what happened in 2016 because every American who&apos;s a critical thinker knows the person who wins the most votes won the election. Moreover, everyone knows Democratic systems ensure an unskewed result, unlike #Russia&apos;s imminent election. 3/ https://t.co/ge5029OrZ9 
 FB denying a data breach happened parallels Americans being told #HillaryClinton didn&apos;t reach working class voters when she won voters making &amp;lt;$50k overwhelmingly and also won women &amp;amp; POC--80% of America&apos;s working class. These lies go beyond 2016 to impact 2018 &amp;amp; 2020. 4/ 
 What will happen to #CambridgeAnalyticaFiles? Where will that accumulated data from the &quot;non-data breach&quot; go? How much of it has already been sold to some other entity? Details are staggering. Two decisive votes were involved: #Brexit &amp;amp; US POTUS election 2016. Both upsets. 5/ https://t.co/OwqYlgz7ke 
 Pundits can assert myriad reasons for both #Brexit &amp;amp; Trump winning upsets. But ignoring the information revealed Friday on #CambridgeAnalytica would be nonsensical. The culpability of the Trump administration is revealed daily. But will anyone ever be held responsible? 6/ https://t.co/KY3kKoTaR4 
 Assiduous work, some genius and the Mercers billions fueled #CambridgeAnalytica. That they got the desired result was by no means an accident. 7_ https://t.co/5xGAVN9BWh 
 Where do we go now? With the #AndrewMcCabe &amp;amp; #StormyDaniels scandals, as well as the latest call by Trump&apos;s attorneys to end the #MuellerInvestigation, will this even survive the weekend news cycle or will it--with help from #Facebook--be buried? Troubling questions all. 8/ https://t.co/ELkRizxpaS</texto><total_retweets type="int">496</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">757</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">39</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">10</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">138168339</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">82272</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3080</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">342563</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0950311725658972</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>