<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">156</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">Finished reading through superseding Mueller Indictment on Manafort and Gates. Here’s my take: #theRESISTance #TrumpRussia https://t.co/Jz5OFPPNPX 
 This one paragraph is a culmination of #TrumpRussia starting with Manafort’s allegiance to Russia #ElectionHacking for Yanukovych; the irony that Ukraine had an “Orange Revolution” and Manafort renting property in Trump Tower for years. Roger Stone where you at? https://t.co/cLtdWBw1VC 
 More on Manafort’s experience in #ElectionHacking and capabilities that together paint a picture Tony Soprano couldn’t paint: https://t.co/Zqq33w0pxU 
 Has to be pointed out that Yanukovych, Snowden, and Assange might as well be sitting in a gilded rat cave in Russia right now, but that’s besides the point. 2005-7 is a key timeframe to understanding how #TrumpRussia came about in the first place... https://t.co/XYMQ8gR1G8 
 Facts are stubborn things. https://t.co/dm4vMYsBFq 
 Is it possible that Manafort used the same “Home Improvement” company that Russian Embassies throughout tri-state used? Using that involved Russian “immigrants” who were “cool” with taking money from Cyprus? Rinat where you at? #OperationHotSoup https://t.co/av9tcbuRrh 
 More on “home improvement” https://t.co/gwCcOqTwKP 
 Let’s not talk about Manafort’s Bannon-esque company name Leviathan, or subliminals like Global Highway, or the fact that Black Sea was set-up to be a propaganda channel - imagine, Manafort with his own Hannity shows. Global Endeavour for 500,000? Sept, 3 2013. https://t.co/bkcYEBNzZk 
 More on Manafort Hannity shows (#KGB style): https://t.co/x9YDIAEzxg 
 “Global Endeavour in September 13’” ask yourself what is Trump doing? Miss Universe, inviting Putin, praising him, “Putin gave me a gift” meanwhile @PreetBharara files Prevezon case against Veselnitskaya from #TrumpTowerMeeting - small world am i right? https://t.co/mvPfJUsgye 
 Quick question, can somebody frame this? https://t.co/0js8SpltQo 
 The irony is that Trump‘s lawlessness and ability to surround himself with the worst kind of political operatives have given law enforcement the opportunity to #DrainTheSwamp within the #DarkMoney GOP - Manafort with Roger Stone, Ailes, and Lee Atwater helped NIXON... #TBT 
 Mueller drops this indictment same day as #CPAC2018 - Trump admitted at CPAC that he got a gift from Putin, safe to say it wasn’t Slutvana peeing on a bed? Or a loyalty pledge for 2016 perhaps? I think Mueller should ask. https://t.co/FozmVtNkHk 
 Trust me my fellow Americans, I would rather not have to tweet at 1:30AM about indictments that are a tuna sandwich away from our current @POTUS but you have to admit, what Trump and his gangsters have done is treasonous and anyone taking this seriously knows the ramifications.</texto><total_retweets type="int">66</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">145</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">28</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">10</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">19895040</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">5636</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">6079</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">97536</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7840977504380292</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>