<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">3</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) Folks sunlight is truly the greatest disinfectant of them all! I admit that I was one of the skeptic’s that was really worried about our AG. I owe AG Jeff Sessions&apos; a big apology. The last 45 seconds of the interview reminded me of the man that was stumping all across the https://t.co/q3X6F1gS4p 
 2) country with our President. He absolutely lit up as he spoke about candidate and now President Donald J. Trump. To me those 45 seconds reassured that every single person involved in this coup will be arrested and prosecuted to the full extent of the law! 
 3) I have had visions for over a year of waking up and turning my tv on and seeing arrests being made simultaneously all over the USA. Every one of these POS being brought out of their homes in handcuffs. Some trying to use their overcoat to disguise their faces from the cameras. 
 4) After reading the post below, I feel that my dream may actually become a reality! There were plenty of guilty men and women that watched that last night and couldn’t fall asleep. They took sleeping pill after sleeping pill and it just didn’t work. Their minds were racing 
 7) like a Formula 1 race car. Every single image imaginable of what will be their life going forward was playing itself out. They also found themselves wanting to vomit out whatever they ate earlier. Their bodies began to go into overdrive to eat them from the inside out. 
 8) That gun on their nightstand began to get louder and louder. Some may have actually picked it up only to put it down again. They were able to once again convince themselves that they were HEROES and that BHO would once again protect them. 
 9) Lets see how that plays out going forward! At some point the realization will hit them like a boulder. BHO isn’t going to save the day because he is in the same sinking ship as the rest of them! The Anticipation Of DEATH Is Far Worse Than DEATH Itself!</texto><total_retweets type="int">9</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">16</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">7</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">857087659008815105</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">2902</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">280</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">20144</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0041002957674237</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>