<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">234</hilo><total_tweets type="int">19</total_tweets><texto type="str">Ok, y’all. Would you like some #metoo Torah? Thread. The Torah portion we read this coming Shabbat starts with the story of Yitro, Moses’ father-in-law, giving him some tips about refining his leadership model, delegating, becoming more effective in his leadership. 
 Then, fast-forward. The people Israel are hanging out at the base of Mt. Sinai, while God gives instructions to Moses. This translation is misleading; there’s no “warning” and no “staying pure.” God tells Moses to קדש the people—to make them holy, sanctified, set-apart. https://t.co/H4nML4ktdc 
 It’s clear from the verb that Moses needs to do a thing to them. So then Moses goes back, and he does it! He קדש them. Sanctifies, makes holy, sets apart, something. It’s still not clear what the action is, but he does it. Plus the clothes washing thing. There’s no warning. https://t.co/2RdIuyrhiX 
 And then *record scratch* he keeps talking. “Don’t go near a woman.” God didn’t say that. Suddenly, Moses is only addressing men. Women have gone from being subjects—part of the people—to objects. Who are sexual temptations who must be avoided. https://t.co/Va4uCaIjWi 
 In one sentence, Moses simultaneously cuts women out of Revelation and turns them into sexual objects. Women aren’t the ones being told to prepare for Torah, here, after all. They’re just a problem. 
 Traditional commentators make sense of all this by suggesting that קדש is a command for Israel to attain a state of ritual elevation/purity, akin to where they must be to offer sacrifices in the Temple. Since seminal ejaculation would imperil that status, that’s what God meant. 
 Only problem is that קדש is not that state. We have a word for that. טהר. Moses dumped his human stuff into his command from God. His ideas about gender and power and hierarchy and who matters and sex and whatever else. He twisted a command from the Holy One to suit his agenda. 
 And the commentators who could have pounced on the discrepancy (they’re very good at that) instead did the same thing. They saw something fishy but it suited their ideas about gender and power so they explained it away. Excused it. Rationalized it and ignored its impact on women. 
 As it happens, we see קדש come up, most notably in the Holiness Code, the metaphoric and literal heart of the Torah (chiastic structure, yo). Explicitly not about ritual purity. Rather: https://t.co/TP4vuPPxdi 
 And what is the Holiness Code about? Mostly social justice and preventing sexual abuse. 
 You can’t make this stuff up. 
 This makes it clearer even still that when God asked Moses to קדש the community, to make-holy them, it was about the whole community, in its fullness, safety, created-in-the-Divine-image-ness. For I your God am holy. 
 And Moses—fresh from his new! Improved! More egalitarian! Leadership!—does great violence to that. And traditional commentators, like so many people today, ignore, minimize, explain away this violence in service to the leadership, the structures. The organization’s reputation. 
 We need to do work that is no less to go back to the base of Sinai and re-receive Torah anew. This time with God’s intended meaning—in a way that sanctifies every single one of us. All of us together. We shall be holy, for God is holy. 
 (You guys got the part where the bad translation of קדש in the @SefariaProject translation is totally informed by this traditional commentators’ misreading of the situation, right? Good. Just checking). (Really, it’s one of the worst translations I’ve seen, and I’ve seen bad.) 
 Also people correctly noted that I was alluding to Judith Plaskow’s Jewish feminist theological masterwork, Standing Again At Sinai. It’s not an accident, that title. Go read the book if you haven’t. 
 And hey, here’s Merle Feld’s classic poem, “We All Stood Together.” This too. https://t.co/ETrAO7Gubx 
 Hey, for everyone asking for the mom-friendly version of this (until I turn it into an essay), here: https://t.co/6pCvXKtpzq 
 OK, @LilithMagazine turned it into an essay, for those who want it like this: https://t.co/Ack4POmjeV</texto><total_retweets type="int">327</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2009</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">76</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">61802282</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">67162</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">767</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">94137</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.2423890118220557</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>