<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">269</hilo><total_tweets type="int">24</total_tweets><texto type="str">Someone labeled #QAnon a #conspiracytheory It&apos;s not. I can objectively show more than once what @realDonaldTrump was about to tweet before he did it and also show coordination between Q and the DOD, and Q and @JulianAssange. Huge events are happening, it&apos;s time to awaken. 
 2) in addition, while it&apos;s still being uncovered, there are deeply coded messages within @realDonaldTrump tweets. The specific intentions behind all of this are many, but one vital one is to specifically prevent #conspiracytheories from being concocted. 
 3) Another reason disclosure is self evident, it&apos;s a public disclosure. It so happens that the disclosures are happening in a location where the user base is sufficiently #redpilled to accept the #truths -they are a bit tough to take for #normies 
 4) #truth is for the people. Some will always be unwilling to accept a real #thematrix exists right under your nose. But it&apos;s there. It&apos;s a giant #Web of #organizedcrime in which our national wealth is being siphoned off using #politicians to direct the flow into pockets. 
 5) #politicians are #pawns in all of this. They are #honeypotted or entrapped in a financial scheme so as to exert leverage, totally #blackmailed - you won&apos;t believe it but mainly by the #CIA but lots of powers engage in it. 
 6) To control our culture you only need to control 2 things: the #MSM and #Hollywood #ProjectMockingbird alive and well. #HughHefner was a #CIA asset, instrumental in CIA&apos;s control of #Hollywood 
 7) LA is #cesspool of #depravity and it&apos;s by design. What better way to control an industry than to fill it with #pedophiles you can #blackmail to high heaven? 
 8) The #MSM is garbage by design. It&apos;s what the sheep get fed so they remain pacified. An informed public is of no interest to the powers of corruption. Twitter was a refuge, but unfortunately it&apos;s run by a leftist monster named @Jack Dorsey who is killing its utility. 
 9) Think pedophiles are reserved for #Hollywood? Imagine they are useful at all levels of power? And from that, consider the possibility that kids are supplied? #Pedogate 
 10) why is our nations wealth being siphoned off in this matter? The #NWO The #NewWorldOrder is non-State actors taking control over the world. They are now powerful enough. On their own, the #Rothschild family Controls most of the central banks in the world. 
 11) consider that. One family controls the majority of the money supply on the planet. When you have unlimited resources at the scale, you can easily Topol Third World regime&apos;s, and eventually go for the big fish, us. 
 12) @realDonaldTrump signed an astonishing executive order about #humantrafficking, go read it. 
 13) @BarackObama has been exposed via the politico article as a facilitator of #drugtrafficking and #HumanTrafficking by allowing #Hezbollah and #MS13 run rampant in our society through policies such as open borders and a bad deal with #Iran 
 14) for some, the deal wasn&apos;t that bad, and if you shift your perspective on @BarackObama you open yourself up for the possibility he really wasn&apos;t on our side. He&apos;s part of the #saulalinsky #NWO crowd. and he knows he&apos;s in deep trouble. 
 15) #militaryintelligence asked @realDonaldTrump to run as president because he was clean. They prevented massive #election fraud and allowed a real election to happen. 
 16) @realDonaldTrump constantly aligned himself with the #military during the campaign, and also was adamant about a #borderwall and dealing with #MS13. Considering Obamas exposure, it makes sense why he was adamant, and also makes sense why he was aligned with the military. 
 17) is it possible that one of our intelligence agencies has become so rogue that they view themselves as a power into their own? Have you done any reading into the history of the #CIA? Don&apos;t they just seem to be in complete control of everything? Watch Kevin Shipp YouTube vid. 
 18) is it possible that the most powerful families on the planet wanted to nuclearized North Korea as a means to consolidate their own grasp on Geo political affairs? 
 19) Is it possible that #charities and foundations are one of the fundamental mechanisms that enables #corruption? 
 20) is it possible that in addition to money, children are currency the world over to exert control over power structures? Private planes. is it possible our culture is being sexualized in bizarre ways? #elsagate is too vast in scope to be anything other than an operation. 
 21) is the rampant drug addiction and device addiction in our society intentional? That our education system continues to deteriorate? The life expectancy of white males is decreasing? are we being pacified? 
 22) is the rampant spying on our citizens being done to protect us? Is the conversation about #UBI a deal with the devil? if you were #elite, wouldn&apos;t a mindless and surveilled population who does just enough to keep the wheels turning exactly what you want? While you #party 
 23) isn&apos;t all this technology great? We&apos;re developing #AI Breathtaking advances in #Robotics Soon, most of what&apos;s necessary for survival will be automated. Ask yourself if it&apos;s possible that some benevolent elites believe depopulation is necessary to survive as a species. 
 24) is it possible that the world is run by a bunch of psychopaths? #QAnon #logic #owls #ClintonCrimeFamily #Hezbollah #Rothschild #CORRUPTION #TheGreatAwakening #Soros #Wikileaks #thematrix #RedPill #ChildTrafficking #NWO #OpenBorders #Antifa #OpioidCrisis #Trump #Military</texto><total_retweets type="int">330</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">779</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">44</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">60</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1623794972</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">11222</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">39</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">10786</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.5565009939878032</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>