<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">137</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">How #CambridgeAnalytica CEO explains, unknowingly to a hidden camera, how they put Donald Trump in the White House. 17:21 revealing one more layer to an illegitimate election. We The American People demand Hillary Clinton takes her rightful place. #Real45 https://t.co/SvagnOetF6 
 3:55 &quot;From the start, the company was keen to claim credit for securing the votes that decided the election in Donald Trump&apos;s favor&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 5:22 &quot;In June 2016, the Trump campaign was flailing; it&apos;s coffers were empty, and the team was in chaos. The Mercers decided to step in and offered a huge cash injection. But they instead that he hires Steve Bannon, and their company, Cambridge Analytica.&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 7:43 &quot;The concept of &quot;Crooked Hillary&quot; was promoted widely on social media including Facebook, Google, and YouTube. CA boasts the online videos were watched 30,000,000 times over. But users would&apos;ve been unaware they came from the Trump Campaign&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 8:16 &quot;The problem is coordination between a Candidate&apos;s campaign and these groups is *Illegal* under US election law...&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 8:40 &quot;This video seems to provide further evidence for this notion that Cambridge Analytica did indeed act as a conduit to sharing information between the Super Pac and the Trump Campaign, and that is *illegal*&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 9:06 &quot;Sometimes you can use proxy orgs who are already there, you feed them, they are civil society orgs... Like charities or activist groups, and we use them, feed them the material, and they do the work.&quot; (BERNIE GROUPS BETTER NOT HAVE SPREAD CA VIDEOS) #HRCLegitimate45 
 Yup. 10:12 &quot;CA&apos;s &quot;Crooked Hillary&quot; onslaught ... it was about turning *off* potential Clinton voters. Directly targeting [voice-over Crooked Hillary clip: Bernie Never Had A Chance] Bernie Sanders supporters to discourage them from voting for her.&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 12:01 &quot;Now, legislators on Cap. Hill want Facebook back to answer more questions over the data-grab of over 50M profiles to Cambridge Analytica. ‼️*Could that data have been accessed by and exploited by 3rd partyies, they ask, including entities in Russia ‼️&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 12:28 Hillary Clinton speaking to camera: &quot;You&apos;ve got CA, you&apos;ve got the RNC -which of course had done data collection &amp;amp; analysis- &amp;amp; you&apos;ve got the Russians. ‼️And the real question is, How did the Russians know how to target their messages so precisely‼️&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 
 HRC speaking to camera ends at 13:08. 14:12 &quot;But during our last undercover meeting with the company, we received an assurance. ‼️CEO Alexander Nix telling us that CA will *not* give US investigators any information about its foreign clients.‼️ #HRCLegitimate45 
 14:52 Alexander Nix to undercover journo on his appearance in front of the House Intel: &quot;I went to speak to them, and the Republicans asked 3 questions, 5 minutes, done! The Democrats asked 2 hours of questions&quot;. #HRCLegitimate45 
 15:42 &quot;... CA appears to have a plan in place to avoid scrutiny. Nix says they use a secure secret email system which destroys emails 2 hours after they&apos;re sent.&quot; (ProtonMail with emails set to self-destruct timer) #HRCLegitimate45 
 16:45 &quot;... the company&apos;s admission about polluting the bloodstream of the internet with poisonous anonymous material raises serious questions not only about the last election, but will the future ones be fought in the same way.&quot; #HRCLegitimate45 END/share https://t.co/k7Lz7Q7Ar7</texto><total_retweets type="int">837</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1904</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">64</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">839188838593540097</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">12671</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2762</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">55086</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9237769222133587</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>