<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">92</hilo><total_tweets type="int">13</total_tweets><texto type="str">How powerful could #ASI become? Note that when an AI gets better than a human at something it gets much, much, much better. (Also note the terrifying scenario of an AGI/ASI running 1:1 for office.) @MIRIBerkeley #sketchnotes https://t.co/SYSwZ9U9e6 
 A favorite concept from the book is that “we already have something that does everything that humans can do, which is humans.” But the charming _bon mot_ is a disservice to the potential at-scale effects of ANI. 
 Eventually ANI may be able to do everything that humans can do, but do it faster, tirelessly, and cheaper than humans. We are going to have to get psych, civics, and law ahead of the potential displacement of humans. Some good news is that ANI will always need human partners. 
 In Chapter 3 of #SmarterThanUs, Armstrong makes the case that a capabilities-measurement of #ASI is more useful than a philosophical one. (Out of order because I reposted with corrected attribution for Marcus Hutter of @anucecs. Hat tip to @robbensinger.) https://t.co/NWY6U9BmbI 
 Chapter 5 speaks of the trappings of communicating human goals to a digital intelligence. #sketchnotes #SmarterThanUs https://t.co/d7PLzMea58 
 In Chapter 6 of #SmarterThanUs, Armstrong reminds us that the implicit “reasonableness” of our values are complex, and they are fragile. And as AGI gets smarter, things get worse. #sketchnotes #AI https://t.co/cRosRtgjjv 
 Filing under “things I’m glad I have gotten to sketchnote.” https://t.co/0bfw8juULM 
 With the command, “Get my mom out of that building!” this chapter illustrates the problem of literal interpreters, i.e. the amount of specification needed to ensure reasonable results is unreasonable. (This builds on @ESYudkowsky’s https://t.co/MNGSCJZCNx) #sketchnotes #ASI #AI https://t.co/j6ce3LBIic 
 Chapter 8 asks if we have to get everything about #ASI exactly right. Short answer: Yes. Because it will be so much more aware and powerful than us, we need it to be that much more moral than us. #sketchnotes #SmarterThanUs https://t.co/O5309En6yO 
 Chapter 9 of “Smarter Than Us” reminds the readers that philosophers and computer scientists have been struggling with these issues for a LONG time. #sketchnotes #sandwich #philosophy https://t.co/KPkRgvlUs4 
 Chapter 10 is pointers to many folks doing the hard work, getting us to a safe seed #AI. @CSERCambridge @MIRI @FHIOxford (Others off twitter…) (But it’s not the last chapter.) #sketchnotes https://t.co/my8AAtNbdb 
 Reposting Chapter 10 because I’d gotten the wrong Hanson! Here’s the right one. Many folks doing the hard work, getting us to a safe seed #AI. @CSERCambridge @MIRIBerkeley @FHIOxford (Others off twitter) #sketchnotes https://t.co/9ws1LwWGrY 
 The last Chapter of “Smarter Than Us” is a call to action. What can you do? Support research! Rain funds! Raise awareness! https://t.co/Io8xLuNMSv</texto><total_retweets type="int">37</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">103</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">17</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">182980233</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">4136</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">661</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">7760</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9465637118394634</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>