<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">18</hilo><total_tweets type="int">9</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) We Patriots must expand our thinking. If you haven&apos;t watched Red October, you should. It depicts exactly what&apos;s going on right now. @POTUS is Captain Ramius &amp;amp; is delivering #DeepState to Justice because they tried to destroy the US Constitution. 
 2) In the Movie, the USSR designed a Submarine that could run so silent that it couldn&apos;t be detected. The Sub was designed to park off the shore of America to deliver a group of Nuclear Missiles within 2 minutes of launch. How does that Mirror #DeepState? 
 3) #DeepState is designed to put the proper people in place to be able to subvert laws in it&apos;s erosion of the Constitutional form of Government we now live under. Deep State has been placing these people for decades. They now control enough of the Government to make their move. 
 4) @POTUS and the @USMC are using Military Intelligence to locate these #DeepState &apos;sleepers&apos; that are in our Government, Private Industry and Foreign Governments and removing them from their roles. In essence, they&apos;re &apos;de-constructing&apos; the Deep State Infrastructure. 
 5) The reason you don&apos;t see any arrests or media coverage is because it is indeed a &apos;Civil War&apos; going on behind the scenes for control of the levers of power for the Federal Government. There are many &apos;actors&apos; posing as loyal Americans who are in fact getting paid to subvert us. 
 6) Back to Red October - One of the final threats to Ramius handing the Russian Sub over to the Americans is that there&apos;s a &apos;cook&apos; who&apos;s actually a KGB agent who tries to set off one of the Nuclear Missiles in the Sub to destroy the Sub. He is killed seconds before he succeeds. 
 7) That is exactly what Trump &amp;amp; the Marines are facing. They have to take out the #DeepState actors that have influence &amp;amp; can harm Americans before they can begin the mass arrests. Look at the #FloridaShooting - That was a message to POTUS that Deep State still has influence. 
 8) What can we do? PRAY! Pray for POTUS. Pray for America. Pray for our Military &amp;amp; our Marines. Pray that they can remove #DeepState without loss of American Life. Make no mistake. We are at War inside our borders that we must win or we&apos;ll lose our Nation. 
 9) What else can we do? Vote! Vote like your Life and Nation depends on it. Because it does. Trump needs help. He needs more Magatarians to help him defeat the Evil that grips our Country. The End #MAGA #QAnon #8Chan #TheGreatAwakening #TheStormIsHere @POTUS</texto><total_retweets type="int">52</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">77</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">11</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">7</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">747544757727952897</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">35823</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">28441</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">58165</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8350215193986962</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>