<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">387</hilo><total_tweets type="int">27</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) #SaveTheKids Now that I have a following, I am recreating...in a single, threaded post...my 27-point story of the #Treason against the US committed by #Hillary, #Obama, and the #Cabal, starting w/ #UraniumOne and #IranNukes deals. https://t.co/8Erg25zHAq 
 2) Trump was recruited by #Patriots/#Military as the only outsider (not part of establishment) who could really #DrainTheSwamp, which is much worse than the aforementioned #Treason. He is protected by the #Marines in particular. https://t.co/rYru2Vm1Bv 
 3) #SethRichMurder The #Cabal, which includes corrupt Dems/GOP, never expected #HRC to lose. They owned #FakeNews #LSM (lying socialist media), rigged #DNC primary for #Hillary, and unsuccessfully rigged actual election w/electronic voting https://t.co/xsyaS1U1Im 
 4) Despite stealing multiple states w/a combination of #ElectoralFraud and #IllegalVoting, the opposition to #HRC and support for #DrainTheSwamp overwhelmed at the booth...and #NSA helped to fight the fraud. https://t.co/dO4UnnqPe1 
 5) As insurance against potential loss, #HRC + corrupt DOJ &amp;amp; GOP (think #McCain) decided to frame Trump as agent of Russia. #RussianCollusion Lie was &quot;projection&quot; by #HRC, who herself actually colluded w/Russia in #UraniumOne deal, enriching herself. https://t.co/ev7WB43qBY 
 6) #HRC got $145M via &quot;donations&quot; to #ClintonFoundation in treasonous deal + millions more in other back-door deals and inflated speaking fees for serial #SexualPredator #BillClinton, while endangering US security w/20% of US Uranium going to Russia. https://t.co/fsjdJheq2H 
 7) #Obama + corrupt players at #DOJ and #FBI were also on-board w/most heinous act of corruption &amp;amp; #Treason this country has ever seen, blessing #UraniumOne deal despite incontrovertible proof of pay-to-play/bribery by Russia. https://t.co/55BHA90Ml7 
 8) Meanwhile, #DOJ, led by corrupt #LorettaLynch was running interference against any true investigation of #Hillary&apos;s multiple felonies in using unsecured server and providing classified documents (including SAP info) to our enemies (a virtual dead drop). https://t.co/weVCzr6UX5 
 9) While Hillary&apos;s #EmailScandal would bring anyone else life in prison. #CorruptComey wrote exoneration letter long before even interviewing key targets, including #HRC, &amp;amp; provided #Immunity + #DestroyingEvidence from accomplices #CherylMills. https://t.co/8vaYxxtlLV 
 10) Comey did not even attend the #HRC &quot;interrogation&quot; (chat), led by #HRC-fan Strzok&apos;s, where #Hillary was not even put under oath and was not recorded. No notes have been released, even if any were taken and not destroyed. It was a #ShamInvestigation. https://t.co/cVWXeXv46M 
 11) #FBI was more concerned w/finding leaker who exposed #BillClinton-#LorettaLynch #Tarmac meeting than recognizing obvious true #ObstructionOfJustice. After all, it was not an &quot;investigation&quot; but a &quot;matter&quot;...that&apos;s what #HRC told #Lynch to call it. https://t.co/ErT2UlxLsb 
 12) #DNCLeaks (NOT &quot;hacks&quot;) exposed utter corruption of Dems and primary process, including massive complicity by #MSM,/#DNC, compounded by #Wikileaks of #PodestaEmails (search it), revealing a #LuciferianCabal involved in #SpiritCooking and #Pedophilia. https://t.co/2vCtHZEhib 
 13) #DNC + #HRC had to clean up matters. Hence #DNCLeaker #SethRich was murdered in &quot;botched robbery&quot; in which NOTHING (wallet, cash, smartphone, jewelry) was stolen; DNC process server #ShawnLucas was also killed. Need emerged to frame Russia in DNC hack. https://t.co/n0LwAQOPG5 
 14) #RussianHacking Lie was born of discredited report by #AntiPutin hack #CrowdStrike, paid for by #DNC. Despite fact that this report has been debunked, FBI and ALL intelligence agencies (an #LSM lie) concluded Russia hacked DNC. https://t.co/UsFeRrF1O3 
 15) #FBI never even looked at DNC server...unclear whether they bothered to ask or were denied. Independent analysis https://t.co/s90n06pGmk…proves that data transfer occurred locally, likely a flash drive, and COULD NOT have been over Internet in a hack due to speed/bandwidth. 
 16) Trump had joked that &quot;perhaps [Russia] should share&quot; Hillary&apos;s illegally-deleted emails...given that she had destroyed them with #BleachBit, while smashing hard drives and cell phones with a hammer...no evidence of intention to destroy evidence, right? https://t.co/jaNkrESE9A 
 17) Thus was born decision to #FrameTrump for colluding with Russia. The effort was elaborate, including these key elements: a) create fake dossier using foreign intelligence agencies working w/muckraking firm #FusionGPS to create fantasy smear document. https://t.co/01w962pE47 
 18) b) Hide your tracks by using law firm (#PerkinsCoie) as intermediary to funnel &amp;gt;$10M in payments to #FusionGPS for fabricated report. c) While #LSM would swallow lies w/o question, still pay some journalists to supplement #MockingBirdMedia lies. https://t.co/11qjEEx7t1 
 19) d) Use fake #RussianDossier document as basis for FISA courts to issue warrant-less wiretaps. e) Install #server in #TrumpTower falsely linking Trump w/2 Russian banks. f) Use #FusionGPS to set up false-pretense &quot;framing&quot; meeting w/Russian + DT Jr. https://t.co/NaNvWg3hbL 
 20) g) Wiretap entire Trump Campaign...and, later, Transition Team, illegally #Unmask key Trump people (like @GenFlynn) w/recorded transcripts of normal calls w/Russian Ambassador, &amp;amp; claim #SmokingGun of collusion to complicit #LSM that runs with the lie. https://t.co/BAeLttB4av 
 21) h) While launching witch-hunt investigation of #RussianCollusion Lie, ignore provable crimes committed by #HRC, #Obama, #McCain and #DeepState. This includes falsely labeling #Truth about #PizzaGate/#PedoGate as &quot;debunked&quot; w/o investigation. https://t.co/c6VkD6y1eY 
 22) i) Take steps to ultimately cause #JeffSessions to recuse himself while appointing #RobertMueller, who himself looks compromised from actions while on top of #FBI. Strong evidence Mueller was a #DeepState appointee; #Truth will soon be revealed: https://t.co/zeunf43VkE 
 23) If #QAnon is legit, we&apos;ve moved from CalmBeforeTheStorm, to #TakeDown to #DrainTheSwamp. Many predictions by Q have come true w/in his first appearing at end of October, such as thousands of sealed indictments, tip-of-iceberg Hollywood/media exposure. https://t.co/QBbc1V6RRZ 
 24) Some of tweets by #POTUS align extremely well w/Q Anon: prediction of twitter takedown of #POTUS account on 11/2, which happened almost immediately, +++ in tweet (11/6), pictures look like from AFO (11/9), and 11/25 tweet pointing to Maga Pill. https://t.co/8eUYKNBN6a. 
 25) #QAnon seems to be making these hi-level points: He&apos;s under attack by CIA, protected by #Military and #NSA (trusts Adm. Rogers); #UraniumOne + #Iran deals most treasonous in history; BO is shadowing his trips; CIA is backing NK + Iran for staged event. https://t.co/Yvfuggsr03 
 26) #QAnon indicates that #Cabal is on run, but it involves massive corruption of up to 70% of politicians: #PedoGate for control, #Treason for $, financial corruption via &quot;foundations&quot; that are piggy banks - explains obscene wealth on govt salaries. https://t.co/VR0vu2CeJH 
 27) We must spread this information and awareness as #POTUS is a salmon swimming upstream against corrupt establishment in both parties and #LSM which claims #Truth = #FakeNews. Crowd-sourced #QAnon Q&amp;amp;A compilation is available via this spreadsheet: https://t.co/BCqImLkNYM</texto><total_retweets type="int">251</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">368</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">40</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">69</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">749684424</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">3785</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3969</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">6802</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7780699304231409</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>