<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">378</hilo><total_tweets type="int">28</total_tweets><texto type="str">The evolution of democracy: Don&apos;t just delete Facebook, kill it. Listen to Heather Marsh tell you how. #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/g5PAr0k3xb … https://t.co/sxxS8zRhB3 … 
 &quot;News without action is just voyeurism and action without information creates a very easily manipulated public&quot; #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/57HSVnHGpr 
 How many people here have heard of a technological singularity? /2 https://t.co/I74p1Xf0mE 
 &quot;We need to somehow create nuanced and detailed information we can trust and we need to coordinate goals with people we will never speak to.&quot; /3 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/Zyblc3saZM 
 &quot;For action based tasks, the model that has become almost ubiquitous is the competitive hierarchical model.&quot; / 4 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/ZZNLephThn 
 &quot;The typical response to a situation which requires an action is to create a noun, in the form of an organization, government body, or an official person and the focus is always on the organization and the personalities involved instead of the action.&quot; /5 https://t.co/xgjMNRPLDA 
 &quot;The alternative to competition has traditionally been cooperation. Cooperative groups try to replace the top down hierarchy with a group consensus driven system which allows diversity of opinion at the top.&quot; /6 https://t.co/X5QKvdzPxe 
 &quot;This is most effective only in groups of two to eight people. For groups larger than 25, cooperation is extremely slow. It is still a personality based system&quot; /7 https://t.co/GPwWsxXONH 
 Do you know what stigmergy is and what makes a system stigmergic? /8 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/i3pgv9FR06 
 &quot;Stigmergy gives people autonomy over their own work. With stigmergy, an initial idea is freely given, and the project is driven by the idea, not by a personality or group of personalities.&quot; /9 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/fy5A9Fuwoc 
 &quot;There are no official authorities but the power of the user group still exists in the ability to accept or reject the work.&quot; /10 https://t.co/V4CnzBi4g0 
 Where is stigmergy? We have always had stigmergy in our social lives and it has been behind most mass movements that have had any success. /11 https://t.co/1nUAoyLcYi 
 &quot;You can see it wherever groups of diverse people who do not belong to any formal organization or have any formal communication with each other are all working together to carry out a goal.&quot; /12 https://t.co/w5KEJh8hZZ 
 It is not often you find one organization or group that is purely stigmergic, but #Anonymous is one. /13 https://t.co/N8lB9tMB5l 
 So the same methods can be used for corporate work. /14 https://t.co/dZZwxNjJPm 
 Which brings us to my next point which is about idea based collaboration. /15 https://t.co/0QoOP6srDP 
 &quot;We have stigmergy for action based collaboration which follows an idea, but what if we want to collaborate on ideas themselves, to build knowledge and find some most reliable facts?&quot; /16 https://t.co/qqYDnhXya4 
 &quot;We can’t keep berating voters for not spending all of their time studying everything that affects them, it’s impossible and it’s not fun either. We need to find a better solution.&quot; /17 https://t.co/FKYzREb0kO 
 Why do we need concentric circles in a democracy? /18 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/Go5s8KM8X7 
 &quot;When people lose faith in those who are supposed to be their experts, like politicians, or those who are supposed to be their knowledge bridges like the media, they lose faith in any stigmergic goal these people present and they will block it&quot; /19 https://t.co/EtWGdFRSsc 
 &quot;The more easily understood and the less challenging your message, the wider your appeal will be so an age that amplifies the most popular information, as we do now, will be an age of demagogues.&quot; /20 https://t.co/RoDyNXpPKK 
 &quot; We need to be able to find expertise and accurate and diverse information that we can trust before we form our opinions and long before we measure them.&quot; /21 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/xvBHFtKDqs 
 &quot;Communication should not be the full responsibility of the experts in the centre, which is where government initiatives like #Brexit .. have failed. &quot; #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/20L10DSb0Q 
 &quot;In a concentric circle, people or ideas promoted to the center by their peer group receive greatest amplification and their findings will be audited, amplified and explained to the general public by outer circles. &quot; /23 https://t.co/MAKhGAlw4y 
 &quot;Ownership of ideas is in complete opposition to stigmergy which is to say it is in complete opposition to rapid progress, finding the best solutions and democracy.&quot; /24 https://t.co/MQJ7viqWI6 
 &quot;So what we have been looking for here are methods of collaboration that bring us a balance between autonomy, diversity and society.&quot; /25 #Stigmergy #ConcentricCircles #Getgee https://t.co/89LKDqoInm 
 Let’s develop better tools for democracy. /26 #DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee https://t.co/gRWfhTagwu 
 Find out more about the future Facebook killer @GetGee_ : The Universal Database at https://t.co/VsEQPm9JRa 🛰️#DeleteFacebookNow #DeleteFacebook #CambridgeAnalyticaUncovered #Brexit #Trump #Getgee</texto><total_retweets type="int">161</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">166</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">35</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">373157754</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">170561</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">834</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">305674</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.3340898903048513</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>