<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">145</hilo><total_tweets type="int">12</total_tweets><texto type="str">Live at #io18, human-centered #AI4all thought leader @drfeifei w/ #GoogleBrain&apos;s @greg_corrado chatting about the future of #AI for everyone w/ #DianeGreene, pics by @AILaPaz&apos;s ambassador @AnitaRui2 &amp;amp; @WTMLaPaz&apos;s @wondermony https://t.co/n8uZQCXvqU 
 2/ @drfeifei on #MachineIntellligence history: 3 critical factors converged to brought us the AI boom: advances in hardware, emergence of powerful big data and advances in deep learning and machine learning algorithms 
 3/ @greg_corrado: renaissance in neural networks &amp;amp; deep learning and recently reinforcement learning leads the re-convergence of disciplines like cognitive science, neuroscience and #AI who have been separated for a while. 
 4/ @greg_corrado on #AGI: machines can do pattern recognition every bit as well as humans can, but it is a tiny sliver of what goes into something like intelligence. We haven&apos;t even scratched the surface of memory, planning, strategy, contingency and even #EQ. 
 5/ @drfeifei on #AGI: &quot;humanity has a tendency to overestimate short term progress and underestimate long term progress, so eventually we will be achieving things that we can not dream of&quot; 
 6/ @drfeifei&apos;s 1st element to complete human-centered #AI thinking: advancing AI to the next stage, there is a need for AI to be more flexible, nuanced, learn faster, more unsupervised, semi-supervised learning ways, understand emotion, communicate with humans. 
 7/ @drfeifei&apos;s 2nd element is technology and application: this tech is to enhance/augment humans, not to replace them, will replace certain tasks and replace humans out of danger, but the bottom line is we can use #AI to help doctors, disaster relief workers, decision makers. 
 8/ @drfeifei&apos;s 3rd element is combine thinking of #AI as a tech as well as societal impact: bring social scientists, philosophers, law scholars, policy makers, ethicists and historians to study more deeply about #AI social humanistic impact. 
 9/ @greg_corrado on explainable #AI: unfortunate mythology that deep learning is a black box which it really isn&apos;t, there are tools that examine how these systems work and explainability is a big part in terms of making these things available for a bunch of applications. 
 10/ @drfeifei&apos;s 2 major kind of #bias: one is the pipeline of #AI development from bias of data to the outcome of the bias, and the second is the human bias, the people who are developing #AI and the lack of diversity. 
 11/ @greg_corrado on #AI&apos;s future: one of the great opportunities is going to be the development of artificial emotional intelligence that allows products to actually have much more natural and more fluid human interactions. 
 12/ The recorded &quot;Building the future of artificial intelligence for everyone&quot; session is available at https://t.co/HPexi8ymzj #io18</texto><total_retweets type="int">8</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">41</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">13</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">822259</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">2032</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2700</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">8044</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7465009650272779</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>