<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">333</hilo><total_tweets type="int">30</total_tweets><texto type="str">The Cambridge Analytica Whistleblower Had A Company That Met With Trump’s Campaign Manager https://t.co/UaUCxtYL5a via @RMac18 
 Eunoia Technologies, subsequently pitched Corey Lewandowski on microtargeting tools that could be deployed on behalf of Donald Trump’s 2016 presidential campaign. Emails from 2014 show that Eunoia, Wylie&apos;s company, possessed a db of more than 50 million Fb profiles at the time. 
 GSR, Cambridge Analytica, and Wylie said they have since deleted the data...mmhmm. 
 Docs show: spring 2015 Wylie’s startup pitched elections-related work to Lewandowski. 1 source, confirmed their authenticity; Another person, who had direct knowledge of Eunoia’s meeting w Lewandowski, confirmed the Wylie-led startup’s interest in working for Trump camp 
 The docs / interviews w sources do not always cast Wylie in a flattering light, but they also do not call into question his claims about the improper transfer of Fb user data... After responding to an initial request for comment, Wylie&apos;s attorney went dark. 
 Late 2013 According to two people who knew Wylie at this time, the he had approached a number of colleagues about leaving their jobs to join him in a new company. According to one person, Wylie hoped to model his firm after Palantir Technologies. 
 “He was very much trying to build this company and his vision was, ‘I want to build SCL without [Cambridge Analytica CEO] Alexander Nix,’” said one person who talked to Wylie about his new venture. 
 Early 2014, Wylie put together a presentation for https://t.co/LqyhCLqyLD. According to its pitch deck, it cld ingest users&apos; social media activity &amp;amp; build “psychographic” profiles for marketers who&apos;d then target ads to specific users/ possibly influence behavior. 
 Winter 2014, Wylie was having conversations about his idea with Silicon Valley venture capitalists, including one who spoke to BuzzFeed News and received a note that said the products that Wylie had promised had been used for previous political clients. 
 After leaving Cambridge Analytica and SCL in late June of 2014, Wylie pivoted his focus to Eunoia — Greek for “beautiful thinking” — formulating a company that could perform so-called psychographic modelling and targeting for its clients. 
 Aug 2014, he was working at Eunoia with Tobias Kloepper, a one time SCL data scientist, who would obtain Facebook data for Eunoia. Emails indicate that Aleksandr Kogan, a data scientist and founder of GSR, shared a database of more than 50 million Facebook users with Kloepper. 
 Sept2014 Wylie claimed to have meetings w Monsanto, the American Petroleum Institute, and Ford. A Eunoia fashion-focused presentation said the company had a “db that contains the info of 100s of millions of individual consumers w emails, Fb/Twitter IDs &amp;amp; mailing addresses,” 
 ...while a separate company brochure specifically discusses targeting voters for potential political clients. Neither document mentions the specific GSR dataset of 50 million Facebook users, and it’s unclear if Eunoia ever put that data to use. 
 In Brochure: “The heart of our work stems from a rigorous scientific understanding of human behavior, which in turn allows us to engineer more responsive audiences and engage consumers more precisely... 
 &quot;...to do this, we have developed a series of algorithms that can predict the personality traits of individual voters by analyzing their voterfile [sic], social, online &amp;amp;consumer data.” 
 According to 1 person, GSR gave data to Eunoia after Kogan negotiated an agreement where Eunoia wld get the info FREE as part of a data-sharing agreement between the two parties. Wylie never provided Kogan w data of his own, this person said, and GSR cancelled agreements in 2015 
 Eunoia appears to never have officially launched; a separate source told BuzzFeed News that it was unable to secure funding. 
 The spread of the Facebook data was not confined to CambridgeAnalytica. Wylie may have had access to the data set for more than a year after founding Eunoia, with Fb only acting to address the violation of its rules in late 2015, after the release of a story in the Guardian. 
 GSR was told to delete its data in December 2015, according to a source, while Wylie said in testimony in front a parliamentary committee Tuesday that he believed he deleted the GSR data “some time in 2015” after being contacted by Kogan. 
 Asked last week if Eunoia had used any data sets on Facebook users, Wylie’s lawyer, Allen, was adamant. “Eunoia was a personal service company that has no data or assets,” she wrote. 
 Wylie didn’t say Eunoia met w Lewandowski. Lewandowski met with reps, including Tadas Jucikas, fmr SCL employee &amp;amp;Mark Gettleson, Eunoia’s comms/mkting strategist in 2015 in NYC. Wylie didn&apos;t go but was well aware of it/purpose. Voter microtargeting for possible potus candidate. 
 Lewandowski met w Eunoia, in part, because the Nix operation was already working for Cruz’s presidential election team at the time. According to that source, that meeting included “high-level discussions” about microtargeting techniques and did not include any talk about Fv data. 
 Emails further corroborate the pitch to the Trump campaign. April 2015 following the mting w Lewandowski, Gettleson, a UK liberal democratic political operative sent an email with the subject line “Trump” to a graphic designer incl attachment labeled “Trump-Handout,”... 
 “Trump-Handout,” contained a list of various political microtargeting products and services offered by eunoia. 
 The graphic designer made adjustments to the doc and placed its contents on official Eunoia stationary before sending it back to Gettleson called “eunioa_stationary_introletter.” Unclear if docs were sent to Lewandowski or others in Trump campaign 
 Docs which included business contracts and pitch decks, reveal other individuals who, to varying degrees, were associated w Eunoia Ray Larson, a former strategist for Canada’s liberal party Brent Clickard, a former colleague of Wylie’s at SCL... 
 Alfredas Chmieliauskas, a London-based employee of Palantir, said he had “no idea” why his name was on Eunoia’s business docs NYT reported while at Palantir, he began corresponding with Wylie in 2013, later gave him idea to develop the quiz app 
 Correspondence from Wylie show him bragging to an acquaintance in late 2013 about the prospect of someone from Palantir wanting to join his startup. “A guy from Palantir wants to join the team,” Wylie wrote. “He knows Tadas [Jucikas]... apparently senior... mting him next week.” 
 According to a source, Eunoia also sought to hire Mark Block, former chief of staff to 2012 presidential candidate Herman Cain. Block’s name and that of his associate, Linda Hansen, were printed on a proof sheet of draft Eunoia business cards given by a second source. 
 “You guys are a bunch of assholes, and you can put that on the record,” Block said when asked about his relationship w Eunoia and Wylie. Block, who reportedly introduced Steve Bannon to SCL, worked for its elections division declined to say anything more. He so sweet...</texto><total_retweets type="int">295</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">720</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">37</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1675563421</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">19221</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2981</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">191665</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9573787595008737</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>