<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">50</hilo><total_tweets type="int">8</total_tweets><texto type="str">The most common form of propaganda is repetition. This is why the @BBC repeat over and over negative stories about Labour and its Leadership but, have hardly ever said anything about the incredible criminality of the Conservative Party and its Leadership in last 8 years. 
 Importantly, this also applies to outright #lies. Mark Twain said &quot;A Lie Can Travel Halfway Around the World While the Truth Is Putting On Its Shoes,&quot; and he was right. 
 But in today&apos;s world with instant communication it takes but the utterance of a lie a single time by a institution like the @BBC for a lie to be believed. 
 Given this enormous power, and given their proclivity for #Lying and, their practice of repeating their lies endlessly (as they do with their smears against Labour) it is surely time they were stripped of their powers to shape the #News cycle 
 By this I mean - The @BBC should no longer be allowed to do anything other than entertainment as they simply cannot be trusted, and even this must be carefully monitored. 
 Remember, a lie repeated often enough by a powerful organisation such as our Government and/or it&apos;s communication wing the @BBC, invariably becomes the accepted truth. And yes, they learned that lesson exactly from whom you think they learned it. 
 Lastly as but a single piece of evidence of this outrageous practice by the @BBC I give you this because it is contemporaneous to the moment, but their are literally thousands of other examples I could give... https://t.co/2mpQXAMyBs 
 Their - There * [oops my bad]</texto><total_retweets type="int">344</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">469</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">27</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">141161261</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">2527</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1258</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">81476</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8299404183302107</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>