<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">394</hilo><total_tweets type="int">28</total_tweets><texto type="str">The new Republican talking point—radio, TV, White House—is any critique of conservative public policy is an attempt to &quot;divide the country.&quot; 
 2/ Let&apos;s be clear: the motto of The New Fascism is, &quot;Don&apos;t divide the country.&quot; It&apos;s a way to intimidate dissenters and *end* public debate. 
 3/ Have a problem with the current debate surrounding police brutality? *Engage the debate*. Only a fascist says &quot;Don&apos;t divide the country.&quot; 
 4/ Trump voters laud his candor, but his &quot;Don&apos;t divide the country!&quot; rhetoric masks a cowardly unwillingness to say what he really believes. 
 5/ And what does Trump really think? That the NFL should&apos;ve given him a team and he doesn&apos;t give a *damn* about police brutality either way. 
 6/ We&apos;ve been hearing &quot;Don&apos;t divide the country!&quot; from Rush Limbaugh, from Donald Trump, from Paul Ryan, from Republicans across the board. 
 7/ We started hearing this New Fascist slogan well before Colin Kaepernick took a knee. The far right uses it on *all* controversial issues. 
 8/ It&apos;s an Orwellian way of seeming to support unity while aggressively preventing the open dialogue that allows a lasting unity to develop. 
 9/ If Donald Trump weren&apos;t a coward, he&apos;d have Huckabee Sanders just come out and *say* Trump thinks there&apos;s no police brutality in America. 
 10/ Of course, saying what you think allows a debate to unfold. Opting for pure rhetoric instead is a fascistic technique—and has long been. 
 11/ The best part? Trump&apos;s base has *long* had, as its animating issue, the notion that the New Left is squashing public debate and dissent. 
 12/ There may well be elements of the New Left that use such tactics. But they use them less often—and less successfully—than Donald Trump. 
 13/ The perverse paradox of Trump is, he wants to be loved but if he ever said what he really thinks he&apos;d discover America isn&apos;t behind him. 
 14/ America *doesn&apos;t* support him not caring about policy—it *doesn&apos;t* support him using the flag as cover for his vendetta against the NFL. 
 15/ It *doesn&apos;t* support him using &quot;tax reform&quot; as a cover to enrich himself as he does virtually nothing at all for middle-class taxpayers. 
 16/ To be honest, I don&apos;t think his base even supports him avoiding the police brutality issue using cowardly, empty nationalistic rhetoric. 
 17/ The Trump voters I come across online are angry—they *want* to debate police brutality, not spout a &quot;Don&apos;t divide the country!&quot; bromide. 
 18/ That&apos;s why I call this &quot;The New Fascism&quot;: what lies behind it is a fear the far-right position isn&apos;t strong enough to withstand debate. 
 19/ Trump wraps himself in the flag as a way to hide his personal motives but *also* his unwillingness to debate the police brutality issue. 
 20/ I think both Left *and* Right should reject the falseness and cowardice of Trump&apos;s &quot;New Fascism&quot; and just debate the issues at hand now. 
 21/ When I hear—say—Limbaugh replace *zero* facility with the facts of the police brutality debate with empty rhetoric, it&apos;s just grotesque. 
 22/ It also suggests that the Right has *no* response to many Americans&apos; concerns about police brutality, and *that* should anger the Right. 
 23/ &quot;Class warfare&quot;; &quot;dividing the country&quot;; &quot;election butt-hurt&quot;—one side of our national political discourse collapsed into lame bromides. 
 24/ Anyone who&apos;s upset about &quot;PC culture&quot; destroying public debate should be *equally* upset about empty rhetoric destroying the same thing. 
 25/ If you love the flag and think it&apos;s being disrespected, defend that view with *studied positions on police brutality*—not fascistic pap. 
 PS/ Actually no, because Trump has yet to take *any* position on police brutality—which is what we&apos;re talking about. https://t.co/Cu3D0PbcMe 
 PS2/ Unless, of course, you count him telling a large gathering of police officers that they should definitely brutalize all their suspects. 
 PS3/ Afterwards he said, clearly falsely, that it was a joke—further proof he doesn&apos;t have the courage of his personal/political conviction.</texto><total_retweets type="int">4752</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">13878</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">341</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">3223426134</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">670013</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">37</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">51875</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">2.258361470728224</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>