<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">5</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">Thread: Kenney&apos;s take on safe injection sites is horribly misguided, even in a vacuum, as @DShepYEG points out. But, in a larger context, it also suggests something more concerning. When you&apos;re Premier, you&apos;re in charge of a great many things. #ableg 
 Whether it be healthcare, education, infrastructure, the environment, or harm reduction strategies for the opioid crisis, the Premier is the person at the head of the table. It&apos;s too many things for one person to know intimately enough such that he/she can make decisions alone. 
 I&apos;m of the belief that the most successful politicians are the ones who will listen to the experts in whatever the respective field may be. Want to craft the best policy to deal with the opioid epidemic? Talk to the experts in that field. Don&apos;t shut them down. 
 Kenney is suggesting that he knows better than people who have dedicated their lives and careers to this field. They present empirical evidence to support their positions, but apparently it&apos;s not enough. 
 We see the same thing in the dealings with @andrew_leach, et. al on environmental policy and the economics behind it. It&apos;s become a quest to alienate expert opinion in favor of anecdotal evidence and sound bites that get certain voters excited, even in the absence of fact. 
 I don&apos;t know when or why we decided that shunning evidence-based policy was the best way forward, but it&apos;s not a good thing for the modern conservative movement. We have to be better than this. When overwhelming empirical evidence suggests X, screaming Y does us no good. 
 /thread #ableg</texto><total_retweets type="int">94</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">250</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">14</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">856850515</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">528</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">647</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">1176</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7145223871602987</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>