<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">334</hilo><total_tweets type="int">27</total_tweets><texto type="str">IN DEFENSE OF BOOMERS (AND PERSPECTIVE FOR MILLENNIALS) /1 
 If you’re like most people, you probably find boomers annoying. Left thinks they’re backwards and destroyed the economy, right thinks they’re naive and destroyed culture 
 But despite what some trad-cons would make you think, boomers didn’t just come in like Miley Cyrus on a wrecking ball and annihilate all that was pure and good in the world Everything they did happened for a reason… and it wasn’t entirely unjustified (or negative) 
 The Greatest Gen had tragedy from the beginning of their lives to give them purpose. Survive the depression as a child, stop the Nazis as a young adult, and then work your life to beat the Soviets Existence was always on the line, and thus it was valued 
 Boomers had it different: they grew up in a world their parents saved. They had prosperity but no purpose. Stability but no love (greatest gen parents were notoriously cold) There were tons of expectations for them, their life was all mapped out. 
 Can you imagine how stifling that might have been? All the money… yet no meaning. Stable households... yet robotic dynamics. You had a role and you had to play it Boomers RIGHTLY indicted the system as lacking. Society had to allow more freedom of expression 
 So they rebelled. Everywhere they could they broke taboos. They made love to strangers, experimented with consciousness altering drugs, and when they finally settled down, they encouraged their children to chart their own path as well. 
 This is a hugely under-appreciated fact today. Boomers were incredibly affectionate to their children, and truly expressed their love for them. They might be the most supportive generation of parents that ever existed. 
 Lest we forget: Men being invested in their children’s lives is a BOOMER legacy. Ever since the industrial revolution men have hardly been involved with their kids at all, and even then, usually cold and abusive. Boomers broke this pattern, including in relationships 
 The idea of individuation? Charting your own course in life? Experiencing the world? BOOMER LEGACIES. Boomers told you it was ok to challenge your preconceptions and see what opportunities the world has to offer you. Boomers told you it was ok to take a year off to travel 
 We lack the context to remember just how disillusioned the west was with itself after WW2. We spent half a century killing TENS OF MILLIONS of each other, all because our leaders demanded it of us. There were serious questions about the leadership of society 
 When the US — the only country that had really avoided this mindset — fell into it in Korea and Vietnam, the latter became a tipping point People weren’t going to be sheep and fight and die for obtuse “global interests” anymore They weren&apos;t going to conform 
 That many of us find the current cultural climate oppressive is because we were raised by boomers who told us to think for ourselves and challenge the system Hating boomers is actually something the boomers taught us Ironically they taught us not to unequivocally respect them 
 The key problem with boomers really boils down to one thing: NARCISSISM They didn’t simply want to fix society, they wanted to turn it upside down And they lacked the self-awareness to see that while they were improving some things, they were creating a lot of other problems. 
 Even now they can’t admit what they’ve done, and they’ve never reconciled the extreme dissonance that for the last 25 years they’ve become “the man” And that things have gotten rapidly worse since then This is what really bothers people - the hypocrisy, lack of humility 
 They simply don’t know how to lead, because their parents kept the fundamentals together while they played utopia. The greatest gen had an &quot;oppressive&quot; system too, but at least it worked No one trusts boomer leadership, no one. It&apos;s chaos 
 The irony of the boomers is they were the generation that pioneered the idea of higher consciousness… and yet they have some of the lowest self-awareness. They can&apos;t see this Rather than fix what&apos;s going on they just blame each other Fox vs CNN in a nutshell 
 But back to boomer defense (this is hard)... Some people talk as if boomers were a virus that came out of nowhere, like they were inevitable… but they noticed the west&apos;s philosophy wasn&apos;t adequate to the changing tech and challenged it 
 Sometimes you must take a step backward to move forward. The boomers went too far, but they showed us a directions we needed to evolve in. And given the attitude of the west at the time, people prob weren’t going to remember what was so good about it unless they almost lost it. 
 My main issue with most boomers is not what they did, but what they are DOING. They can’t see their experiments have failed and that it’s time to back off. I want them out of power not because they made mistakes, but because they can’t learn from them. Ego-blindness 
 Our gens mission is to turn this ship around. To take the boomer critiques and integrate them with the prior foundation, calibrating for modern tech Boomers were right about many things, but wrong to think because something needs improvement it is fundamentally broken. 
 The west needed reform not revolution. This remains the case We must not make their mistake and throw the baby out with the bathwater like them You can NEVER go back. Even if you could, what died died for a reason You can only birth something new 
 People are prone to give up in such times, but every crisis has a silver lining: MEANING We have so much work ahead of us… is it not exciting? We have that rare opportunity… to be heroes. Not every generation has this chance. 
 Which is what makes nihilism reprehensible. There are too many ways people can make an impact to complain about “life not mattering.” This is particularly a problem with Gen X, who pioneered outrage culture and seems most addicted to doomsday predictions 
 Remember: People who tell you “nothing can be done” are ALWAYS miserable Why are you following them? STOP Don&apos;t isolate yourself and IGNORE the problems, but start working on a small level &quot;clean your room&quot; 
 If you’re not preparing now or thinking big visions of the future and how to manifest it, you’re missing out. There is not going to be another Boomer president; there may not even be another Gen X one. Millennials are going to have ALL the responsibility very soon 
 Which will take it? The future belongs to those who act. Get yourself together, because within the decade… you’re going to have the opportunity to lead And it’s an opportunity the boomers gave you Don’t complain, be grateful. You have a chance to matter. Seize it. /END/</texto><total_retweets type="int">97</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">777</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">47</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">2508068568</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">12020</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">278</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">24700</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1841001915646883</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>