<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">287</hilo><total_tweets type="int">24</total_tweets><texto type="str">🌊New #Qanon Thread🌊 🌊5/22/18🌊 &quot;Flood is Coming&quot; #Q #QArmy #WWG1WGA #WeThePeople #MAGA #GreatAwakening #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #DrainTheSwamp #tuesdaythoughts @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/LLBctuTaiS 
 New #QAnon 1434. Re_read. Slowly &amp;amp; carefully. https://t.co/VZOGNcqMID Did you see Ryan [PR] interview a short time ago? When you are no longer seeking another term you are &apos;FREE&apos; to make better decisions. RAPID FIRE. &apos;Flood is coming&apos; Future proves past. [CNN]. #MAGA @POTUS https://t.co/1HyaFgm5Sf 
 Re_read. Slowly &amp;amp; Carefully. https://t.co/VZOGNcqMID Sessions appointed Huber to conduct this investigation over 6 months ago. They&apos;ve been compiling a FLOOD of evidence &amp;amp; can move quickly to prosecute vs a slow, cumbersome special council. We can TRUST SESSIONS &amp;amp; HUBER. #Qanon https://t.co/8nNj4Qplrf 
 Q asks &quot;Did you see the Ryan [PR] interview a short time ago? When you are no longer seeking another term you are &apos;FREE&apos; to make better decisions.&quot; PR can no longer be controlled by THEM and is assisting in opening the proverbial floodgates. #Qanon #MAGA https://t.co/ZcxWbgwwTz 
 Q goes on to say &quot;Flood is coming&apos; Future proves past. [CNN].&quot; As this article explains, new McCabe emails &quot;show FBI brass discussed dossier briefings with CNN.&quot; McCabe entitled the email re: this matter-&apos;Flood is coming&apos; #Qanon #MAGA #Q #kag @POTUS #Trump https://t.co/MNQ8T2LnqL 
 Senator Johnson wrote to FBI Director Wray yesterday, on the newly discovered McCabe &apos;Flood is coming&apos; email, voicing concerns that top FBI brass were clearly aware that CNN was about to run a story with leaked details on the dossier. #Qanon #MAGA #Trump @potus #POTUS #WWG1WGA https://t.co/1XX66bqLVL 
 In Q&apos;s latest post, [CNN] is square inside the killbox. Does this mean CNN&apos;s press credentials will be revoked over these reports that &quot;suggest CNN helped orchestrate a possible set-up of then president elect Trump&quot;? #Qanon #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump @potus https://t.co/T3Kh0Liq3Q 
 Future does prove past, once again, as #QAnon predicted the &apos;flood is coming&apos; as early as December 22nd, and #Q brilliantly stated, the Flood is &quot;unstoppable&quot;. SURF&apos;S UP! 🏄‍♂️ #QAnon #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #DrainTheSwamp #tuesdaythoughts @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/IP2X2s2MxA 
 New #QAnon 1435. Anon: NELLIE OHR HAM RADIO Q: Avoid NSA data collection. It failed. #Q #WWG1WGA #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #WeThePeople #GreatAwakening #DrainTheSwamp #tuesdaythoughts @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/llrG6PDT1A 
 @TheLastRefuge2 states &quot;So, are we to believe it&apos;s COINCIDENTAL? All of a sudden a 60(ish)-year-old woman decides to us a HAM radio the month after contracting with Christopher Steele for a Russian dossier on Donald Trump? #Qanon #MAGA #Trump @POTUS #Q https://t.co/yvdukANLMN 
 New #Qanon 1436. It&apos;s happening. #Q #WWG1WGA #WeThePeople #MAGA #GreatAwakening #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #DrainTheSwamp #tuesdaythoughts @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/CwT6cToZMF 
 RAPID FIRE, mentioned in #Q&apos;s post today, is the name of a movie where a witness is betrayed and set up by FBI agents, a similar plot to the movie we&apos;re about to watch. You don&apos;t want to miss this thriller! Enjoy the show! 🍿 #QAnon #MAGA #Trump @POTUS #WWG1WGA #TuesdayThoughts https://t.co/4qgzv9Mlde 
 New #QAnon 1437. AF1_5A_2.jpg AF1_5A_3.png Air Force 1 photos of what? The storm? Watch the water? Wrays of light? 40,000 feet? #Q #WWG1WGA #WeThePeople #MAGA #Trump #POTUS #PatriotsFight #DrainTheSwamp #tuesdaythoughts @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/iAQL2fBxew 
 Anon theories on the photos #Q posted. Vietnam? Korean Peninsula? Beijing&apos;s militarization of the South China Sea? #QAnon #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #DrainTheSwamp #TuesdayThoughts @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/AsIqmXAuSI 
 Anons noticed that the first in the series of 3 photos #Q posted today, was originally posted on 11/9/17, which gives us a timeframe, as well as verifies that #Qanon is the same team both then and now. (Proof for all those claiming Q has been compromised). #MAGA #Trump @POTUS https://t.co/YPF4J9pNwb 
 If the photos #Q posted are of S. Korea, they would be very timely, as #Trump met with S. Korean President Moon today, hinting of a possible delay on the NK Summit. Are the photos our reassurance that the deal has already been done? #QAnon #MAGA @POTUS https://t.co/ASNHggAuh5 
 New #QAnon 1438. IDEN_reconf v. 11.9 Sequence. Attack[s] anticipated. Coordinated? Why are they continuing [internal]? Attacks will intensify [all sides]. #Q #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #draintheswamp #TuesdayThoughts @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/zlv0Iqiafr 
 In the latest #Q post, #QAnon is confirming their identity as the same Qanon back in Nov- a direct shot at Corsi et al who claim Q was compromised in April. Q implies they are coordinated and will intensify. #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight @POTUS #TuesdayThoughts @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/4nLiNl2epb 
 UNITY NOT DIVISION. Last post was simply for IDEN_reconf. https://t.co/jMnshHkFk4 Who is missing from the schedule meeting? [RR] Who is Ed O&apos;Callahan? [Ed] DECLAS_ Pain. Enjoy the show. #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #draintheswamp #tuesdaythoughts @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/0yvaWs8Bp2 
 The meeting on Thursday for lawmakers to review classified docs will include: Wray, Nunes, Gowdy, Coats and O&apos;Callahan. Not present: ROSENSTEIN. Fired or recused? Future will prove past I&apos;m sure. #Qanon #MAGA #WWG1WGA #POTUS #tuesdaythoughts @POTUS https://t.co/jMnshHkFk4 
 Who is Ed O&apos;Callahan? Could he be appointed to replace Rosenstein once recused/fired? Here is some info on O&apos;Callahan. #QAnon #MAGA #WWG1WGA #Trump #potus #PatriotsFight #draintheswamp @POTUS #TuesdayThoughts @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/l2IBu7cz0k 
 Only time will tell what color hat Ed O&apos;Callahan wears. He worked for the McCain/Palin campaign and was appointed by Rosenstein. In #Q&apos;s latest post, his name is in the kill[ ]. Will he be next after RR? #QAnon #MAGA #Trump #KAG @realDonaldTrump @POTUS https://t.co/55GdbdyJo2 
 Well, McCabe was right about one thing...a flood IS coming. Only, not the kind he expected. The deluge that&apos;s coming will cover this parched land with thirst quenching TRUTH and JUSTICE. Take a moment to soak it in. #QAnon #MAGA #Trump #WWG1WGA @realDonaldTrump #tuesdaythoughts https://t.co/2oGt6odTAq 
 @threadreaderapp unroll please</texto><total_retweets type="int">218</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">405</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">44</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">18</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">952758329301807104</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">33262</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">790</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">31371</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1600196745691849</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>