<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">264</hilo><total_tweets type="int">23</total_tweets><texto type="str">Fashionably late #BlackHistoryMonth ! Garrett Morgan (Thread) #TheResistance #BLM #RiseUp #Resist #ResistanceUnited #BlackLivesMatter Today, we have a happy ending, so let&apos;s all relax a bit and read up on a forgotten hero: https://t.co/sdtcz9R2mh 
 One of the reasons for #BlackHistoryMonth is that blacks are so often systematically erased from history, or simply forgotten in favor of their fairer-skinned counterparts. Today, we&apos;ll learn about Garrett Morgan, one of the greatest of the early 20th century. https://t.co/iK25sVfMCh 
 Born in Kentucky in 1877, he was the son of former slaves, reared in the reconstruction South. Actually, he also had European and Native American ancestry too, though, as we will see, this did not stop him from facing widespread discrimination. 
 At the age of 14, Morgan fled north to Cincinnati, away from the active KKK in Kentucky. With only a 6th grade education, he worked during the day, then hired tutors in the evening to complete his education. Four years later, 
 The KKK would move into Cincinnati as well, and again Morgan fled north to Cleveland, where blacks were far more rare. Eventually, he would be hired as an unskilled laborer at a textile factory, but that would not last long. https://t.co/uMNDhcItjd 
 He became so skilled at repairing the sewing machines, they gave him a job as a repairman. Not content with that, Morgan soon invented a retainer for the machine drive belts that reportedly increased efficiency by 20%. 
 The entire textile industry in Cleveland took notice of him, and he was hired away, with a significant raise, by a competitor, the Prince &amp;amp; Wolf Co. Unfortunately, the company&apos;s progressive employment policy would not last long. https://t.co/VZWHmwUiOr 
 There, he met a Czech immigrant working as a seamstress, Mary Hasek. When their relationship was discovered, they were ordered to either break it off or to leave the company. They left, and opened their own Shoe and Sewing repair company. https://t.co/5be3jGBUbp 
 Still not satisfied, Morgan expanded his business to fashion and tailoring, then, to hair products. He patented a sewing machine attachment that allowed for a zigzag pattern. He advertised his clothing and tailor shop locally, and his hair products regionally. https://t.co/1zJhH2sJOV 
 The business was a runaway success. Still not satisfied, Morgan saw how local firefighters in the rapidly expanding city of Cleveland were often suffering from smoke inhalation. He invented a “Safety Hood” the precursor to the modern gas mask. Still going, https://t.co/DgRVAH2vwJ 
 He saw how many traffic accidents there were on the chaotic and crowded streets of Ohio, and he invented a Three-Position Traffic Light to control intersections. This was the first of its kind in America, with Go, Stop, and Caution. https://t.co/9H8ReeRxIN 
 There was almost nothing that this man could not invent. Meanwhile, he began printing and publishing his own newspaper, targeted towards the black community in the region. He also began traveling back to the South to sell his “Safety Hoods.” https://t.co/Gah9e8nKf8 
 Being a black man, he was unable to sell his hoods there, so he hired a white friend to pretend to be the inventor, while he took the guise of “Big Chief Mason,” a Native-American who assisted the “white man” with “his invention.” 
 Personally, I think it is OK to laugh at this. In my mind, I imagine this ruse as something like an absurd comedy sketch from Richard Pryor and Gene Wilder, all designed to trick racist white people into giving their money over to a black man. https://t.co/HadeQWVEHE 
 In 1916, during the development of Lake Erie, a tunnel explosion occurred 50ft below the water. Dozens of workers were trapped, the tunnels were filled with noxious gasses, and two rescue attempts failed, the teams missing in action. Morgan was called to the scene. https://t.co/3ncNpalw7Z 
 Few of the white rescuers were willing to trust their lives to a black man&apos;s invention, so Morgan, his brother Frank, and a handful of brave volunteers donned the Safety Hood themselves and ventured in. Morgan and his invention saved nine workers that day. https://t.co/uOBgyUgNIy 
 Yet, when the Carnegie Hero Fund Commission later handed out awards for bravery during the disaster, Garrett and Frank Morgan were not among those honored. Even today, the CHFC disputes that Morgan played a substantial role worthy of the honor. https://t.co/pPgJojjEWN 
 To quote the CHFC in a letter to “Popular Mechanics”: “from the facts at hand it does not appear that it was attended by any extraordinary risk to [Morgan&apos;s] own life.” Yes indeed, because of the Hood that he himself invented you racist twits. https://t.co/WqXVMtE2IJ 
 In the end, Morgan had his revenge. When the local Country Clubs refused him entry, he simply founded his own, all-black, Country Club. Though rumor has it that Morgan&apos;s white friends were welcome, it can just be hard to know if you can trust white folk. https://t.co/lD2FV1seHP 
 Later in life, Morgan was among the early supporters of the NAACP, and dedicated much of his wealth and time to supporting education and college tuition for other blacks in the region, not to mention helping fund and establish black colleges. https://t.co/PpJq9lvnVd 
 And that&apos;s our hero of the Day, Garrett Morgan. The O.G. “Marry-White-Women, Get-Money, Invent-Lifesaving-Device-Then-Use-Said-Device-In-A-Daring-Tunnel-Rescue-Of-White-Folk, then, Retire-To-The-Country-Club-While-Being-A-Pillar-Of-The-Community” Black Man. https://t.co/0HrSf69sYA 
 So, next time you stop safely at a traffic light, or next time the police try to break up your Punk Rock Show using tear gas, (happens to me all the time) remember to thank the great Garrett Morgan. https://t.co/WfU0RVjmzG 
 Morgan had a saying: “My name is Morgan, but it ain&apos;t J.P.” The first to adapt that into a sick rhyme gets imaginary internet points. Thank you for taking the time to read this. -Ryan. https://t.co/XBWYUtdb4v</texto><total_retweets type="int">367</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1049</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">43</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">7</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">392212735</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">22961</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">20014</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">7984</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.822621617229562</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>