<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">158</hilo><total_tweets type="int">13</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. New #QAnon drop tonight tells us that: &quot;The gun found by the #USSS&quot; (Secret Service)) &quot;was an intercept&quot; they provided, that the &quot;Protect code went live,&quot; and that they &quot;are moving up the timetable&quot; on their plans. #Q https://t.co/lbQFBzdpTM https://t.co/fEvYnimjJk 
 2. #QAnon tells us tonight to&quot; &quot;Stay tuned. Everything has meaning or a purpose. @Jack - getting nervous? &amp;lt;-------------------------Twitter CEO* Phase [2]. #Q&quot; Many on Twitter tonight have had large numbers of their followers go away. I lost about 50 net out of 25,035 (0.2%). https://t.co/cX2DlFhYRB 
 3. So one #Anon connects #QAnon&apos;s &quot;Deep Dream&quot; reference to the Bourne film (https://t.co/ansGUpRcIb) in which the CEO of a social media giant known as #DeepDream secretly funded by #DeepState in the startup stage has has 2nd thoughts about giving #CIA access. https://t.co/X5Ae14Ul7h 
 4. The same #Anon also connects &quot;Iron Hand&quot;to #Qanon&apos;s references to &quot;Iron Eagle&quot;? &quot;Iron Hand&quot; is CIA&apos;s targeted assassination program in Bourne film. I saw that &quot;Iron Eagle&quot; is a movie where &quot;full access to.. intel&quot;&apos;s used to save where US gov wouldn&apos;t. https://t.co/I5l5s7Vs1G https://t.co/X0LuSGUCB1 
 5. In resp to above #Anon (3., 4.) #QAnon responds: &quot;Big post. @Jack thought he was protected. No sleep since drop. Tasked [3] to remove followers in drip order and restrict. Coincidence? HOT in DC. No sleep. Stay tuned. #Q&quot; So, this&apos;s why we lost our followers here tonight. 
 6. Note #QAnon tonight writes: &quot;@Jack thought he was protected. No sleep since drop.&quot; #Q Does Q &quot;knows when you are sleeping, knows when your awake, knows if @Jack been bad or good so be...&quot;? https://t.co/31C6wwMorn 
 7. On Sunday night 2/18, just before 9PM, #QAnon had told us &quot;:Protect 6/14-46 :Protect 6/14-46&quot; #Q (6/14-46 is President Trump&apos;s birthday.) https://t.co/PFGBquTgi0 
 8. &quot;Tonight #QAnon tells us that &quot;The gun found by the USSS was an intercept we provided. This is not a game. Protect code went live.&quot; #Q 
 9. #QAnon also tells us that &quot;Everything has meaning or a purpose.&quot; #Q 
 10. So tonight, an #Anon responds to #QAnon&apos;s indication that &quot;The gun found by the USSS was an intercept we provided,&quot; by posting #Q&apos;s Sunday 9PM post 9748) telling us twice to protect &quot;6/14-46&quot;. So, then in lieu of Monday morning&apos;s gun discovery, Q asks, &quot;Coincidence? Q&quot; https://t.co/G3mCY4X3SY 
 11. So, it appears credible to believe that #Q may have potentially saved President Trump&apos;s life Monday morning this week, by imploring Sunday night to protect the President. &quot;Coincidence? Q&quot; #QAnon &quot;There are no coincidences&quot; Q https://t.co/jMJvRuzB0t 
 12. Lastly, we note, early this mornig, that #QAnon posts: &quot;AG Sessions. US Cyber Task Force. Important. #Q&quot; 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">81</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">80</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">18</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">8</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>