<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">344</hilo><total_tweets type="int">26</total_tweets><texto type="str">Lean into this thread like #Zuckerbitch leaned into Kremlin financing. 😍😍 https://t.co/UFpZvXKwfb 
 2/ Angry @LincolnsBible is the best @LincolnsBible. Funny thing about trying to play the victim now, Zuck. It&apos;s a bit of a hard sell after numerous people tried to help you before and you called their efforts to educate you a &quot;pretty crazy idea&quot;. https://t.co/7f4YK3qaHK 
 3/ All the way back in October 2010, you did this, Mark. &quot;Facebook will supply Yandex with a data feed of status updates from Facebook Pages.&quot; &quot;Yandex says it will add the Facebook data into its blog search index.&quot; Closing in on 8 years ago. https://t.co/gxyFiihYP9 
 4/ Less than a year later, we find out Yandex is willingly passing its data to the FSB. You think the FSB didn&apos;t obtain everything Yandex had on Facebook? Lol. It&apos;s Russia. Of course they let the FSB do whatever they wanted to. https://t.co/03Zrb1lQhN https://t.co/rjNSYgCm5h 
 5/ Look here, @ericgarland. Andrey Sabelnikov created the Kelihos botnet. &quot;According to his public LinkedIn profile, from 2005-2007 he was a senior developer and product manager at Agnitum, a Russian security firm well-known for its firewall software.&quot; https://t.co/lxr18XbAmB https://t.co/WFcaoNWfWX 
 6/ Now let&apos;s fast forward to the 2016 election campaign. Agnitum. Hmm. Oh, here we go. &quot;On January 14, 2016, Agnitum confirmed on its official blog that the company was acquired by Yandex in December 2015.&quot; But what about all their customers! https://t.co/FzFVLc2qDb https://t.co/x917DdyL4o 
 7/ Agnitum➡️Kasperky &quot;To ensure further security of your computer, we encourage you to make use of a special offer. We offer all active Outpost license holders to exchange their Outpost licenses for Kaspersky Internet Security licenses free of charge.&quot; https://t.co/jkGeHMP4kI 
 8/ You mean Agnitum&apos;s users were able to move straight to &quot;ex&quot;-KGB/FSB man Eugene Kaspersky&apos;s platform free of charge? Why, yes! How nice of the FSB, right? But what about Facebook.... https://t.co/IzI7viCxRH 
 9/ Oh, dear. Zuckerberg left the front door open and the FSB walked right in. https://t.co/cRcuKqcpvn 
 10/ Right around the same time Facebook started running Kaspersky software on their platform, this happened. &quot;Kaspersky Lab paid former national security adviser Michael Flynn $11,250 in 2015 for cyber-security consulting.&quot; https://t.co/pK1BFbF9xJ 
 11/ Then this happened: https://t.co/lcO03DVCbC 
 12/ Then: &quot;Barry Bennett, senior political advisor to Donald Trump, will meet with Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg at the company’s headquarters on Wednesday.&quot; Bennett met Zuckerberg on May 18, 2016. That&apos;s one day after Rohrabacher met w/Rinat Akhmetshin. https://t.co/PkqcAyFMec 
 13/ Then something weird happened. Facebook posted a job listing for a SEO or SEM engineer on June 2, 2016. Normally, no big deal, right? Except, it almost seems like they wanted to make the qualifications so difficult, nobody would be qualified for it. https://t.co/q3zSzF6CQB https://t.co/cZUrGUFhWZ 
 14/ But why oh why would they do such a thing? Maybe because they didn&apos;t want a person in the job at all? Maybe the plan was to make it all automated/algorithm driven, but they didn&apos;t want people to know? That is what ended up happening, after all. https://t.co/jpa7OopKiH 
 15/ But I&apos;m getting ahead of myself. On June 9, Yandex announced changes to their version of Google&apos;s PageRank algorithm. You know, it&apos;s the thing that decides which news articles pop up first when you do a search or scroll through your news feed. https://t.co/EOXuZsszDt 
 16/ Wouldn&apos;t you know it, though. The Yandex code was already in Breitbart&apos;s site by this point! June 9, 2016 was the day of that infamous meeting in Trump Tower. Rinat Akhmetshin (who met with Rohrabacher in May) was there. So were Manafort &amp;amp; Kushner. https://t.co/dWZCFl4r2o 
 17/ Guess what Facebook decided to do that week? &quot;You have always been able to hide posts from your Facebook page after the fact, but now Facebook lets you post to the News Feed without the items ever touching your Timeline.&quot; Perfect for bots bots bots. https://t.co/tIXJ8y45xx 
 18/ Facebook only recently admitted to this because of pressure by people like you and me who are sick of being lied to by Mark Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg. &quot;Facebook has admitted that up to 270m accounts on the social network are illegitimate.&quot; https://t.co/vD3Yxu4jo0 
 19/ There are/were plenty more fake accounts than that. Don&apos;t kid yourself. Zuck wants to get off easy. Don&apos;t let him. In any case, Facebook tried a new algorithm in August 2016. They said it would work! Spoiler: it didn&apos;t. https://t.co/o9zpYJxlvS 
 20/ At the same time their new algorithm was failing by design, Facebook made sure your data was their data, even if you tried to stay safe. &quot;Facebook is making the HTML of its web ads indistinguishable from organic content so it can slip by adblockers.&quot; https://t.co/pj8NxzZTEF 
 21/ Here&apos;s Facebook’s VP of ads Andrew Bosworth with the lamest excuse for stealing your private information you may ever see. Hey @boztank, I can see Russia from your bank account! https://t.co/MFFKZbPPc2 
 22/ Because in late August 2016, we also see Yandex doing this. &quot;And this week, it dipped a toe into yet another territory: user feedback interpreted by machine intelligence.&quot; Data mining. They tell you: &quot;We want to make things better for you!&quot; https://t.co/AcpS9lGUsB 
 23/ When really, they want harvest all your personal information and sell it to the highest bidder. &quot;It &apos;mines&apos;, refines, aggregates and sells its users’ personal information and data trails to advertisers, who then use it to target ads at said users.&quot; https://t.co/b4A31GEwbR 
 24/A key insider from the Trump campaign&apos;s digital operation-Theresa Wong-unravels for the first time the role played by social media and Facebook&apos;s in getting Trump into the White House. &quot;They were helping us. They were basically our hands-on partners.&quot; https://t.co/BJw8lnMnw4 
 25/ Here&apos;s the deal: Facebook only cares about one thing: profits. They don&apos;t care about democracy dying in darkness or thriving in sunlight. They care about money. Want them to change? Hit them where it hurts. Then hit them again. Just like this: https://t.co/u1u4yj86u4 
 26/ cc @sherylsandberg Tell Mark good luck with his Congressional testimony! I&apos;m sure he&apos;ll do fine! 😂😂🤣🤣 Sorry, Sheryl. Eventually, he&apos;s gonna have to use his big boy voice all on his own. Mommy can&apos;t protect him forever. I&apos;m done here, but ... https://t.co/O3A7A7LZJY</texto><total_retweets type="int">2259</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">4181</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">116</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">817166972764962816</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">42617</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">879</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">61149</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1736882754594713</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>