<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">159</hilo><total_tweets type="int">13</total_tweets><texto type="str">Morning all! Time for my daily #brexit realisation: &quot;#Brexit only makes sense when you realise that these people really, REALLY just don&apos;t care.&quot; 
 They don&apos;t care if the NHS fails. They have private healthcare 
 They don&apos;t care about EU citizens - bargaining chips - they&apos;ll just get cheaper labour in to clean their privvies, build houses and work in the NHS. (Don&apos;t forget #Windrush) 
 They don&apos;t care about British people in the EU27. Bargaining chips and citizens of nowhere 
 They don&apos;t care about food standards or farmers, people can eat chlorinated chicken. Farmers can go use food banks. 
 They don&apos;t care about environmental standards, they WANT to pursue damaging fossil fuel strategies 
 They don&apos;t care about cancer patients who need isotopes for their treatment 
 They don&apos;t care about stripping workers rights - in fact this is a bonus and part of the plan. 
 They don&apos;t care about the people of NI, Gibraltar or the Falklands. 
 They don&apos;t care that Scotland was threatened having their EU membership voided in 2014 during indyref and now despite Scotland voting #remain they will lose it anyway. 
 They don&apos;t care that the will of the people has changed 
 They don&apos;t care that UK will become a tax haven. Again this is a bonus and possibly the end goal of #brexit https://t.co/wWNEToeYmO 
 So happy Saturday folks(!) Sorry this was all rather depressing. I DO believe we can #StopBrexit but just bear this all in mind. They are quite happy to torch this country for their own gain. Remember that as the fight goes on. And keep up the good work using #FBPE! https://t.co/i4mjqdWJ1g</texto><total_retweets type="int">211</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">598</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">25</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">943788254</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">10611</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">10617</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">156642</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8009874696220625</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>