<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">237</hilo><total_tweets type="int">20</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. IRAN; A timeline for those of you conveniently absent minded of the facts. #IranNuclearDeal #Iran #Iranian #ThanksObama #ObamaLegacy #Obama 2002- Iran was caught red-handed secretly building an underground centrifuge facility in Natanz. 
 2. 2009 Iran was again caught secretly building a huge underground nuclear facility for uranium enrichment. Ask Yourself &quot;if the Iranians had only peaceful ambitions with their nuclear program, why then hide your uranium enrichment from everyone&quot;? https://t.co/wgl5Sz9dhp 
 3. Heavy sanctions &amp;amp; UN sanctions were put in place against Iran. But no sooner were they in place, that Obama had Hillary open back channel communications through her buddy &amp;amp; Clinton foundation supporter, the Sultan of Oman.The sanctions ended up having no real effect on them. https://t.co/kENOzPzpD5 
 A senior official in the Middle East was quoted &quot;Just when the sanctions started working &amp;amp; Iran was feeling real economic pressure, Obama threw them a lifeline&quot;. https://t.co/3oCr40iYSi 
 4. 2012 Secret meetings in Oman initiated by Hillary. The Iranians wont sit at the table unless Sanctions are relieved &amp;amp; the US stop seeking global commitment against Iran&apos;s Nuclear enrichment &amp;amp; allow them to continue enrichment. https://t.co/X1NduHoMcr 
 But wait! That&apos;s not all! Iran demanded 12 Billion dollars in cash payments from frozen Iranian assets prior to the beginning of negotiations!! Setting a pattern for concession after concession. https://t.co/ajOJbqiMyK 
 and we knew the money was not going to be used for good. THAT is one of the main reasons why the assets were kept frozen all this time! And yet, Obama.... https://t.co/0CZPQCN1QB 
 5. June 2009 In what is at that moment the greatest threat to their power. Iran&apos;s Mullahs crush protests against a rigged election Obama; remaining hopeful of that sit down with Iranian leadership sits out on his support of the Iranian people. A major mistake. https://t.co/z3dLE4poUt 
 6. All thru 2000&apos;s Iran continues to defy multiple Security Council resolutions, these resolutions are the reason for the sanctions &amp;amp; the sanctions cripple its economy. https://t.co/WbAXSzUy0a 
 Use some critical thinking here: If you&apos;ve nothing to hide, use that ACE card to open the country for inspection in return for lightening those sanctions. They didn&apos;t because they couldn&apos;t. https://t.co/4bj7uR1KPu 
 7. Iran develops an ICBM program, you don&apos;t put rocks, firecrackers or conventional TNT on them. ICBM&apos;s have only one purpose. https://t.co/TSQzUQleaf 
 8. As of now, heavy water reactors are in the works in Iran. Research how heavy water reactors give you Plutonium. Could plutonium reactors be used for peaceful purposes? Sure, and a 16-inch beheading knife also could be used to spread jam on your toast in the morning. https://t.co/YSY0uV3Iaf 
 9. 2013 Rouhani, on Iranian TV in May, detailed how he broke nuclear pledge in 2008 &quot;While we were talking to the Europeans in Tehran, we were installing equipment in Isfahan.&quot; https://t.co/FCnwbnuXFX https://t.co/seUiNWLAVT 
 10. Since the declaration of the Islamic Republic of Iran in 1979, the government of Iran has been accused by members of the international community of funding, providing equipment, weapons, training and giving sanctuary to terrorists https://t.co/33BUy5qD3n 
 11. Iran has remained the most active state sponsor of terrorism in 2010. Iran’s financial, material, &amp;amp; logistic support for terrorist groups throughout the Middle East &amp;amp; Asia had a direct impact on international efforts to promote peace, threatened economic stability in the Gulf 
 12. Despite its pledge to support the stabilization of Iraq, Iranian authorities continued to provide lethal support, including weapons, training, funding, and guidance, to Iraqi Shia militant groups that target US and Iraqi forces. This is the result https://t.co/1NMw43ec9T 
 13. So spare me your apologist BS that we unfroze &quot;their money&quot;. There was a very good reason to keep it frozen. Spare me your BS about Iran&apos;s right to nuclear power, you&apos;re an idiot. Spare me your crap about Obama &amp;amp; the Iran deal. It stunk, they knew it stunk &amp;amp; went thru anyway. 
 13. Dec. 2015 - Iran Lied About Its Nuclear Program. A new report has debunked Tehran&apos;s claims about what its unclear program was up to. Iranians had falsified their declarations to the I.A.E.A. https://t.co/GI6TpDyHlz 
 14. Sept .27.2017 IAEA Chief: We Are Now Unable to Verify Iran is Implementing Nuclear Deal because there no means to ensure &quot;that Tehran has not engaged in activities that “could contribute to the development of a nuclear explosive device,” https://t.co/Npp49LaLnw 
 15. April 30, 2018 Israel intelligence Reveals a huge archive of stolen Iranian nuclear plans, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu of Israel accuses Iran on of lying for years about its efforts to build a nuclear weapon. https://t.co/fTOW8Ncdu1</texto><total_retweets type="int">415</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">544</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">28</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">248692627</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">2396</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3638</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">35367</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7409956875174015</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>