<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">120</hilo><total_tweets type="int">11</total_tweets><texto type="str">Everyone&apos;s heard of #FakeNews. Before it was called fake news, it was called #disinformation. The goal is to cause confusion and chaos, so people don&apos;t know who to trust or what to believe. THREAD 1 #RussianCollaborators #Propaganda #FridayFeeling #FridayMotivation https://t.co/PJXJvHi6x9 
 Disinformation promotes so much misleading &amp;amp; false info that people lose faith, give up. Disinformation is designed to weaken the enemy by discrediting it with lies and &quot;leaks&quot; of damaging &quot;info&quot;. Hint: the enemy is us, the resistance. 2 https://t.co/fQL7qIcbXw 
 Joseph #Stalin is credited with inventing the term &quot;dezinformatsiya&quot;, defined in the Great Soviet Encyclopedia as &quot;dissemination (in the press, on the radio, etc.) of false reports intended to mislead public opinion&quot;. 3 #ColdWar #Propaganda #Lies #misinformation https://t.co/Q3ZP4F3Rip 
 This past week, 4 of Washington&apos;s top experts on #Russia discussed their plan to combat #disinformation at a forum organized by the Atlantic Council. All agreed that Western democracies need to find &quot;concrete solutions&quot; to the problem of disinformation. 4 https://t.co/brooYfP56l 
 One of #Mueller&apos;s indictments stated that Russian agencies had a strategic goal to sow discord and heighten existing political divisions in the U.S. The Bernie v. Hillary divide was a great target. So was #Benghazi and the #email &quot;scandal&quot;. #5 #Unite https://t.co/wqEvtjOT6r 
 It&apos;s hard to measure precisely, but #disinformation has been effective. It&apos;s crucial that we talk about this tactic and educate people about it &amp;amp; how to spot it. 6 https://t.co/qtJiGMhsLi #TruthRevealed #FactsMatter #FactChecker #FactFriday https://t.co/XZ0o7zoqm7 
 So how do you spot disinformation? There are a couple of things to look for. Do your best to educate yourself about #bots, #Trolls and #sockpuppets. These are used to amplify disinfo &amp;amp; make the bots and trolls look like they have many real followers. 7 https://t.co/oZLTI58HM3 
 Some people create multiple sock puppet accounts and use tools like TweetDeck to tweet from the sock puppet accounts. This makes it look like many people are agreeing with them, making supportive comments &amp;amp; retweeting their content. As Twitter purges bots, those RTs disappear. 8 https://t.co/paxxBeazEl 
 The single most important thing is to USE CRITICAL THINKING. Question what you read, what people say. Ask for sources, then evaluate those sources - are they biased (left or right)? Neutral? Reputable? Check a couple of reputable sources and compare information. 9 #accurate https://t.co/KAnHPFuynr 
 People WILL target the resistance &amp;amp; try to discredit us. That means we&apos;re doing something right &amp;amp; making a difference. Observe &amp;amp; evaluate - what are their motives? Who do they associate with? What do they do most - cause drama, or educate, inform, promote candidates? https://t.co/hvUYcGfPEq 
 If in doubt, ask others. Get the opinion of trusted, knowledgeable friends. Use @snopes and @factcheckdotorg to see if &quot;news&quot; someone is sharing is accurate. Do a little detective work, and then share what you find. That way, we all help each other. #PSA https://t.co/e1TpOLITE7</texto><total_retweets type="int">1995</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">3267</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">120</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">24</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">815708250217840640</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">64892</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">32956</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">119855</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8720992184208249</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>