<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">66</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">Wow. After seeing Reddit posts last night re: &quot;austinbomber&quot; poss targeting Alex Jones, many anons believed it was a set up to bring down Q &amp;amp; truther forums. Now Q says FBI has opened a case on &quot;Q&quot; due to &quot;BOOM&quot; drops. Now that the bomber is dead, [4am news], is it over? https://t.co/KK0qOcxCR1 
 2. Looks like Zuckerberg and RT (Rex Tillerson??) met w/8 others incl 1 fmr IC Dir (Brennan?) to strategize plan &amp;amp; 4am Clown Media narrative/talking points. Q team still monitoring thanks to algorithm provided by @Snowden. Checkmate time? FB on last legs? Nobody gets free pass. https://t.co/5wkZGCswac 
 3. Q posts link to an episode of Comedy Central&apos;s &quot;The Opposition&quot; which mocks #QAnon &amp;amp; those who follow. Q warned us this was coming. They started w/Pizza Gate which, through mockery &amp;amp; conspiracy label silenced those covering. High-level pedos ARE real. https://t.co/T6X5ZMlDKn https://t.co/itBhKLpkXd 
 4. Some non-US anons are unable to watch the link Q posted. Here&apos;s the YouTube video of JUST the part where they talk about #TheStorm and #QAnon. https://t.co/U4uMmyyuht 
 5. Anons are quick with the memes...lol. https://t.co/l1WWTU3Rpz 
 6. Q has used &quot;RT&quot; before to designate real time. I&apos;m inclined to believe this is what Q meant (vice Tillerson). Zuckerberg was meeting in secrecy w/either Brennan or Clapper &amp;amp; 5 current mbrs of Congress or Senate? 4am talking pts uploaded via Secure Drop (owned by Snowden). https://t.co/ZOh9eyg0LI 
 7. I agree w/these anons. The bombings were DS FF to highlight Q as dangerous &quot;fake news&quot;. I had never heard the term &quot;fake news&quot; until right after @wikileaks published the Podesta emails w/all the pedo code. They are using the exact same playbook here to &quot;debunk&quot;/silence Q. https://t.co/l1Qh712xJm 
 8. Apparently some are still unable to view both links of the clip I shared to the Comedy Central &quot;The Opposition&quot; mocking #TheStorm and #QAnon. Here&apos;s a HookTube link. Hope you can see it now! https://t.co/1SdqFKADGq 
 9. Love it when anons generate these graphics showing connections between the news and Q&apos;s drops. The DS doesn&apos;t care who they kill to achieve their goal. They want to shut Q comms down. Must be over the target. (h/t @M2Madness) https://t.co/Y56OtRw46T 
 10. Love the anon meme makers! https://t.co/4UHpmKhWLp</texto><total_retweets type="int">3827</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">6289</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">436</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">9427572</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">133320</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14423</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">39842</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.993373408952516</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>