<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">78</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">Alexander Nix on tape saying Cambridge Analytica completely ran Trump’s digital campaign and then erased all traces. That’s pretty clearly against the law prohibiting foreign assistance in US elections. 
 “Did you meet Trump?” “Several times,” says Nix. “We did all the research, all the data … all the digital campaign, the television campaign, and our data informed all the strategy.&quot; #cambridgeanalyticaUSA 
 #CambridgeAnalytica has taken credit for “Defeat Crooked Hillary … you’ll remember this of course? ‘Crooked Hillary’ in handcuffs.” “You created this?” “Defeat Crooked Hillary, yes.&quot; 
 #cambridgeanalytica deliberately targeted Sanders voters to discourage them from turning out or voting for Hillary. “It affected the thought processes of voters,” says Hillary, rightly. 
 “The real question is how did the Russians know how to target their messages so precisely to undecided voters in Wisconsin,” asks Hillary. “If they were getting advice from #CambridgeAnalytica … that indeed would be very disturbing.&quot; 
 Alexander Nix says if US government asks him if #CambridgeAnalytica were involved he’ll say “none of your business… they’re politicians, not technical, they don’t understand how it works.” And anyway he’s “absolutely convinced” it’s “beyond their jurisdiction.&quot; 
 And now we’re on to self-destructing emails. Two hours later, they disappear. &quot;No paper trail, no nothing.”</texto><total_retweets type="int">521</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">689</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">28</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">56687115</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">27407</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1950</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">86528</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0344082107336539</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>