<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">396</hilo><total_tweets type="int">27</total_tweets><texto type="str">There are still many who tell me that they simply cannot see any connection at all between #Windrush scandal and the situation of EU citizens in the UK now. So I want to explain this in some more detail — I made some basic points here already: https://t.co/FCux0CXxqR 1/ 
 If you don’t just want to consider my view, look at this for example. But there are quite a few other pieces making similar points. https://t.co/w0DFrJhX8H 2/ 
 Wider context is of course this: the strategy of the #HostileEnvironment and the fact that its reach is continuously being extended. I’ve traced the tip of its iceberg here ... the evidence is overwhelming and there is a lot more. https://t.co/0wqhe6HeR5 3/ 
 Consider this, for example. This is just plain vicious and unacceptable. How could we ever trust a Home Office that behaves like this? https://t.co/qASXcEFV1Z 4/ 
 In any case the #HostileEnvironment has already reached EU citizens — there can be no doubt. From the significant increase in the number of deportations of the most vulnerable https://t.co/tqsUegbcEA 5/ 
 to stuff like this https://t.co/tsKK0Rc84X 6/ 
 Brexit will make the situation worse because the UK government decided to make us bargaining chips in the negotiations. I must be very clear: when @theresa_may and other politicians tell you our rights are now secure and we will be able to live as we do now, they are lying. 7/ 
 EU citizens in the UK will be forced to apply for settled status. That status means losing rights. And that is the “best case” outcome: loss of rights for which we have to actively apply...and pay. Otherwise we will become illegal — even though we are here legally now. 8/ 
 Many of us won’t get to that “best case” outcome, but will fall through the cracks before. There are many questions about eleigibility and having the right records. As simple a thing as a letter in the name could make this fall over if no care is taken. https://t.co/5ac1afIM7b 9/ 
 For those of us whose settled status application is reject I have particularly significant concerns because of the uncertainty that will cause, the potential for discrimination, and what will happen in light of this terrible move by the government: https://t.co/X15Nj6MsLo 10/ 
 And also because of this view @theresa_may has long since held. This is from a speech she gave as Home Secretary in 2013. For those who have their settled status application rejected this is a possibility too. Full text https://t.co/9BlcacPD97 11/ https://t.co/y6f0OhtrWO 
 Now consider the two together: deportation prior to appeal in an environment in which you may not be able, due to the changes to data protection, to ever find out why the application was rejected. That makes an appeal a thousand times harder. 12/ 
 For those who are lucky and “only” have to deal with loss of rights the story won’t end there either though. We will be placed on a special register only for EU citizens. Landlords, banks, employers etc will be required to check our status against that with a special number. 13/ 
 Special register. Special number. Special checks. Only for us. Nobody else will have to do this. .... Still can’t understand why this is worrying? 14/ 
 E.g.: EU citizen wants to rent a flat; there’s 1 other person who also wants to, not an EU citizen. The EU citizen will have to give landlord that special number to check against that special register prior to any agreement. Who will landlord choose all else being equal? 15/ 
 Now let’s look into the future. That’s where the #Windrush scandal link is the clearest. After 8 years, as per current draft agreement, we will lose the protection of the ECJ. That could well open Pandora’s box with respect to rights. There is meant to be an Independent 16/ 
 Authority, but we don’t know anything much about it. And if our status is not secured through the right legislation it could be changed at any point. #EternalLimbo anyone? 17/ 
 Then there is the case of children—not unlike that of the Windrush children, really. Not all will be able to prove their status easily, e.g. those in care, those whose parents perhaps didn’t keep the right records etc. Who is protecting them? 18/ 
 So, in sum, we are looking at a very large group of people. People who have contributed to this country, many for decades. They are suddenly being asked to prove their status. In an environment that is hostile and where the onus is on the person under investigation. 19/ 
 As much as I knew the EUref would result in a Leave vote I never saw this coming. Looking at it now I have no idea why. I was just very dumb. I should have known given May’s record. But I guess I believed there was a basic level of decency and humanity in this country. 20/ 
 I was wrong. That too Windrush proved. Because while there has been a big outcry, what has actually improved? More and more devastating stories are coming to light. https://t.co/ma9TmLFOqP 21/ 
 They all strike fear into our hearts because many of us have stories just like these in terms of past life and contributions to this country. All of it meaningless from one day to the next. Still see no problem? 22/ 
 Settled status, with all its pitfalls and problems as I set out (and those issues are only the tip of the iceberg) is directly paving the way to future problems. I have no doubt whatsoever that that is deliberate. 23/ 
 .@theresa_may is actively creating the next Windrush generation. But that is not where it will stop. Never forget that she is not fond of the Human Rights Act either. That will have implications for Britons too. If a government wants to replace a universal Human Rights Act 24/# 
 —who could possibly take issue with universally recognised human rights—with a specific British Bill of Rights ... well, good luck with that. It’ll end up with a huge pile of something like this. And yet more lives, yet more futures, will be negatively affected. 25/ https://t.co/gqmBHSTnlx 
 So how may more people will it take, UK? How many more destroyed lives? How many more stories like Albert Thompson’s? https://t.co/MXLMDNdKDC 26/ 
 On a day on which @michaelgove spun some disgusting spin about how open Britain is, how positive a change Brexit has already brought, the world is looking at you. It is seeing all this. Global Britain? Not so much. https://t.co/HsIDc8h42B 27/27</texto><total_retweets type="int">452</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">691</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">46</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">554648712</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">40096</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1523</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">49285</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1004371081551187</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>