<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">19</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">(1) Anatomy of an MSM segment: A: Present two extremes of a topic and pander to their differences. B: Hire &quot;experts&quot; to compete for camera time. C: End segment unresolved. It&apos;s too complicated to discern the right answer. Now, let&apos;s analyse this chemically. #mkultra #qanon 
 (2) When we are beset by two extremes, we end up with tunnel vision. This is fight/flght. It puts the viewer in a reptilian mindset. The drama, the music, the quick segments. This or that! Now the actors come in pretending to be experts. They are here to etract adrenalin. #qanon 
 (3) It doesn&apos;t matter which &quot;expert&quot; you choose. If he is attacked you feel his shame. When he scores a point you get hit with the same dopamine. This is the dark magic of the checkerboard. It&apos;s the confusion of light and shadow. The segment ends unresolved. Why? #mkultra #qanon 
 (4) The product is dissonance. The cabal wants you to look for the wizard. It convinces you the answer is far too complicated for you to solve. It urges you to tune in tomorrow. It has nothing to do with the news. Traffic, weather and sports are only there to give it validity. 
 (5) It&apos;s a set. Those are actors pretending to be experts. When you feel adrenalin and helplessness at the same time, what happens? Your neuro pathways remember the passion. It&apos;s a chemical boost to a helpless, unresolved world that&apos;s too complicated to fix. Programming. #mkultra 
 (6) You will find these 3 elements in every MSM broadcast. When someone complains about their dishonesty; look back at this formula. I bet they followed it perfectly. Their goal is to make you feel helpless while pumping your adrenlin. Snake charming. #mkultra #TheGreatAwakening 
 (7) Put yourself in the chair. Masculinity is toxic. Republicans are uncompassionate. Trump is a Russian rape menace. How would you react to a world where #LoveTrumpsHate is compassion? Would you be confused? Would you snap? #mkultra https://t.co/dHi78r0ASZ</texto><total_retweets type="int">22</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">28</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">10</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">4</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">947828772362956800</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">6225</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2857</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">26613</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8514713047595716</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>