<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">210</hilo><total_tweets type="int">17</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. Catching up on #Q post analyses: #QAnon had mentioned a reference to Deep Dream on Feb 18. Looking into it took time because it took 96 hours to process my 90 second video from this: https://t.co/BvnGCKATv5 into this: https://t.co/n1WMTAz2Qx - rather devilish! 
 2. It turns out that #QAnon had confirmed to us then that DEEP DREAM= TWITTER, &amp;amp; that it was related to the sudden loss of twitter followers that many of us had suddenly sustained very shortly after #Q&apos;s post. But what @Snowden had to do with it was a matter of much speculation https://t.co/Yve0xu6YfM 
 3. So, since then, #QAnon posted last Sat an interesting bit: &quot;Projection.&amp;lt;-----------------------------Attribution of blame outward Russia&amp;gt;D/HRC&amp;lt;------------------------We&apos;re supposed to think not DNC Twitter Bots&amp;gt;GOOG operated (not Russia)/Narrative &amp;amp; Political &amp;lt;-Google! #Q https://t.co/dIg7hnOdnu 
 4. So it appears that #Q was telling us that Google was using it&apos;s AI technology to operate the twitter bots, NOT &quot;Russia&quot;. But see next tweet: No. 5 #QAnon 
 5. So @prayingmedic had noticed a post that is very significant to exactly what #Q was telling us: An #Anon claiming to be a Google employee posted it on 4chan. It details Google&apos;s plan to use AI to push political narratives on social media! #QAnon Wow! https://t.co/CIw1Lsl9Vt 
 6. Then on Wed this wk #QAnon tells us: &quot;We have the algorithm. Thank you @ Snowden. #Q&quot; This has interpreted to mean that @Snowden was serving a white hat function in cooperating with #QAnon in the reveal of the Google AI algorithm being used on social media to censor speech. https://t.co/8AGDwxNm6h 
 7. MZ. = Mark Zuckerberg of facebook RT. = Rizvi Traverse (most think), Rex Tillerson (unlikely)? 1 former intel dir = wow! #QAnon is maybe mocking @Snowden having left a back door open here, some think. #Q is showing world they know about meeting and so, that plan will &quot;FAIL&quot; https://t.co/gnnaeiWHkg 
 8. So a lot has changed in a week&apos;s time, &amp;amp; #QAnon had told us to expect it this week. Only a little over a week ago anons were worried #Sessions would let McCabe skate, but #Q told us to &quot;trust the plan&quot; the eve before #McCabe was fired! Q predicted 3 &quot;booms&quot; for this week. https://t.co/gAQyw8CCfn 
 9. Since #QAnon&apos;s 3 &quot;booms&quot; predictions last week, now this week: Boom - McCabe fired Boom - Tillerson fired Boom - McMaster fired After Cohn&apos;d been fired he had told us previously to &quot;expect more&quot; - #Q 
 10. Last Sat #QAnon was referring to &quot;TRUMP ADMIN v2&quot;, version 2 of the Trump administration, BEFORE this week&apos;s changes. Was #Q posing the question as to whether Flynn maybe serving a role, &quot;know[ing] where the bodies are buried&quot;? https://t.co/VD0zSaYFWP 
 11. #Q predicted that rooting out the #DeepState friendlies would put them into &quot;panic mode&quot; granting that we may &quot;enjoy the show&quot;, the &quot;March madness&quot; show. #QAnon https://t.co/6Y58jzmIcY 
 12. #Q had told us on Wenesday that, laughably, #DeepState #FBI holdovers had opened up a file on #QAnon because of his &quot;boom boom&quot; statements. More significantly, Q predicts the Austin bomber&apos;s death 4am Wednesday, hours before he exploded himself in his car. Wow. https://t.co/LdN0jxJtjo 
 13. Illustrative of the #DeepStateInPanic #MockingbirdMedia LameStream efforts, #Q shares w us a video with phony canned laughter, phonier than the #Clowns&apos; &quot;anti-muslim&quot; video for #Benghazi coverup. They mischaracterize an anon&apos;s question as #QAnon&apos;s prediction. Can&apos;t even read. https://t.co/bkv4pSNLna 
 14. The above #fakenews hit on us falsely stated (to canned laughter) that #Q predicted #HRC&apos;s arrest in October. Instead, Q was clarifying that they were only keeping track of her border crossings. It was well worth re-reading all of #QAnon&apos;s Oct posts: https://t.co/ePdjfNk3Es 
 15. #Q refers to the extent of our government&apos;s corruption - bad! Many anons&apos; consensus re #QAnon&apos;s post here: FBI - mueller comey mccabe DOJ - holder lynch rosenstein State - hrc kerry Plus another 29,18,and 41 ppl respectively in those depts yet. https://t.co/sYnb5P1aDr 
 16. Rod Rosenstein&apos;s lawyer wife has represented: Robert Muller 3x James Comey 5x Barack Obama 45x Kathleen Sebelius 56x Bill Clinton 40x Hillary 17x &quot;Historically this indicates that the individual is a protected clown op&quot; https://t.co/agF7OrCDd3 #Q: &quot;follow the wives&quot; #QAnon https://t.co/YMwIitEaEu 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">34</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">77</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">24</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">13</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>