<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">285</hilo><total_tweets type="int">21</total_tweets><texto type="str">To those who believe we should roll over and &quot;accept&quot; the ref/vote... Do you know how democracy works? #ABTV #FBPE #BrexitIsPersonal 
 It&apos;s a PROCESS. Not an end product. You don&apos;t do it just the once. Remainers/leavers who insist we should respect the vote are either not aware of the threat democracy is currently under or they don&apos;t understand the concept of democracy. 
 &quot;You don&apos;t get to keep voting until you get what you want&quot;. Well actually that IS kinda the point. You want your vote to count. And you want your values and policies to be realised. 
 There are a lot of definitions of democracy. Just having a vote is the most basic level. The idea according to the Universal Declaration of Human Rights (Art 21) is that the elections should be &quot;free and fair.&quot; 
 Now you might argue a referendum operates on different rules. It&apos;s not one of those things you can keep re-running. But the 2016 was deeply flawed. https://t.co/mrfBHHLKvI 
 The EU ref was designed to be advisory. To inform HoC of the will of the people. Therefore a supermajority was not imposed, despite it being a request. It was never meant to force through a major constitutional change without at least SOME idea of what the impact would be. 
 Yet how can we possibly know what the will of the people is, if the information they made their decision on was flawed? It&apos;s like failing someone on a maths test because you gave them the wrong numbers to work with and now it doesn&apos;t match your answer sheet. 
 Yet here we are. No one has a clue. All the unicorn fantasy dreams have fizzled out. All the grandiose promises have boiled down to &quot;it won&apos;t be like Mad Max&quot; https://t.co/6gXnJ1q54Y 
 At the very least I&apos;d expect there to be more of an outcry that we were promised unicorns, yet the unicorns are failing to materialise. WHERE ARE THE UNICORNS AT?! https://t.co/zXDWLIucCc 
 But this is all part of the #Brexaganda we are subjected to. &quot;It&apos;s ok we never really wanted unicorns. It&apos;s all the EUs fault&quot;. Shifting the goal posts over and over and over again to justify the mandate. But if we aren&apos;t getting the unicorns how can there still be a mandate? 
 You might not care about non-UK cits. But what about the 1.2m British migrants where the majority were excluded from having a say in their own future. How is that fair? https://t.co/SOJ3uR0bAX 
 And lest we forget the role #CambridgeAnalytica and #Facebook has played here. Laws have been broken, foul play on a level most sinister. The turkeys have been tricked into voting for Christmas. I can never respect that. https://t.co/u1OjOLAhXU 
 Taking all this into account (including the deafening hypocrisy of &quot;respect the vote&quot; bollox spewed by eurosceptics who haven&apos;t shut since the first ref 40 yrs ago). How can you just shrug your shoulders and say &quot;oh well.&quot; It&apos;s your democratic duty to oppose it. 
 I mean people like Farage may have actually committed TREASON. Are you happy to just shrug your shoulders and say &quot;oh well&quot;. SERIOUSLY? https://t.co/V7SwsKT2is 
 But as a side line... I&apos;m not sure if those proud leavers have thought about it. What kind of image does #brexit create for the British People? &quot;We gave up. We&apos;re quitters&quot;. They talk about having faith in all things British (without an actual concrete way of doing so) 
 But it looks a bit lame doesn&apos;t it. Not a great slogan, eh? &quot;Britain... the place where it&apos;s ok to give up&quot;. or &quot;We HAD a seat at the table and some rich American/Russian people tricked us we&apos;d be better off out back by the dumpsters. Oh well. I guess we live here now.&quot; 
 *scientist stares at a screen and sighs* &quot;Nah. Sod this I can&apos;t be arsed. Someone may have stolen my research, hacked my PC, threatened my livelihood but I suppose fair&apos;s fair. I&apos;ll just give up&quot;. Doesn&apos;t look good, does it? 
 I will never stop fighting it. In my eyes #Brexit is illegal. Why would I ever accept it?! Democracy is a right but it&apos;s also an obligation. It&apos;s my democratic duty to oppose it. If you think #Brexit is still OK and you&apos;re gonna still get your unicorn then good luck to you. 
 If, however, youve realised that #Brexit is in fact the con of the century please join in the #Bresistance any way you can. Check out https://t.co/FGF6giVRQZ or @W_A_T_O_N or @InLimboBrexit for more info. 
 Most Remainers welcome bregretters. If you have doubts about #Brexit don&apos;t be afraid to voice it. It&apos;s important that we all use our voices. 
 With that said don&apos;t forget that all EU and UK/EU citizens can vote in the #LE2018. Make your voice heard! #ABTV #FBPE</texto><total_retweets type="int">369</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">983</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">41</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">10</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">943788254</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">10611</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">10617</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">156642</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8009874696220625</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>