<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">374</hilo><total_tweets type="int">26</total_tweets><texto type="str">Long weekend listening: Podcasts that are worth checking out, a thread of things to listen and subscribe to. https://t.co/97CurxJQ93 
 Lore: Haunting rather than horrifying tales, a remarkable experience written and read by Aaron Mehnke. https://t.co/t9QDTBm2IJ 
 Here&apos;s my review of Lore --the podcast and now, the TV series on Amazon. https://t.co/pemvphV8Uk 
 No Such Thing as a Fish: from researchers of a UK trivia show called QI (Quite Interesting). Amazing facts, weekly. https://t.co/O06DMJjqfg 
 The Memory Palace: each short episode is a jewel of writing and reading. Some will make your heart ache. https://t.co/Hcp7xL0hkE 
 Desert Island Discs: Someone noteworthy discusses their ten favorite songs. Archives go back 50 years. Wonderful. https://t.co/Wwf7wpVWkT 
 You Must Remember This. Seamy, intriguing, sometimes inspiring, insider stories from the Golden Age of Hollywood. https://t.co/F5V4FkPMzZ 
 In Our Time: A nerdfiesta every week on ideas that matter from dinosaurs to novels to events. https://t.co/9WsdktKuc1 
 Monocle: The Urbanist. Why things are as they are for city dwellers, and what it can be for problem solvers. https://t.co/BLvUkYzHsT 
 Pop Culture Happy Hour: So you can be as the unhip say, au courant about what the zeitgeist’s fussing over. https://t.co/TXTb0wDJUw 
 History Extra: A fantastic way to keep up to date on new books, ideas, and findings by historians today. https://t.co/ZLZnnHqdva 
 Intelligence Squared: Real debates; uncompromising presentations. Powerful discourse. https://t.co/04luHplWai 
 Slate’s Whistlestop: John Dickerson’s engrossing presidential and political tales. https://t.co/PO52ZhGhXo 
 The Guardian’s Audio Long Reads: Reportage/reflections at their long-form best, when you’d rather listen than read. https://t.co/S4PskTs6vu 
 Great Lives: Each week an advocate pitches a life as one deserving of being called great with an expert weighing in. https://t.co/1KQBasDYVb 
 Sinica Podcast: The many facets of a changing (and unchanging) China, from experts and observers. https://t.co/Fz77WAbSKx 
 On The Media: Beyond who, what, where and why, including the how of news and newsmakers. https://t.co/S6caCAAU3P 
 Slate Presents Lexicon Valley: For anyone who loves words, and the story of how they came to be. https://t.co/BBAFYZBNYD 
 Note To Self: The human dimension of technology, interesting people responding to interesting things. https://t.co/b24Rsmoeft 
 Welcome To Night Vale: 21st Century radio drama with a wacky, satirical slant. A rich, funny, strange enterprise. https://t.co/4ANfZQmpev 
 Stuff You Should Know: A dorkfiesta shooting-the-breeze romp on random topics. https://t.co/EkqEmpbLoZ 
 Radiolab: The podcast that got me into podcasts. The full potential of listening to stories on display. https://t.co/8XdHJmbDuC 
 Reply All: Because Internet. https://t.co/rGO3x1uVVH 
 Analog(ue): Because feels and tech. https://t.co/6zpwfQoriT 
 The Essay: Every week, a topic, and for every topic, mutiple essays by multiple voices. https://t.co/IQEwAUkc6a 
 Fresh Air: What talk radio ought to be like, but will never be, here at home at least. https://t.co/MdO0JgwpFW</texto><total_retweets type="int">17</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">86</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">36</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">4202781</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">173688</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2172</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">94094</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.2081393029845606</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>