<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">54</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. @realDonaldTrump #RedPill 10-part thread laying out prediction of how #POTUS will expose evil #Cabal &amp;amp; workings of #DeepState #Coup. #Memo will reveal #DeepState abuse of intel services, leading to exposure/removal w/in #DOJ, #FBI, #CIA, #Agencies (leave behinds), #SES, etc. 
 2. @realDonaldTrump Next, we will need to expose, remove, and try for #Treason those involved in the #DeepState. Their nefarious work doesn&apos;t stop with the current #Coup but is widespread, including more recent scandals (#Benghazi, #IRS, #FastandFurious) but goes back decades. 
 3. @realDonaldTrump Before the full #TRUTH can be disclosed, we must round up, arrest, and try for #Treason and other relevant crimes those involved with the #Cabal. I&apos;m unclear on sequence here due to need to manage the public (civil unrest will be pushed by #Cabal). 
 4. @realDonaldTrump It&apos;s still an open question on how arrests/trials will sequence. Will it be top-down (#HRC #Obama #Lynch) or a rollup...slow roll to #RedPill public ? It&apos;s challenging as #POTUS faces #CognitiveDissonance, #Tribalism, and #LSM that will do what they do...#LIE. 
 5. @realDonaldTrump I vote top-down, starting with the #LSM to expose and remove the #MockingBird. This way, #WeThePeople can hear #TRUTH from more places than what they denigrate as &quot;alt media.&quot; FYI, alt simply means TRUTHFUL, so just substitute that when this term is used. 
 6. @realDonaldTrump #Whitehats have turned the very apparatus that the #DeepState abused (#NSA) against them...we know where they are, what they are doing and saying, everything. They CANNOT hide. We&apos;ve blown up their bunkers and 12/21 stripped them of access to black money. 
 7. @realDonaldTrump I believe the #Elite #TPTB should be the first to be arrested, but there may be some need to roll them up from the standpoint of evidence gathering and societal #RedPilling. I hope it happens quickly! 
 8. @realDonaldTrump #UnsealTheIndictments Once we have all those involved...and it&apos;s a large number (~10K sealed indictments), the next step will be disclosure of the other evils, beyond the #Coup, that the #DeepState has perpetrated. THIS is the BIGGEST #RedPill to swallow. 
 9. The #TRUTH that the #Truthers (#JFK, #USSLiberty, #Agenda21, #Agenda2030, #GulfWarSyndrome, #OklahomaCityBombing, #911, #SandyHook, #VegasShooting) have been trying to uncover will slowly be revealed. No one has cornered the market on #TRUTH, so be open minded. 
 10. @realDonaldTrump I saved this as my tweet...to HIGHLIGHT the MOST IMPORTANT #TRUTH of all. We must know about &amp;amp; STOP the evil that is #PizzaGate/#PedoGate. This cannot wait as kids are suffering. #FranklinConspiracy, #Finders, #ConspiracyofSilence. https://t.co/49NxT1gO0N</texto><total_retweets type="int">31</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">46</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">14</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">45</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">749684424</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">3785</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3969</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">6802</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7780699304231409</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>