<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">369</hilo><total_tweets type="int">27</total_tweets><texto type="str">Campaigning. A thread. ➡️➡️➡️While we spend another day (what is left to us after chatting endlessly about a #RoyalWedding), thrashing about over the Irish border, Customs Union &amp;amp; Single Market, my worry is not about what sort of brexit is being presented 1/n #stopbrexit 
 I doubt many are aware of the types &amp;amp; how that has unrolled. My worry as a campaigning #remain er is quite different. It is about the nature of the way in which we campaign, and how we reach people. 2/n😎 
 Some examples 1) We regularly call ordinary voters &quot;stupid&quot; - &amp;amp; direct anger at them. 2) Gather together in closed forums, mainly on Facebook &amp;amp; agree with each other. BIGLY. 3)Identify what is good about EU for us ( I mean me) &amp;amp; think it good or important for you too. 3/n 😬 
 We talk about languages &amp;amp; travel and other things that we like - but that others find scary &amp;amp; overwhelming. 4) we have parties and picnics &amp;amp; leaflet a bit and go to the Pub. 4/n🙄😳😖 
 I&apos;m being cruel - I feel I need to. I have done all of these things. We do all of this with no self-awareness at all. We tell people proudly that the uneducated (usually we say &quot;stupid&quot; ) voted leave 5/n 🤨 
 There is of course a difference between knowing things, or not knowing them - and being stupid. We all know that. You can be incredibly clever and not be able to even read and write.6/n 🤓 
 Perhaps my time teaching asylum seekers really forcefully taught me this. I have lived amongst the unpriviledged. Though I still know I am of this &quot;elite&quot; (bad word - but we&apos;re stuck with it) that are lampooned by the #leave camp.7/n 😒 
 I was prompted to come back this topic by reading this article: https://t.co/soHCIXSZCU 8/n 
 I agree with much of it - we are still taking our cues from the same groups &amp;amp; leaders. They have more passion now, true, but they (&amp;amp; we) are still, IMO, talking, not listening.9/n 
 Of course few of us have the total compass of the activities of the EU, I would perform brain surgery poorly, I am neither trained nor qualified to be one, why would anyone expect me to be able to do it? 10/n 
 So why do we expect others to be able to adequately judge the EU? Even without reference to the lies? One truth that is now universally acknowledged is that the vote split on educational level 11/n 
 The truth about education is that it does one thing for you in this (unless your skill is in something relevant to the EU) - it teaches you how to analyse. How to debate, how to sift information &amp;amp; make judgements on the value of information you are given. 12/n 
 So it happened this way bc of lack of education. So what now? Probably he truth is that for many ordinary working people, (call them working class if you like that flavour, I am wary of it) they lost the thread on this thing somewhere about a year ago.13/n 
 They see #brexit as #brexit &amp;amp; why hasn&apos;t it happened yet? The #leave camp have that understood. We don&apos;t. We are still knitting hats with yellow stars on them. I know I am. 14/n😬🙄 
 It is not for the &quot;badge of honour&quot; of being educated that we should look to the break down of the referendum result - but to the inescapable fact, that the people more able to analyse, were less likely to take the lies at face value.15/n 
 I am supposing that we have this campaign to fight again. A look for a #finalsay to get us out of this mess. At the very least a need to heal the rift - we cannot ignore the fact that half the country feels this way. It is how it started to go wrong. 16/n 
 And we are happily listing everything that is going wrong - as it does go wrong. But too often from our own point of view. 17/n 
 For people in working class areas - EU is as relevant as a moonlanding - but just not as exciting. It is some weird thing with people speaking foreign languages, which they can see no reason at all to be a part of 18/n 
 They live in Huddersfield &amp;amp; go to Leeds or Manchester Xmas shopping once a year. That is their horizon. We are not going to change it - and why should we want to? 19/n 
 What we should be working to help them see is that the EU is within that horizon already - not something outside it. Not sneer at the horizon, or discount it as irrelevant. It is very relevant 20/n. 
 We can only reach the people who will be most hurt, by talking about things that are inside that horizon. Schools, food prices, doctors, housing, etc etc. Not Erasmus, not science investment, not going to the moon. (metaphorically or otherwise) 21/n 
 All of those things are being massively impacted by attempting to #leave. Those things massively impact on lives of working people. Need to reach them, making a case for why the infrastructure is failing. So that we tie up why it is relevant to every one of us to be in EU 22/n 
 Increasingly, we find the #lexit campaigners have been there before us &amp;amp; uncoupled the train from the engine. For them all of these issues that affect people are recognised &amp;amp; they are promising a different solution. 23/n 
 One we know won’t work. For us to connect the 2 again we already need to be talking about the issues as the most important. The price of your shopping, the school place, the poor public transport. 24/n 
 Also need to make the case for why we need migrants &amp;amp; why they are good for the country. Not run away and try to make some mash up to make it look as if we can stop migration &amp;amp; not be damaged 25/n. 
 To do this we need to start consulting the people we want to reach - &amp;amp; involving them, as we are trying to do with young people, where the same applies.26/n 
 Just waiting for the #Leave voters to die isn&apos;t going to work. Nor is assuming that people will join these dots themselves. 27/27 &amp;lt;ends 🐟</texto><total_retweets type="int">32</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">123</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">33</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">8</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">304852634</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">17079</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">18435</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">133028</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8037895499145579</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>