<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">222</hilo><total_tweets type="int">16</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. #QAnon told us #Parkland was &quot;was specifically organized &amp;amp; designed to DISTRACT&quot;. But, &quot;justice will be served&quot; - #Q https://t.co/R9ECDreYNZ 
 2. Last night&apos;s #QAnon posts reveal more about the #Clown social media #MockingbirdMedia connections used to control people. And, with voting manipulation, a &quot;Constitutional CRISIS.... TIDAL WAVE INCOMING. BUCKLE UP. #Q&quot; https://t.co/wqJQKf42Yh 
 3. #QAnon just now posted reference to the parallels between his posts last night, and .@POTUS tweets today. https://t.co/uSRrOCgsXl 
 4. WOW! The NYT is reporting that John Dowd, Trump&apos;s former attorney, has had discussions with Michael Flynn&apos;s attorneys about the possibilities of PARDON!! HOORAY! #QAnon #Q https://t.co/ZXELzgYTyd 
 5. Holy Cow! #QAnon tells us just now that the team&apos;s communication devices are under attack. The read-only board greatawakening is now locked or terminated. The attack source is overseas (best way to cover). Code Monkey locked out. Desperate. New board&apos;ll be up &quot;in 1-2.&quot; #Q https://t.co/65BtT60Ash 
 6. BREAKING: IG Horowitz announces DOJ to review &quot;compliance with legal requirements&quot; against FISA political spying abuse. #QAnon asks us: Think outside box re the timing of release being post-Facebook news, referring to #Clowns role with corporate technology to spy on us all. #Q https://t.co/NqE6UMQx5n 
 7. #QAnon (972, above) posts: @Snowden &quot;shine the light bright&quot; on this evil social media spy network so that it can be targeted for &quot;death on arrival&quot; [DOA]. Snowden points out that FB &quot;allows foreign govts vast warrantless access to stored data which can be sent back to U.S.&quot; https://t.co/tw0gshW6f1 
 8. With #QAnon suggesting we &quot;think outside box re the timing of release of the IG investigation of FISA abuse being post-Facebook news&quot;, we note ,@Snowden&apos;s retweet connecting the two: https://t.co/v63PW6zUzR #Q 
 9. #QAnon asks us to consider how our data is being used, &quot;used for what?&quot; He tells of Kickbacks &quot;BIG TIME&quot; to private from public, bypassing laws by going across borders w intel asset&apos;s across the globe in partnership to spy on us. Constitutional crisis? Magnitude?&quot; (huge) #Q https://t.co/xgSQ5IAs1y 
 10. After #Qanon elucidates the international cabal of social media spying on us &amp;amp; the &quot;role of search engine platforms&quot; in skewing results to &quot;&apos;weight&apos; elections&quot;, #Q asks us: &quot;Why is Obama traveling the world conducting high-level meetings? Use logic.&quot; https://t.co/EB3PRtZnZ5 
 11. Obama expanded the existing Senior Executive Service program of #DeepState managers and appointed over 7,000 of the 8,156 bosses who are called the SES in present gov. 
 12. #Qanon mentioned today Nancy Salzman Pres. of NXIVM whose cult leader, Keith Raniere, was arrested in Mexico. Her house is raided yesterday by FBI. They call their women “slaves,&quot; brand &amp;amp; coerce them into sex acts. Nancy teaches executive mind control. Big CF donors. #Q https://t.co/1woYyavTbT 
 13. #QAnon&apos;s mentions of #Salzman leads to reveal that more than a dozen contributions poured into Clinton’s coffers from NXIVM. Nancy Salzman is a Clinton Global Initiative member, membership by invitation only w min $15,000 donation per person per year. https://t.co/HN50UtTyy6 
 14. NXIVM (&quot;nexium&quot;) head Raniere&apos;s bankrolled by Clare Bronfman from whom they bilked the Seagram&apos;s liquor fortune. He&apos;s nabbed at $10,000/wk Mexican hotel. &quot;Developing new tools for human empowerment, expression &amp;amp; ethics&quot;, they had women &quot;in cages&quot;. https://t.co/h3BBo81ChS 
 15. #QAnon&apos;s last post (so far) today speaks to intel ops attacking the boards non-stop trying to convince everyone Q and Sessions work for the #Clowns. In #Q&apos;s case we are to believe that someone who calls them &quot;clowns&quot; is one? I don&apos;t think so. At all. &quot;FAILED&quot; https://t.co/DZELnLc6JK 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">84</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">125</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">29</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>