<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">69</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">#QAnon #GreatAwakening #TheStorm #OIGReport #internetbillofrights #InternetBillOfRightsNow (1) SHORT THREAD ON REVOLUTIONARY ATTITUDE. I&apos;m reading a lot of patriots say: &quot;I can&apos;t wait for the prosecutions to begin, OR for so-and-so to be released, I want to know it all, now.&quot; 
 #QAnon #GreatAwakening #TheStorm (2) My response is always the same: &quot;Are you red-pilling people around you? Are you informing them and conforting them when the information is uneasy to digest?&quot; BECAUSE I AM. ARE YOU? 
 #QAnon #GreatAwakening #TheStorm (3) My intelligent friends in Rio know all about Haiti. Know about the raids in SA. Know about The Standard Hotel. Know about fast and Furious, Benghazi. They know Mueller&apos;s probe is deception. They know that we TRUST SESSION, ROGERS, WRAY. 
 #QAnon #GreatAwakening #TheStorm (4) My friends in Rio know about Q-team, Q-clearance. Hell they know about adrenochrome and Bohemian grove. They Know the stakes of the game. BUT: 
 #QAnon #GreatAwakening #TheStorm (5) Do they believe me? Do they think I&apos;m crazy? YES AND YES hahaha In the beggining they heard me out of cortesy, but the INTEL checks out on an intellectual and operational level. So they&apos;re openning up to it. I think I fully converted one. 
 #QAnon #GreatAwakening #TheStorm (6) That&apos;s the greatest story of my lifetime. I have to be part of it. And share it with those around me. My elderly mother, so uneasy at some of the stuff. I don&apos;t have time to complain it takes too long, I&apos;m doing The Riddle Revolution. /End. 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll!</texto><total_retweets type="int">117</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">426</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">35</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">938139949710405633</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">38539</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">6586</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">39448</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9516930813158719</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>