<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">112</hilo><total_tweets type="int">11</total_tweets><texto type="str">**** THREAD ***** Roger Stone told me that he communicated with Donald Trump throughout the campaign in an exclusive interview and I&apos;m going to break down why that&apos;s important here, with audio and links. #TrumpRussia #TheResistance https://t.co/8dhAmQbfwt 
 Last May, I met Stone at iHeartRadio studios after a national broadcast with @AmandiOnAir on @WIOD. Fernand Amandi photographed us chatting and this is the interview. https://t.co/fQZaMxVLWN 
 Roger Stone&apos;s a dogged debater when you go off the topics he&apos;s interested in pushing. On May 1st, 2017 there was no Special Counsel and former FBI Director James @Comey wouldn&apos;t testify for two more days. So I asked Stone first about his role in Trump&apos;s hiring of Paul Manafort. https://t.co/eBpMh6Tg2f 
 I knew of Roger Stone&apos;s past business with Paul Manafort, and at the time it wasn&apos;t clear who brought him onto Trump&apos;s campaign. https://t.co/qIYNQW2jTM 
 Donald Trump fires many people, but never seems to get rid of any of them... especially if they&apos;re offering &quot;free&quot; advice. Roger Stone maintains that he quit the Trump Campaign, but he told me in detail about his relationship with Trump from 2015 until the election. https://t.co/r9Bjged3Yi 
 Last week, @NatashaBertrand revealed Roger Stone&apos;s DMs with @wikileaks during the #TrumpRussia campaign while @JulianAssange was busy strategically leaking Hillary Clinton&apos;s emails. https://t.co/hxPHKV6G2v 
 When you combine Stone&apos;s prior denials of any discussions with @Wikileaks with @NatashaBertrand&apos;s story and my reporting there&apos;s only one logical conclusion: Roger Stone was the campaign&apos;s back channel to #Wikileaks https://t.co/WkXXeYCVyG 
 Roger Stone&apos;s complete testimony to Congress is still confidential but the portion he released left his role with Trump open to interpretation. Stone was less forthcoming in subsequent interviews about divulging his private conversations with Trump. https://t.co/kBiL9iq2oc 
 The remainder of the interview was about Roger Stone&apos;s &quot;Stop the Steal&quot; PAC which he called an &quot;exit polling&quot; operation, but about which he could recall virtually no details other than operating in Cuyahoga County, Ohio which includes Cleveland. Stone never released his results. https://t.co/ASE1hzFarz 
 I spoke with Roger Stone for about six minutes, and he ended our discussion with both a tremendous compliment and a foreboding admission. https://t.co/wUbHojaLJf 
 This is probably why he will regret that. https://t.co/zGql59gJ8h</texto><total_retweets type="int">764</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1128</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">65</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">19422491</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">60227</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">9577</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">115581</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9595532473626968</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>