<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">349</hilo><total_tweets type="int">27</total_tweets><texto type="str">Adam Schiff Asking Carter Page Whether He&apos;s Invoking The Fifth Amendment Is Something Else. https://t.co/aNchV7MnTG 
 Carter Page appears to thinks the &quot;double jeopardy&quot; bar means suffering from &quot;extrajudicial punishment&quot; bars a legal trial. Or something. 
 Page on July 2016 Dvorkovich conversation: &quot;No private meetings&quot; &quot;I greeted him briefly&quot; &quot;a private conversation&quot; &quot;5 seconds to 10 seconds&quot; https://t.co/Jm8qhQvZ3e 
 You can basically hear Schiff&apos;s voice from the transcript; he can&apos;t believe what he&apos;s hearing. https://t.co/swmQAyWupJ 
 Carter Page On Why He Withheld From The Committee The Memo He Sent To The Trump Campaign About His July 2016 Russia Trip: https://t.co/pjYtoZkYIh 
 Carter Page has been interviewed by the FBI &quot;four or five&quot; times this year, he says. https://t.co/PnIzuD86HO 
 UM. DOES ANYONE KNOW WHAT THIS IS ABOUT? https://t.co/cvD2UBYKdc 
 [Page says something.] Gowdy: &quot;I hope not.&quot; Page: OK. [Gowdy says something.] Page: &quot;I know there&apos;s kind of overlap.&quot; Gowdy: &quot;I hope not.&quot; 
 Even Gowdy can&apos;t get over Page. https://t.co/cwP5dVNfQG 
 😑 https://t.co/JpNr9v7z27 
 jfghsksdhgf 
 Page believes allegations made against him are more likely to have influenced the election than efforts at interference by the Russian govt. https://t.co/oB0vUl7YiF 
 Seriously, read this. This is Trey Gowdy questioning Carter Page. 
 Shlomo Weber invited Page to come to Russia in 2016 after Page became affiliated with the Trump campaign. https://t.co/RkkRkZsPSg 
 This is what transpires, Marx Brothers-like, when Schiff asks if anyone Page met in Moscow in July 2016 maintained communications w him. https://t.co/ELcpV8Oj58 
 This is Page on a second meeting with the high-ranking Russian gov&apos;t official he first met in July 2016. https://t.co/CjzkhRUSMm 
 Oh. My. God. https://t.co/IXrmwUV9OO 
 In addition to the March 2016 meeting in which Papadopoulos talked about Russia, that group, minus Trump, got together again in June 2016. https://t.co/dXOUF6uIfe 
 Sessions was at this June dinner meeting. And Carter Page testified under oath that he directly told Sessions that he was going to Russia. 
 So, that&apos;s another Russia contact that Jeff Sessions knew about. 
 It&apos;s like, each conversation is more painful than the last, even when it&apos;s relatively mundane like this. https://t.co/5EId6TmA9j 
 &quot;And I&apos;m a Delta Sky Miles member, so I got, you know, upgraded to economy comfort on one way.&quot; - Carter Page 
 Oof. https://t.co/914kQagwHW 
 Hmm. What did Schiff do here? https://t.co/n69u4y8kTt 
 Lol. https://t.co/HC107EXfBS 
 &quot;I would include outreach as being — again, it was a general warm greeting.&quot; https://t.co/6ZYrug3HFi 
 *blink* I think I just passed out sitting upright on my couch, so, I&apos;m gonna have to end it here for tonight. Thanks for following along!</texto><total_retweets type="int">5599</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">17099</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">791</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">22891564</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">129387</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">5387</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">240762</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.080412603978394</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>