<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">113</hilo><total_tweets type="int">13</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. It’s Worldwide. It’s orchestrated, it’s organized, &amp;amp; it goes back DECADES Canada: aboriginal children who died or went missing while in the care of the ... church-run residential schools, the last of which shut down in the 1990s. @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016 #QAnon 
 2. Think. Why did they leave the school? Did they really leave? What happened? Appr. 150,000 aboriginal children were forced to leave their homes for the schools to assimilate them. some estimates, prior to the 1940s, mortality rates reached 50% #Qanon @realDonaldTrump 
 3. Think. Does this really make sense to you? “Although some deaths were suicides, most fatalities were due either to disease or occurred after the children ran away from the schools, then had accidents, hypothermia or drowned.” @realDonaldTrump #QAnon @fixurheart2016 
 4. “The testimony of residential school survivors is a litany of human depravity. Rape, murder, medical experiments, forced sterilization, and electrocution, among other things, were common” https://t.co/9x62opKJ3r @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016 #QAnon #WeThePeople 
 5. “To those few of you whose minds are still unfogged enough to understand, and whose hearts and will are still free enough to cause you to act.” @realDonaldTrump @Potus #WeThePeople 
 6. This report includes original field notes from the Mohawk Institute excavations, video recordings of the dig, and evidence of the bones and bits of school uniforms that were uncovered on the former school grounds. @realDonaldTrump #QAnon 
 7. BOOM! forensic evidence has now substantiated that the Crown of England, the Vatican and the Canadian government and churches are responsible for the death of more than 50,000 children across Canada. https://t.co/fT9nY1ZNFH @realDonaldTrump #QAnon @fixurheart2016 
 BOOM! BOOM! The Queen Pope Benedict. What I’ve known since the 80s: 9th Circle Child Sacrifice Satanic Cult, going back centuries. Watch. Listen. Pray. Repeat. https://t.co/JGGgxU8oyB @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016 #QAnon #WeThePeople 
 The Ninth Circle Satanic Cult, a child sacrifice group composed of global elites, appears to be routinely raping, torturing and murdering children. It has existed according to Vatican documents for centuries. @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016 #Qanon #WeThePeople 
 Watch. Learn. Pray. Repeat. Nobel Peace Prize Nominee discuss the trafficking and bodies found dismembered. Argentina, Ireland, Spain, North America ring discussed: https://t.co/QpI8TUAjjf @realDonaldTrump #QAnon @fixurheart2016 
 Kevin was re-nominated for another Nobel Peace Prize in 2015. Sacrifices occur around not only Roman festivals but New Moons. Mazy Shaw was sacrificed Christmas Day, 1946 This is a difficult listen. https://t.co/mewNP10H2H @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016 #QAnon 
 “Crimes Against Humanity in England and Canada and How to Stop Them” by Kevin Annett 30 minute address. https://t.co/zHNZzB5z3i @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016 #QAnon 
 The choice to know is yours. Links to eyewitness testimonies including sacrifices by priests dating back to the 1940s. Did you know? Did you ever wonder where all missing children go? Think. Watch. Learn. Pray. Repeat. https://t.co/vqpfU0yp5C @realDonaldTrump @fixurheart2016</texto><total_retweets type="int">93</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">81</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">17</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">838225775287414784</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">141</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">219</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">508</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.6439306305370129</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>