<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">356</hilo><total_tweets type="int">28</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. Another huge intel drop from #QAnon tonight - a night that #Q refers to as &quot;Night [2]&quot;. Last night #Q told us that &quot;@POTUS will be up all night.&quot; and to &quot;Pray&quot;, which, aside from my conviction in prayer, and my prayers, sounded a bit concerning. 
 2. #QAnon&apos;s drop last night made ref to a &quot;Traitor&quot;, after his revelation that someone had prematurely leaked @POTUS not being under criminal investigation. The anon&apos;s&apos;ve been abuzz as to who the &quot;Traitor&quot; may be. Mueller? RR? Hussein? #Q referred then to a &quot;Massive intel sweep.&quot; 
 3. Amidst the #QAnon&apos;s anon buzz, one posted a VERY interesting linked piece finding that &quot;UK intel services fabricated evidence of collusion in order to create the appearance of a Trump-Russia connection.&quot; w much more than the Clinton/Steele/Fusion piece. https://t.co/jYrYOWCxTT 
 4. Last night, #QAnon had revealed that both Page and Manafort were &quot;plants&quot;. Connected to #Q&apos;s revelations, the above piece by Vos shows how #Papadopoulos was developed for the task as well, by #Mifsud and #Downer culminating w ex-MI6 head Hannigan meeting w ex-CIA head #Brennan https://t.co/3ntCIrWnmV 
 5. #QAnon thanks us for our prayers. #Q tells of Night [2] tonight, last night said &quot;@POTUS will be up all night.&quot; Did last night&apos;s Mueller leak relate to the &quot;forced reaction&quot; to vehicle involvement, planes, resulting in military show of force projection? https://t.co/n0Jdlndh7Z 
 6. #QAnon suggests there is a silent war now going on, and tonight, #Q asks again that we &quot;pray&quot;. There have been a lot of &quot;accidents&quot; lately. https://t.co/f07ZoyDgBK 
 7. #QAnon opined on &quot;coincidences&quot; (as he has often) early last month as he gave a tantalizing clue as to his identity. #Q asks the &quot;c&quot; word again tonight in connection with all of this. https://t.co/bjDG95jlzY 
 8. Bad actors have the capability to hack into electronic systems on vehicles. &quot;This should not have happened,&quot; David Barnhart, a satellite designer who is the director of the University of Southern California&apos;s space technology and systems&quot; https://t.co/DsBqzG16GC #QAnon https://t.co/ouUyLFOC4t 
 9. #QAnon notes that Obama was in China last Nov, just after @POTUS was there. Why? #Q. https://t.co/ulf1wKl5AD 
 10. #Qanon had posted about Jared Cohen &quot;Coming soon to a theater near you.&quot; #Q has prompted the anons finding some very interesting information his #Clown role in our internet discourse. https://t.co/s3xbiQQ7X2 
 11. #QAnon&apos;s reveal prompted some at Wiki&apos;s description of Cohen where citation notes him as one of the &quot;architects of&quot; &quot;21st century #Statecraft&quot;. He&apos;s been a key player in the Council of Foreign Relations, and #Clown work at Google. https://t.co/7UcXp0UchX 
 12. Since #QAnon mentioned &quot;Cohen coming to a theater near you&quot;, revealed is a fact on sheet on him, revealing his work in many tentavles of #DeepStater control of what people write and read about on our internet. https://t.co/oFLS11T4XZ 
 13. Once #QAnon&apos;d tagged him, others&apos;ve highlighted @JulianAssange&apos;s @wikileaks intel on Cohen, who&apos;s covert role as Director of Google Ideas&apos;s heavily involved w #DeepState social media manipulation receiving #NSA $$ for Google to harvest our data, manipulate our search results. https://t.co/Khy3pSHDIB 
 14. #QAnon had told us (no surprise) that there&apos;d be a &quot;&apos;Conspiracy&apos; push to norms&apos; in response to his reveals. Just now, #Q responded to the New York Times writing about him and our Very Stable Genius President. &quot;Here we go&quot;, says Q. https://t.co/dO8gYmxYlS https://t.co/MzDgnmqBz8 
 15. Ha ha!! #Q now tells us that the New York Times even called the White House first before publishing their pathetic &quot;Conspiracy&quot; hit piece on #QAnon, #Roseanne, and our #VeryStableGenius President! &quot;Would you believe they called the WH for comment prior to publishing? #Q&quot; https://t.co/tu7IyD1UAw 
 16. #QAnon makes mention again just now of the string of US military crashes. Evidently, Fox called the WH for comment about this as well. #Q https://t.co/sMk9w0OSLI https://t.co/f8kyrS5xKo 
 17. OK here we go. Now we see what #QAnon&apos;s saying. Despite unprecedentedly whopping military budget, the #Clown #Bezos #Wapo&apos;s using the military &quot;accidents&quot; to claim there&apos;s no mil $$ for NG on border. We know #Clowns can crash vehicles electronically. https://t.co/oTsgmWbQ7M 
 18. Just now #QAnon gave confirmation of this by responding to an anon&apos;s mention of it. #Q https://t.co/Vk5JOFFCh0 
 19. #QAnon drop just now states that &quot;Pics will surface of Hussein holding AK47 in tribal attire. One of many.&quot; And that in response there will be a &quot;Net shut down. #Q&quot; https://t.co/3GR7ZHFOR4 
 20. #QAnon had warned of us Apr 4 of #Clowns, &quot;false drops&quot;, and something called #QT2810C, which we had no idea about. Now anon sleuths found where someone posted Jan 20 QT2810C supposedly as plan to use social media AI against. #Q https://t.co/dEr9Rd3Wjg https://t.co/3opu7iPR6A 
 21. #QAnon elaborates that in response to the pictures he just mentioned, that MSM will push the idea that they&apos;re &quot;Fake&quot;, but that they have &quot;Videos / backup&quot;. Nonetheless #Clowns in social media will all &quot;kill&quot; it to amount to a virtual internet pause, but - HAMMER on time. #Q https://t.co/EG3ygN7NHL 
 22. One anon asks #Q &quot;How soon?&quot; the picture will release. #QAnon responds in classical Trumpian/Sun Tsu fashion that &quot;We don’t inform our enemies of the specifics. We instead instill fear in them to make unplanned and disastrous countermoves. Q&quot; https://t.co/0EaLxExXZC 
 23. #QAnon refers to their full team at the center of command on duty always with much enjoyable in store to come. #Q https://t.co/AeNU4sqgAW 
 24. One anon complains to #Q that people wouldn&apos;t care about another picture of Hussein in Moslem garb even if he were holding a gun. #QAnon reassures why he thinks rather it would be of great interest. https://t.co/l8RhPcapEN 
 25. #QAnon reminds that we can understand 44&apos;s mission by connecting the dots via past religious leaders (re: Hussein).&quot; Remember, &quot;We have everything.&quot; and, &quot;They know we do.&quot; They are at &quot;RISK.&quot; #Q https://t.co/6mdMhxvdZz 
 26. I think #QAnon is exhorting us to remember the good progress we can expect now with North Korea situation, and consider what it could mean in that step of freedom from the &quot;Nuke stranglehold.&quot; The plan proceeds on a timeline. Can we think? Are we awake? Or .... #Q https://t.co/MtX4cjuniC 
 27. #QAnon Words of brotherly love between two patriots encourage and support our hope and commitment of good things to come, thinking how close we&apos;ve been to losing our nation and culture to the depravity that abounds. #Q https://t.co/5KEQR5VjLP 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">213</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">331</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">40</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">18</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>