<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">377</hilo><total_tweets type="int">26</total_tweets><texto type="str">Absolutely excellent breakdown by conservative treehouse. &quot;The DOJ FBI FISA request was for “Title I” surveillance; this is not some innocuous request for metadata exploration – the FBI said Carter Page an American, was a “foreign agent of hostile foreign government”, a spy. 
 “Title I” FISA surveillance of U.S. citizens is the most intrusive, exhaustive and far reaching type of search, seizure and surveillance authority, permitting the FBI to look at every scintilla of Mr. Page’s life. All communication, travel and contact can be opened and reviewed&quot; 
 All aspects of any of Mr. Page’s engagements are subject to being secretly monitored. This is an entirely different level of surveillance authority, the highest possible, and has nothing to do with FISA-702 
 “Title I” designation applied retroactively to any action taken by Page, auto-generating exponential list of people he came in contact with. Each of those people/organizations could have their communications reviewed, unmasked &amp;amp; analyzed with same surveillance authority on Page 
 Because consequences of this type of surveillance are so comprehensive; and severity to immediate loss of constitutional protection (privacy and liberty) so stark; U.S. Government, through FISA court, makes it very difficult to gain Title I authority over U.S. citizens 
 Comey allegedly signed three of the FISA applications on behalf of FBI. Andrew McCabe reportedly signed one and former Attorney General Sally Yates, then-Acting Deputy Attorney General Dana Boente and Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein each reportedly signed one or more. https://t.co/VCRKUl8VAx 
 Tip of the hat to @SharylAttkisson And @TheLastRefuge2 Thank you. https://t.co/3GAZwwvxKT 
 I dare say this is going to be an even deeper exploration of what else the FBI was hiding. https://t.co/SEkf7iceQR 
 Excellent breakdown of traditional &quot;title 1&quot; vs section 702 FISA. Very granular but for those looking for comparison, there&apos;s even a table. https://t.co/UmBdKnY91R 
 Here&apos;s Sharyl Atkinssons article. https://t.co/8LBUAw2aEB 
 Woods Procedures were named for Michael Woods, the FBI official who drafted the rules as head of the Office of General Counsel’s National Security Law Unit. 
 They were instituted in April 2001 to “ensure accuracy with regard to … the facts supporting probable cause” after recurring instances, presumably inadvertent, in which the FBI had presented inaccurate information to the FISA court.&quot; Yes that&apos;s what happened previously too. 
 “By signing and swearing to the declaration, the headquarters agent is attesting to knowledge of what is contained in the declaration.” 
 So... Despite Woods procedures, inaccurate information was presented to the judge? It’s incredible to think of how many FBI and Justice Department officials would have touched the multiple applications to wiretap Trump campaign adviser Carter Page 
 — allegedly granted, at least in part, on the basis of unverified and thus prohibited information — if normal procedures were followed 
 completed FISA application requires approval through FBI chain of command “including a Supervisor, the Chief Division Counsel (the highest lawyer within that FBI field office) and finally, Special Agent in Charge of the field office, before making its way to FBI Headquarters 
 At FBI headquarters, an “action memorandum” is prepared with additional facts culled by analytical personnel assigned to espionage allegations involving certain foreign powers. 
 Next, it goes to the Justice Department “where attorneys from the National Security Division comb through the application to verify all the assertions made in it,” 
 “DOJ verifies the accuracy of every fact stated in the application. If anything looks unsubstantiated, the application is sent back to the FBI to provide additional evidentiary support – this game of bureaucratic chutes and ladders continues 
 until DOJ is satisfied that the facts in the FISA application can both be corroborated and meet the legal standards for the court. After getting sign-off from a senior DOJ official&quot; 
 So are we to believe that ALL These procedures were followed religiously in order to get the FISA warrant on Carter Page? All went through without a hitch, using unverified information that even Comey called unverified? How? 
 Woods Procedures aren’t arcane rules that could have been overlooked or misunderstood by the high-ranking and seasoned professionals working under the Obama and Trump administrations who touched the four Carter Page wiretap applications and renewals. 
 And unless they’ve secretly been lifted or amended, Woods Procedures aren’t discretionary. 
 Now hadn&apos;t the FISA court turned down previous applications till the Steele dossier was used? So was this entire, elaborate, procedurally complex FISA warrant obtained using the dossier as it&apos;s &quot;weight bearing beam?&quot; 
 In past, when FBI presented inaccuracies to the FISA court, it was viewed so seriously that it’s drawn the attention of the DOJ Office of Professional Responsibility, which investigates Justice Department attorneys accused of misconduct or crimes in their professional functions 
 &quot;The Arc of the moral universe is long. But it bends towards justice&quot; – Theodore Parker.</texto><total_retweets type="int">2209</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">3944</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">158</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">879548970082721792</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">51217</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2940</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">38261</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0539169429458746</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>