<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">328</hilo><total_tweets type="int">25</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) Some takeaways from this thread. https://t.co/vnmEmxlYMk 
 2) The product mined by the Uranium One mines in the US is not weapon grade uranium ready to be put in nukes. Takes more steps at different types of facilities to get there. Those facilities in the US aren&apos;t owned by U1 or Rosatom. 
 3) We&apos;re in no danger of running out of uranium plenty of other companies doing the same thing in the US. Plenty of reserves available in the US for our need. We also have our friend to the north Canada with more than enough to fulfill our needs. 
 4) My point is to stop letting the fear mongers in the media make this out to be some major national security threat. It&apos;s not. 
 5) Now the approval of the license for U1 was conditional on there being no shipments of uranium outside the US without approval. If they violated that then they should lose their license at the very least. 
 6) The important issues revolve around political corruption. Were the Clintons selling their influence to help get the deal approved? How involved were they in the deal? Were there conflicts of interest while she was SoS? Was U1 a vehicle for tax evasion or money laundering. 
 7) Let&apos;s focusing on these issues &amp;amp; not pretend the U1 deal is some sort of national security threat. The End 
 8) When people talk about the strategic uranium Reserve I&apos;m going to assume they this. https://t.co/cOGI1cv0ga https://t.co/UJBenWzOKw 
 9) Same to assume the stockpile is mainly for nuclear power plants in cases of an energy crisis. This would be enriched uranium. It&apos;s not what the U1 facilities produce. If it would be for military use would also be enriched uranium &amp;amp; possibly some depleted uranium. 
 10) I don&apos;t think the DOE is worried out stockpiles b/c their trying to dump excessive inventory here... https://t.co/qzJl5zkb9V 
 more info on this... https://t.co/B1wZ0E42CS https://t.co/tcRjdh1btS 
 12) I had a feeling Rosatom overpaid for Uranium One. Now I have some confirmation. Hmmm.... https://t.co/TTOKeuKInb 
 13) Did you hear about the uranium bubble &amp;amp; crash? Nice for Uranium One to have found a buyer at the bottom of that crash. Hmmm.... https://t.co/DBUAyBMEJh 
 14) You know Democrats hate coal &amp;amp; push &quot;green&quot; nuclear power energy right? Hmmm... 
 15) Fun fact a Clinton Foundation advisor helped push a Uranium One deal in Kazakhstan in 2005. Witness said the advisor told the Kazakh reps that the deal was a financing mechanism of the Democratic Party. Hmmm.... https://t.co/XlvW2uU7RU 
 16) The one operational mine in the US (Willows Creek) is insignificant (&amp;lt;1%) to Uranium Ones overall production. Vast majority of mining is in Kazakhstan. https://t.co/s5F90TYHwm https://t.co/7liY49Npxh 
 17) BTW Kazakhstan is on the border of Russia. Like I just said Uranium One owns huge mines in Kazakhstan. I&apos;m sure there&apos;s no problem for Uranium One to ship uranium from their mines in Kazakhstan to refineries Russia. None whatsoever.... https://t.co/h5KeCQFrAE 
 18) But of course Putin likes to live dangerously. He&apos;d insist Rosatom secretly ship the uranium in from the little mine on the other side of the world in Wyoming instead. 
 19) I&apos;m sure Putin would love for Rosatom to lose one of their facility licenses, he&apos;d find it fun to risk future work for Rosatom &amp;amp; their employees getting arrested. Yes I&apos;m sure he&apos;d love an international crisis. 🙄 
 20) Putin could care less about Rosatom aims to start building Turkish nuclear plants. Take or leave right? https://t.co/fX0k6Dt9VE 
 21) Here&apos;s another project. But I&apos;m sure the investors from India won&apos;t might Rosatom breaking laws in the US. Won&apos;t effect this project at all...right? https://t.co/UUhCeuB6Mz 
 22) Look here&apos;s Rosatom 2018 procurement plan from their website. But I&apos;m sure risking all this is well worth it to sneak that little bit of uranium out of Willows Creek....right? https://t.co/LyGsTg9DXx 
 23) ....or wrong? Seriously just doesn&apos;t make sense for Putin to risk so much for so little. 
 24) I think we&apos;re looking in the wrong direction here with this Uranium One deal. Focus on Hillary Clinton ---&amp;gt; Racketeering, money laundering, tax evasion &amp;amp; maybe insider trading. 
 25) Note: IMHO Putin is rotten in many ways. Just don&apos;t think he&apos;s the focus for the U1 deal. The End</texto><total_retweets type="int">101</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">132</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">56</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">735147297856757765</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">13896</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">10421</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">38905</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8256200590016869</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>