<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">11</hilo><total_tweets type="int">9</total_tweets><texto type="str">#MkUltra should terrify everyone. available on the US SENATE website. Following tweets will outline horrifying details of #CIA ABUSE in the 50s. Governments are not beyond reprimand. They must be held accountable. @POTUS saved us all. #TheGreatAwakening #TheStormHasArrived https://t.co/sJlhKABCL4 
 Project #MKUltra was the CIA program of research in behavioral modification. Test subjects were not volunteers. They were unknowing US citizens from 86 universities/institutions. #QAnon #TheStormHasArrived #research @POTUS https://t.co/zjQ5L6cYfy 
 #MKUltra was comprised of 144 subcategories divided into 15 groups. Limited information is available, pieced together from financial records. Why, you ask? The CIA claimed “present practice [was] to maintain no records of the planning and approval of test programs.” https://t.co/8kRk5PrdP5 
 Can someone take a gander on WTF #bloodgrouping means?! #MKUltra #qanon @potus #FollowTheWhiteRabbit https://t.co/ccxMcj6PWL 
 The real issue is, if the #CIA was doing these behavior and drug experiments in the 50s, #WTF makes us think they just decided to stop? They think we are sheep. They are wrong. @POTUS gave us back our voice. #Qanon #TheStormHasArrived #MKUltra #RedPill https://t.co/rpHmPmIdW6 
 The #CIA also made a $345,000 donation to a hospital for construction, claiming to be a private donor. The government then proceeded to match the contribution. #taxdollars hard at work. @potus will get justice for us all. #Qanon #TheStormHasArrived #corruption #DeepState https://t.co/YAFGvPsWvc 
 In exchange for this $345,000 donation, the #CIA was granted access for 1/6 of the facility. No records exist for what the facility was ever used for. It is verified that unwitting patrons in NY &amp;amp; SF bars were drugged and tested “unwittingly.” #MKUltra #Qanon #TheStormIsHere https://t.co/TIv9gJ1dsE 
 Stated by Senator Kennedy: “...there are perhaps any number of Americans who are walking around today ... who were given drugs with all the kinds of physical and psychological damage than can be caused.”[page 16] #MKUltra #Qanon #TheStormHasArrived #CORRUPTION @POTUS https://t.co/qAkqYbEt98 
 Part of #MKUltra that led to its exposure was the death of Frank Olsen who was drugged with LSD by the CIA without his consent in the 50s. One week later, he “threw himself off a balcony.” Or did he? #Qanon #CIA #DeepStateInPanic @POTUS https://t.co/lIwyYf7YG5 https://t.co/exK9AMebCZ</texto><total_retweets type="int">113</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">89</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">18</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">19</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">941163760252866562</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">6064</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">6671</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">6561</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7841272883727834</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>