<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">17</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">THREAD: It’s hard to keep up with all the threats facing young children these days, but recent changes to the EPA are particularly alarming for children’s health: /10 https://t.co/CrzmtjF8AX 
 Our children deserve environmental policies that will protect their health. But @EPAScottPruitt is protecting large corporations and the chemical industry instead #BootPruitt 
 @EPAScottPruitt Here are 5 recent environmental safety changes that are threatening children’s health https://t.co/CrzmtjF8AX 
 @EPAScottPruitt 1. Pruitt has reversed a ban on chlorpyrifos, a common pesticide and known neurotoxin that has been shown to cause brain abnormalities in children #BootPruitt 
 @EPAScottPruitt 2. The EPA weakened standards for toxic metals—like lead and mercury—in our air and water. Children, particularly low-income children of color, could risk ingesting these metals through the water they drink and the air they breathe. 
 @EPAScottPruitt 3. The EPA is allowing corporations to release more pollutants into the air. Poor air quality can cause damage ranging from asthma to lung disease. 
 @EPAScottPruitt 4. The EPA is now letting chemicals go to the market, even if there are concerns about the risks of potential uses. Chemicals are everywhere—including food packaging and children’s furniture—and not fully testing their safety could have serious consequences for kids. 
 @EPAScottPruitt 5. The EPA announced that it would close an important office that studies the effects of chemical exposure, which could leave children in danger of being exposed to toxic substances. 
 @EPAScottPruitt Rather than prioritize big corporations, our representatives must do what is best for the health and safety of America’s children 
 @EPAScottPruitt Are you worried about what these changes could mean for you or your family? Share your story here: https://t.co/MsDMFo5WEj #BootPruitt</texto><total_retweets type="int">274</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">350</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">15</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1484990160</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">4302</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1188</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">8362</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.891683236654616</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>