<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">293</hilo><total_tweets type="int">23</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. #QAnon just now pointed out that it&apos;s only been 1 day since he told us April&apos;s to be a &quot;BIG month&quot;: Already we learn that Rod Rosenstein wrote secret memo to post-authorize jack-boot raid Manafort&apos;s home, realizing they violated special counsel law. #Q https://t.co/rZXyomnSy6 https://t.co/xy8N5NlN7b 
 2. #QAnon also points to it only being (less than) one day since he told us &quot;Border. Wall. Military start. BIG month.&quot; till we learn of the President&apos;s announcement on military&apos;s imminent border defense. https://t.co/w56FW0eAPt 
 3. #QAnon confirms suspicion&apos;s that today&apos;s shooting may be another #FalseFlag op needed for #ClownMedia &quot;narrative change on release of damaging news.&quot; #Q notes that &quot;people are waking up.&quot; Though shooter&apos;s name not yet released, evidently #Q knows her. &quot;Trace..[her] Father&quot; https://t.co/qFR2gKXcre 
 4. An anon asks if P = Pope and #QAnon puts [Pope] in the kill box [brackets indicate target or &quot;kill box&quot;] saying May&apos;ll not be a good month for the Pope. &quot;Dark to LIGHT. TRUTH. #Q&quot; https://t.co/Ev7wpHLVRn 
 5. #QAnon posts that &quot;[Pope] will be having a terrible May&quot; because &quot;those who backed him will be pushed into the LIGHT&quot; and that the &quot;truth&quot; will come out. #Q https://t.co/kA7jpx3k4y https://t.co/t0wY5ADGCZ 
 6. An anon asks how many are connected to the Rothschilds. #QAnon answers: The &quot;Chair&quot; serves the Master. Who is the Master? P = C. #Q Saying that the Pope is the Chair who serves his Master? https://t.co/a6OzUsim58 
 7. Re the #youtubeshooting #QAnon told us to &quot;Trace background of shooter. #Q&quot; #NasimAghdam was enraged over #YouTube&apos;s censorship of her channel. She was Iranian orig from San Diego, against &quot;abusing &apos;non-human animals&apos;, polluting environment, &amp;amp; promoting sexual degeneration&quot; https://t.co/JKlyi1eQu7 
 8. #QAnon had asks us whether it were a &quot;coincidence&quot; we get &quot;another MSM narrative change upon release of damaging news?&quot; (to #DeepState). Evidently the &quot;boyfriend&quot; story was #FakeNews. ABC reports that #Aghdam had no relationship with anyone at YouTube. https://t.co/466gWpmJYS https://t.co/YhILt5Dah4 
 9. #QAnon&apos;s suggestion that we &quot;trace the background&quot; of the #youtubeshooter reveals that #Aghdam was angry that #YouTube took her channel&apos;s revenue. She complained about receiving 10 cents for 300K views, despite her main English channel having more than 15,000 subscribers, https://t.co/4bSkMlz9qr 
 10. Pertinent to #QAnon&apos;s suggestion about both #Q telling us about archiving and the shooting, #youtubeshooter #Aghdam&apos;s media content is being rapidly censored across the internet. Here, she outlines her #YouTube rage. https://t.co/gDgS0rKlNp 
 11. Related to #youtubeshooter #Aghdam #QAnon had told us to: Focus on Father. 20 years. #Q All we know so far is Ismail Aghdam warned police #NasimAghdam might be heading to YouTube &amp;amp; hated them. Police called back that everything was &apos;under control&apos;. https://t.co/gTSVRK4KgE https://t.co/BCwSuSGkMw 
 12. #QAnon then dropped some very strange info asking &quot;Why is Epstein spending $29mm to bury the tunnels underneath is temple on Epstein Island? Problem. Phones were allowed in. These people are stupid. #Q&quot; Convicted pedo, Jeffrey Epstein&apos;s demolishing Orgy Island tunnels? https://t.co/dGTN1ZrKaC 
 13. Note that #QAnon said &quot;...underneath is temple&quot;. We wonder what is the meaning of the missing &quot;h&quot; followed by the capitalized &quot;H&quot;? #Q uses such literal devices intentionally to convey things not yet ready for explicit declaration until maybe &quot;future proves past&quot;. https://t.co/aezBFofCnM 
 14. After #QAnon&apos;s 1000th drop, w the &quot;H&quot;, it gets even weirder. #Q&apos;s next drop tells of &quot;Pure EVIL&quot; in context of Epstein&apos;s Island temple. He alludes to the 4 directional Princes of Hell after Pope supposedly told us nevermind there is no hell. #HRC https://t.co/UWa3sJpby7 https://t.co/hOs4QiAVvm 
 15. In #QAnon&apos;s next next drop he tells us that &quot;Symbolism will be their downfall. MONEY. POWER. INFLUENCE. The BITE that has no CURE - #NSA. #Q&quot; https://t.co/G60rTqrRJe 
 16. Next #QAnon drops that &quot;We are under attack. https://t.co/vTDjm5zXtE WAR. NO DEALS. #Q&quot; 
 17. Following on the above, #QAnon refers to a &quot;UK.ROGUE_FAILURE.&quot; but that @POTUS declined it. Looks like May went rogue &amp;amp; chose wrong side, but we&apos;re prepared &quot;at all costs&quot;. 188 exclamation marks = Poisoned Skripal &amp;amp; daughter to cover MI6&apos;s role vs @POTUS? #ReconnectJulian https://t.co/plRUT5NZMG 
 18. #QAnon then posts: Bunker. Forest. Blue. + ++ +++ APRIL SHOWERS. #Q https://t.co/o2W1Yskt4U 
 19. #Qanon post with the +&apos;s are represented by this say the anons:. + = Soros ++ = Rothschild +++ = House of Saud https://t.co/2sZ9QQqLSz https://t.co/LX8K6h3Lx2 
 20. #QAnon once again shows how &quot;Future proves past&quot;. #Q told us 4/2/18 of &quot;RR problems&quot; &amp;amp; 4/3/18 we learned about the secret 8/2/17 memo to Mueller post-authorizing illegal authority on Manafort - 6 days after the jack-boot house raid on Manafort 7/26/17. https://t.co/PBbbgmphAU https://t.co/CmSTUPWkfj 
 21. #QAnon&apos;s BIG April is panning out very well according to #Q&apos;s &quot;Future proves past&quot; so far! https://t.co/o9Fheabvdo https://t.co/Dg4SMbz6P4 
 22. #QAnon spoke of the April &quot;MOAB&quot;. Is #Q referring to what we learn today that the National Guard Presence is done through the respective governors through a Memorandum OF Agreement BOOM!? https://t.co/36b8punwKf 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll</texto><total_retweets type="int">213</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">230</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">43</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">15</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>