<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">165</hilo><total_tweets type="int">11</total_tweets><texto type="str">A Thread for Men: When your #woman is #emotional, #crying or #stressed out, do not hold it against her. One of the lies of #feminism is that men and women are the same, including that we should process #emotions the same way. Reject the lie. Listen and learn in the posts below. 
 #Women have much greater #hormonal fluctuations each month than #men do. Simply put, a woman&apos;s thought life and #emotions are more prone to high highs, and low lows. This isn&apos;t a &quot;design flaw&quot; but rather how #God made a #woman to be in touch with the needs of small #children. 
 Nothing is more short-sighted as a #man than viewing a #woman as an &quot;overly emotional&quot; or &quot;flawed&quot; version of a man&apos;s thought process or #emotions. A woman that does not let her emotions out will become very #passiveaggressive, #depressed or #angry. Your job is to be an #outlet. 
 How can you be a #refuge for your #woman&apos;s #emotions? First and foremost, do not be dismissive of her #feelings. They may seem excessive from a man&apos;s standpoint, but they are very real to her. Withhold any #critiquing or desire to immediately solve her #problems. 
 The most effective way to be a refuge for a woman is to hold her in your arms, her head against your chest. Cradle her as you would a small child. Cup the back of her head and pull it into your warmth. This is extremely soothing. Listen actively to what she is sharing. 
 When comforting her, say the following in a soft voice: - &quot;It is okay.&quot; - &quot;I&apos;ve got you.&quot; - &quot;You&apos;re safe.&quot; Short phrases of affirmation let her know you&apos;re still listening, without interrupting her flow of thoughts and feelings. She&apos;ll let you know when she&apos;s done. 
 Let her rest on your chest and continue to hold her until she thanks you. She will show her appreciation for being her Rock, her Oak Tree. Do not feel obliged to help offer solutions to her problems unless she asks for your input. This is key. 
 If she wants your help, she can ask for it. Alternatively, later that day or the following day when she&apos;s feeling better, you can prompt her to see if she would like your advice. The comfort you gave her when she was feeling down will make her more prone to listen to your input. 
 A #man that #masters this skill will build #intimacy with his #woman, and will drastically reduce #fights. Write down the advice above and apply it until it becomes second nature to you. Be that #masculine man she needs you to be. 
 This is what she needs. You can give a woman a sense of deep calm and peace, and it also gives you a sense of being a force for good in her world. https://t.co/QyVCCbnMcH 
 Trap her in your warm masculine energy, let her know her heart is safe in your arms. ❤️</texto><total_retweets type="int">37</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">108</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">19</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">24</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">919470041770242048</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">102</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">149</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">1592</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.6337466591887636</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>