<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">138</hilo><total_tweets type="int">15</total_tweets><texto type="str">Tweet storm on how India has built a worse manipulation engine for elections than Cambridge Analytica 
 When #Facebook allowed third parties to colonise your relationship with them, they corrupted the purpose for which you and Facebook came together https://t.co/eUijtKwJEx 
 One such third party, Cambridge Analytica, corrupted your relationship with your government by destroying your right to free choice https://t.co/wf5qhOEVXm 
 @rsprasad is worried that efforts are on to influence India&apos;s electoral process through undesirable means and says they will neither be tolerated, nor be permitted https://t.co/DwpkUN3b8M 
 @rsprasad asks &quot;My question to Congress party is whether to win elections, Congress will depend on data manipulation and theft of data&quot; https://t.co/VTsFbtNixY 
 In 2009 @MD_Nalapat and I pointed out how third parties corrupted free and fair elections using spreadsheets that destroyed the votes cast in EVMs https://t.co/lECCgy9yX9 
 @Swamy39 approached the court to get voter verified paper trail https://t.co/izscHwG9QK 
 The Supreme Court has directed that VVPAT be ready for 2019 polls https://t.co/8VY7tlua6Y 
 However the UIDAI, and its ecosystem for #Aadhaar, is the new third party colonising elections 
 By linking #Aadhaar to EPIC genuine voters will be replaced by the ghosts and duplicates from Aadhaar&apos;s uncertified, unverified, unaudited database that can&apos;t distinguish citizens from residents or identify anyone https://t.co/QY61VEdbCp 
 By selectively causing #Aadhaar authentication to fail for genuine persons to receive benefit and services, the new colonisers will selectively cause opinion swing to vote in their candidates 
 By selectively switching on or off #Aadhaar the colonisers can even disenfranchise voters to ensure the victory of their candidates 
 We the people are no longer sovereign when the databases that protect the sovereignty, democracy and republic of our country are now colonised, corrupted and destroyed by the ecosystem of #Aadhaar 
 Cambridge Analytica is obsolete. The Trojan horse called #Aadhaar is the tool of the new colonisers to influence India&apos;s electoral process through undesirable means. @rsprasad why is it being be tolerated and permitted? 
 @MD_Nalapat agrees that knowing well that #Aadhaar goes beyond theft of data to destruction of sovereignty, democracy and republic of India, shouldn&apos;t @rsprasad launch an immediate judicial investigation supported by the CBI into UIDAI and its ecosystem?</texto><total_retweets type="int">506</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">428</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">35</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">17733956</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">2774</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">708</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">14690</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8942039276415109</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>