<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">181</hilo><total_tweets type="int">16</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ NEW INVESTIGATION: Former Tesla safety experts say production demands often trumped safety at the car company’s factory. Here’s what reporters @willCIR and @alyssajperry dug up: https://t.co/sojyThHgjJ 
 2/ Tesla, led by Elon Musk, is worth about $50 billion. It employs around 10,000 workers in Fremont, California. https://t.co/3B312O4Mii 
 3/ Under fire for mounting injuries, Tesla recently touted a sharp drop in its injury rate for 2017, which it says came down to meet the auto industry average of about 6.2 injuries per 100 workers. https://t.co/pHnwSDfQ1W 
 4/ But as @willCIR and @KQED’s @alyssajperry found, things are not always as they seem at Tesla. In fact, their reporting shows that Tesla has failed to properly count worker injuries, which makes their stats look better than they actually are. 
 5/ Here’s how it works: Employers are required by law to log workplace injuries that result in job restrictions, time off or medical treatment. Logging is not required if the employee’s injury is classified as a personal medical issue or a minor incident requiring only first aid. 
 6/ Which leads to cases such as Tarik Logan’s ... https://t.co/qLv8cuP6Ht 
 7/ How could this happen? Former Tesla safety personnel say there’s a fundamental problem there. https://t.co/5CTo8Zecbu 
 8/ Another part of the company’s culture that frustrated White? CEO Elon Musk’s purported distaste for the color yellow. https://t.co/m9vkB79WU6 
 9/ Other safety-related things Elon Musk reportedly didn’t like, either: *Too many signs on the factory floor. *The beeping sounds forklifts make when they back up. 10/ Few dared confront Musk about these issues, though. Why? They were afraid to. https://t.co/QyYONY07Y0 
 11/ We brought all this stuff to Tesla for comment. In response, Chief People Officer Gaby Toledano questioned the motives of our sources. 
 12/ Tesla said it records injuries accurately. They also point to an internal survey that they say found 82% of employees believe the company is committed to their health, safety and wellbeing. 
 12/ Right before this story was published, Tesla issued a fiery statement that accused us of being an “extremist organization.” 👇👇 https://t.co/bGfZNNIPmC 
 13/ SICK BURN, TESLA!!! But quick question ... How many extremist orgs are this well-decorated for their independent, nonprofit journalism? https://t.co/jApMuLRTTr 
 14/ Whoops! Left a few out. They didn’t all fit in that first tweet. https://t.co/nyi0MqS8E5 
 15/ This story is but one in an ongoing look at workers and power in Silicon Valley. Hear this week’s hourlong episode: https://t.co/MWpv59ZZop 
 16/ And if you liked this story, be sure to sign up for The Weekly Reveal newsletter: https://t.co/y5B7mmuzcm</texto><total_retweets type="int">107</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">307</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">41</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1726074810</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">68152</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">604</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">25465</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.2781061964043554</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>