<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">399</hilo><total_tweets type="int">29</total_tweets><texto type="str">1 We have seen the TRP hungry Tapori media, Clueless Spokies and You Tubers speaking on #CambridgeAnalytics all these people are Non-Technical and no nothing about DATA This long Thread expose @incindia &amp;amp; @RahulGandhi with #CambridgeAnalytics I will be slow in Twitting https://t.co/coej6Em7UN 
 2 In one of my article in Jan 2016, I did explain the power of Social Media over MSM. Read this Article again https://t.co/WS1MD1wiPf 
 3 2013/14 @narendramodi Ji know the power of SM where as @incindia laughed on it Today @INCIndia is serious about SM and @BJP4India losing the catch from an organization point of view. With a non functional IT/SM cell at BJP 
 4 Before i go into #CambridgeAnalytics Few important point 1 Facebook, Twitter, WA, google etc are not charitable companies. They need to make money. They offer U their platform free bcoz they make money from Advert and DATA. 2 ppl who were dancing Naked on Aadhar, where r u? 
 5 As a professional in same space, I 100% agree with @buzzindelhi that #CambridgeAnalytics tools are among the best in world. DATA Crunching is no Crime Data Analytics &amp;amp; Astrology if done correctly can pin point events 
 6 So what is #CambridgeAnalytics Crime? 1. Use of GIRLS to blackmail people 2. Using Personal Chat history to expose ppl and silence them on Social Media. Using DATA as a decision-making Tool is no crime. The world is driven by DATA 
 7 If @incindia or any party use DATA to understand voting patterns, Caste analytics, Local issues etc, no harm. I use Analytics for election results Problem is when @RahulGandhi PIDIs start posting personal chats on SM via fake handles created by Prashant Kishor 2 silence ppl 
 8 #CambridgeAnalytics was formed in 2014. The domain was registered on 1/04/2014 with these 3 key people Alexander Nix (CEO) Robert Mercer (investor) Steve Bannon (vice president, former) CA is heavily funded by &quot;hedge-fund&quot; billionaire Robert Mercer and it is a SCL Group Co https://t.co/39PR4IPVZj 
 9 SCL Group provides data, analytics and strategy to governments and military organizations worldwide. SCL expanded into military and political arenas. It became known for alleged involvement &quot;in military disinformation campaigns to social media branding and voter targeting&quot; https://t.co/szEfGtfCpL 
 10 Robert Mercer, the investor in #CambridgeAnalytics he studied at University of Illinois and was Co-CEO of Renaissance Technologies, an old US Hedge Fund company @sampitroda also studied &amp;amp; from Illinois https://t.co/MQUr9nQtkH 
 11 Now the first link is established #CambridgeAnalytics was funded by Robert Mercer who was Co_CEO of Renaissance Technologies (rentec), he linked to SCL Group Rentec old Hedge fund company and CA was formed by SCL Group for US election in 2014 
 12 In July 2014 Renaissance Technologies was included in a larger investigation undertaken by Carl Levin and the Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations on tax evasion by wealthy individuals. https://t.co/MwZ2BANsd0 
 13 Earlier today I challenged KC Tyagi when i saw his statement on media that his SON &amp;amp; His company OVLENO had nothing to do with CA Amrish, KC Tyagi son was India Head of SCL Group, the father of #CambridgeAnalytics https://t.co/NafEpU6FMU 
 14 Amrish Tyagi worked at Trump War Room. He is a successful person. The question is when OVLENO was doing so well why this company is not &quot;STRIKE-OFF&quot; category at RoC? If he was Technical so good why Infra company director? Was he just a POLITICAL BROKER? https://t.co/zQc8cTLhyY 
 15 As per RoC info Amrish Tyagi company OVLENO was registered in 2010 BUT its web domain was registered in 2016. WHY? Was OVLENO just a shell company before 2016???? https://t.co/n309mURXHN 
 16 Alexander Nix met @rahulgandhi and others during India Visit. Nix is well connected with Robert Mercer the Investor in #CambridgeAnalytics and CA is SCL Group company. Robert is known well in political circle and the BOMB. @sampitroda SON Salil Pitroda worked with FACEBOOK 
 17 The full circle from @RahulGandhi to #CambridgeAnalytics to #facebook @sampitroda son SALIL was Deal Lead and Corporate Development at Facebook from June 2013 to August 2014 in the Social Networking business CA was formed in April 2014 https://t.co/P8qhmpyQcZ 
 18 Salil son of @sampitroda who is organizing @RahulGandhi comedy talk show all over world worked in hedge fund unit of Citigroup in Manhattan. HEDGE FUNDS and King of Hedge Funds is &quot;ROBERT MERCER&quot; who is well known to NIX of #CambridgeAnalytics https://t.co/KsQ5iF6Yqi 
 19 Ref to tweet no 13 Some @RahulGandhi PIDI like @rssurjewala says that JDU is NDA partner. So BJP Involved Some one tell this joker that JDU was not in NDA till early 2017. Also KC Tyagi was against joining NDA till 2017 
 20 So now @RahulGandhi, NIX, Robert Mercer, @sampitroda via SON SALIL, #CambridgeAnalytics and Facebook all are linked In tweet no 8 i highlighted &quot;HEDGE FUNDS&quot; meaning Financial Market Now let talk about Indian Stock Mkt 
 21 There was a news that Tyagi company is paid via NGO etc. this need Investigation BUT @sampitroda is Director of The International Engineering Consortium, a Non Profit co which gives funds for research etc https://t.co/DNZEsCSF2k 
 22 Since in #CambridgeAnalytics scam of @RahulGandhi financial investment companies are also linked, it is important to share another info in relation to Indian Stock Mkt and @PChidambaram_IN @arunjaitley 
 23 Remember when @RahulGandhi went for dinner at Chinese embassy? There was a guy by the name Jonathan SEED. Mr SEED is a Political Broker in financial space #CambridgeAnalytics 
 24 Mr SEED was tasked to invest in Indian PSU and big companies via SHELL Companies using P-Notes. P-Notes are difficult to track. The investment size is few thousand Cr @Swamy39 Sir can explain P-Notes better 
 25 and when the stock Mkt shoot up, suddenly pull out all investment which will crash Indian Stock Market. Was this planned by @PChidambaram_IN? Schedule time was June-July 2018 but seems it is now postponed after October and before December 2018. My guess would be DIWALI 
 26 DIWALI bcoz that time most Hindus do Lakshmi Pujan, A sudden crash will hit @narendramodi ji and in a single stroke, discredit can be booked on Modi ji for failed economics policies 
 27 I may disagree respectfully with @Swamy39 sir on various issues but one thing is sure he should get proper backing of the @narendramodi govt on @PChidambaram_IN case, a free hand bcoz if u let lose LUNGI, he will create Financial Tsunami for sure 
 28 Last TWEET in this thread for now. A message to all on SM Use FB, WA, Twitter but never use chats for planning hit job on anyone, No abuse, XXX pictures Someone Somewhere reading it 😂 @incindia want to pitch RW ppl against each other &amp;amp; Blackmail to silence us Jai Hind 
 29 Sorry my last tweet in this thread is to our own Global Comdian @RahulGandhi, His PIDIs, @sampitroda and @incindia MAZA AAYA? https://t.co/jPVJit80Br</texto><total_retweets type="int">8192</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">8834</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">183</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">74433034</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">178375</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">5</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">160903</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">2.953256321536303</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>