<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">76</hilo><total_tweets type="int">8</total_tweets><texto type="str">Thinking of @JulianAssange and how badly Hillary still wants him dead. Write to him. 
 “I was so ticked at him. Until I realized where he was headed..” #ReconnectJulian https://t.co/4bmNsbgz2G 
 https://t.co/bSuE0kmQO7 
 Julian Assange has never had to retract a single story as #FakeNews. #Wikileaks has won every single court case that challenged their information. Every. Single. One. NO mainstream media network can ever say that. #ReconnectJulian 
 A corrupt media establishment is more dangerous —IMO— than having corrupt government. Hell, they ARE the government. Their silence on Julian’s torture tells all. #ReconnectJulian 
 The publications Julian Assange has given us (undeservedly) have lifted the veil of corruption so high that journalists everywhere should thank him for giving them an endless amount of information to write about and inform the public about. 
 Unfortunately, most of those “journalists” would rather turn their cheek and fill the void of Julian’s presence with even more corruption, even if they have to make it up along the way. That’s incredibly sad. 
 You don’t have to like Julian. But know this: No one has come close to publishing what he has published, and NO ONE has EVER protected their sources like #Wikileaks has. Have you ever blown the whistle? If so, support him now. #ReconnectJulian</texto><total_retweets type="int">400</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">869</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">28</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">466183294</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">33169</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">6307</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">104356</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9418432265816142</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>