<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">319</hilo><total_tweets type="int">21</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. NAFTA and The Stock Market timing... https://t.co/UhXEn79C6P 
 2. There are trillions at stake. Unfortunately for the Multinationals (corporations and banks), they don&apos;t have a seat at the table. Trump, and the U.S. trade team are independent. https://t.co/5si26hArnO 
 3. The decision has ultimately been determined. The &quot;if&quot; was always about the economics of the issue; the U.S. is simply far better off without it. The &quot;when&quot; to announce is a political decision. 
 4. But for those multinational corporations and multinational banks, there must be a great deal of frustration. The &apos;globalists&apos;, per se&apos; don&apos;t have influence upon this White House. Long-term, there are trillions at stake. https://t.co/8R1Fg4ATHp 
 5. So, if you were one of these global financial institutions what could you do? https://t.co/pDqtUa8JHM 
 6. Well, it’s pretty much a certainty that a rapid pullout from NAFTA would have a noteworthy negative effect on the Stock Market, at least in the short term. Most good analysts agree around 7% drop immediately, with a +15% rebound after a year as the benefits show up. https://t.co/gdmAFhtwpO 
 7. Not a problem, with the DOW sitting at record highs over 24,000. But what if the DOW were pushed down – way down – in a violent fashion that instilled fear in the hearts of many retail investors? https://t.co/3gmkrzeEj7 
 8. Would President Trump be so bold as to make a withdrawal announcement NAFTA then? https://t.co/cVUGEAT1x7 
 9. Despite the pundits trying to explain why the market has shifted violently with nothing but good economic news coming in, have you really been convinced investors are now breathlessly chasing &amp;lt; 3% interest? https://t.co/LWrYMKshcs 
 10. What if a market move such as this could be fairly easily pulled off (if you had tangible influence) using algorithmic traders (Market Makers) like VIRTU placing bids and making offers on huge volume, and executing orders on massive ETFs even after hours. https://t.co/snJiM87Svz 
 11. What if these Market Makers could promise a client anonymity as well? Well they do, and arguably they just did.... https://t.co/bo8DSbfosS 
 12. The question now is, WHO is it doing the bidding? https://t.co/kyCGd9nEg5 
 13. Melissa Hodgman was promoted to Associate Director of the SEC’s Enforcement Division by President Obama late in 2016. 
 14. Mrs. Melissa Hodgman is married to an increasingly well known FBI official. https://t.co/JBVvYEitdY 
 15. Nah... all just coincidences, I&apos;m sure. https://t.co/35qGryplyp https://t.co/c9VvQ1zYi4 
 16. I mean, seriously. C&apos;mon... it&apos;s not like the deep state is real or anything. Sheesh. Tin foil much? https://t.co/LQYazeGTO1 
 17. Next we&apos;ll be thinking that multinational corporations and banks conduct meetings with DC politicians to write legislation, and sculpt outcomes favorable to their financial interests. Good grief.... can you imagine? https://t.co/IjAcV20boi 
 18. I mean it&apos;s not like these &quot;trillions at stake&quot; would lead to spending billions on purchased political outcomes, right? https://t.co/mNGERGGVq6 
 19. Good grief. Would the Wall Street Multinational financial class really be so duplicitous as to attempt market manipulation to handcuff a President simply because they don&apos;t have any campaign donor driven leverage on him? https://t.co/5HAN1Y8GlA 
 20. I mean, next we&apos;ll start thinking the apparatus of the intelligence community could be weaponized by the same system benefactors just because they couldn&apos;t control President Trump. ROFLMAO... That would be insane. Crazy right? https://t.co/ywpiwnaYen 
 21. Tin-foil-hat wearing conspiracy nuts. Get serious. It&apos;s all just coincidences. Shine on you crazy diamonds. /END https://t.co/inhpulAeAT</texto><total_retweets type="int">2631</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">5034</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">213</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">594886554</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">117199</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2014</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">85635</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1776495582270425</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>