<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">217</hilo><total_tweets type="int">18</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ Is #QAnon legit? I started typing this thread this morning. It&apos;s more urgent to post and share this given the attack on #Q on the Great Awakening board this afternoon. The attack confirms that my assessment that #QAnon is over the target is, in fact, on target. 
 2/ The question of #QAnon being a LARP has been debated, but there&apos;s huge evidence that #Q is real and very directly tied to #POTUS. Many, I believe correctly, speculate that Q is military intelligence (possibly #GeneralFlynn) or at least uses this for some sourcing. 
 3/ Recently, a YouTube channel &quot;American Intelligence Media&quot; (AIM) claimed that Q is a LARP/#Psyop. This was upsetting to many as it has seemed that #AIM is dedicated to exposing the cabal and the #DeepState, w/a rightfully-heavy focus on the #SeniorExecutiveService (#SES). 
 4/ The recent push by #AIM about the #SES may have caused AIM to be targeted. How do we interpret the claims by AIM? 
 5/ Here is my analysis: There are many factors that serve to debunk the #AIM video that tries to debunk #QAnon as legit, namely: a. They claim that @jerome_corsi says he has communicated directly w/#Q. This is absolutely not true. 
 6/ b. They claim that #QAnon contacted them directly. Q said he would engage in &quot;No comms privately w/ anyone.&quot;[...] 
 7/ c. They claim that #Q could NOT be a close insider since the release of the info would be a national security violation that would put them in jail. This is NOT THE CASE if it is a true insider w/authorization from #POTUS, who can declassify ANYTHING. 
 8/ d. They falsely claim #Q has not shown confirmations w/in 3 weeks of predictions. This is easily disproven by the dozens of confirmations of Q…of connections to #POTUS (tweets, images from Air Force One, pen at Camp David, &quot;chain of command,&quot; hand gestures in speeches, etc.) 
 9/ …and of foreknowledge of events (BDT bomber, Hawaiian missile alert, NK deal, use of Omnibus deal to fund building the wall via Army Corps of Engineers). Look at 3/23 post https://t.co/WXPoHas6kU vis-à-vis #POTUS&apos; 3/25 tweet https://t.co/vHd4LYeYop 
 10/ e. They WILL NOT DISCLOSE how they figured out the original #Q to be legit…nor how they debunked the current one. f. They also claim specific knowledge that #Sessions (&quot;we won&apos;t reveal what we have on him&quot;) is compromised but will not disclose it. 
 11/g. They claim that the current Q is anti-Semitic…based on WHAT evidence?? h. #AIM also specifically attacks other channels that are clearly on the side of patriots and truth. This is a classic &quot;divide and conquer&quot; strategy of the #Clowns. 
 12/ i. They claim to &quot;be smarter than the public&quot; (having solved the &quot;puzzle&quot; in minutes) and to have been invited into #Q&apos;s Club. This behavior is 100% contrary to the Q movement (&quot;Where we go one, we go ALL&quot;), displaying the very &quot;elitism&quot; that we are fighting. 
 13/ In case it helps, they claim the #puzzle they solved is encrypted in this message: &quot;Eagles rain fire on the Canaanite as the merchant of wine challenges Sirus. The sword of Lilly joins forces with Jacob&apos;s adopted children.&quot; 
 14/ j. The idea that #Q was shut down by the cabal, who took control for a psyop, w/o making an effort to communicate this fact over many months is ludicrous. Also, it is hubris by #AIM to think that Q would target a relatively small YT channel w/60K subscribers. 
 15/ k. Important to remember: #Q warned us that &quot;they want you DIVIDED.&quot; The logical conclusion is either that #AIM is a #disnifo/#psyop channel or that it has been compromised. 
 16/ I believe that the latter interpretation is more likely based on their prior history, especially given the events that happened on the #8chan board a few hours ago. They were either threatened or have been trapped by their own arrogance into their current assessment. 
 17/ To conclude, all evidence...the many confirmations and the escalating attacks on #Q and efforts at division of #Patriots...point to #QAnon being a legit insider source providing real intel. 
 19/ The recent disinfo campaign and direct attack on #QAnon&apos;s GA board today compel us to analyze. Please retweet/comment to engage a vigorous analysis/discussion. Our goal should be the #Truth and not to prove an embedded position. /END</texto><total_retweets type="int">830</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1980</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">124</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">17</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">749684424</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">3785</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3969</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">6802</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7780699304231409</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>