<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">251</hilo><total_tweets type="int">20</total_tweets><texto type="str">The time my body count went from 0 to 3 in a week #thread #storytime https://t.co/nqjiWBUubs 
 I&apos;m 18 yrs old. Fresh out of highschool. I&apos;m a virgin. I&apos;d been known for it through out my 4 YRS in highschool, unlike my 2 BFF&apos;s at the time marisa &amp;amp; claire. THOSE HOES. Ughhhh #badinfluences Fr https://t.co/UGBXnPUX1l 
 Sooooo i&apos;d been dating this guy, we&apos;ll call him #1. He was sweet, kind, thoughtful, caring &amp;amp; I THOUGHT THAT MF was the one !!!!!!!!! But *buzzer* ehhhh wrong https://t.co/SFDbbPhWa7 
 Boom!! It&apos;s prom night. EVERYBODY got drunk &amp;amp; shit. I had a few drinks but, I did NOT get drunk like at all 
 My 2 BFFs were KNOWN for hooking up with ALL TYPES of nigga!!! But my dumb ass ain&apos;t believe it! Soo, yeah it&apos;s prom &amp;amp; everybody goes to the hotel. Claire &amp;amp; marisa go back to hotel EARLY, they were THAT drunk &amp;amp; my bf #1 being the kind nigga he is drove them! How sweet!! https://t.co/op1ITknID1 
 #1 told me he&apos;d come get me later bc I &quot;looked like I was having fun&quot; sooo yea he left. The prom has been over for an hour now &amp;amp; I&apos;M STILL HERE sitting on the curb in a PRETTY ASS DRESS !!!!!!!! Mad as FUCK ******plottin plottin plottin plottin****** 
 I FINALLY just call an uber. The uber got there in 5 minutes. My ass fell asleep in the uber !!!!!! Anyways, we pulled up. I got out &amp;amp; went up to my bf&amp;amp; I&apos;s room &amp;amp; BITCHHH GUESS WHAT I SAW https://t.co/yRoOFl1sc3 
 THEM 3. In the bed. Kissing. All over eachother. I WAS HEATED AS FUCK! A bitch ain&apos;t NEVER been this MAD !!!!!!!! 
 I got my shit &amp;amp; left. #1 followed me to &quot;talk to me&quot; while marisa &amp;amp; claire stayed in the room. There was weed &amp;amp; alchol EVERYWHERE !!!! #1 agreed to take me home &amp;amp; as soon as we pulled off, I called they asses in for underaged drinking AND possession of marijuana !!!! Haha BITCH https://t.co/AjlnZtol0j 
 (This was SATURDAY night by the way) So, #1 took me home. The VERY next day is when I met #2. We were talking for a few days &amp;amp; he asked to come over. I said WHY THE FUCK NOT???! Deadass likeeee https://t.co/hgB1ycSLUd 
 I ended up losing my virginity. SEX WAS GREAT. His personality was WACK asf. I was BORED the whooole lil evening. Whatever thoooo a bitch was feelin good soo I was likeeee — FUCK it !!!!! https://t.co/0RvQbFoCb0 
 I met #2 on that sunday, THEN I MET #3. HE WAS SO PERFECT. Omg. I loved him. Like fr. BITCHHH HE MY MAN NOW, that is how fr I am. I met #3 on that monday. He was sooo FINE. We went on a REAL FIRST DATE at a NICE ass place &amp;amp; he had a place we went there AFTER! I was EXCITED ASF https://t.co/oHKCyf8PpS 
 OF COURSE. We fucked in his COMFY ASS BED !!!!!!! Yas BITCHsfhjkksd! He was WAY BETTER THAN my FIRST!!! I was spruuuuung or whatevaaaa! https://t.co/f5OLwMRadA 
 So, I slept over his house until thursday &amp;amp; I LOVED THAT SHIT !!!! Except, a bitch KEPT throwing up! Like none stop ONLY in the morningggg!!!! I was wore out from THAT SHIT 
 HE suggested I go get a pregnancy test. I did it, but I was like &quot;NIGGA I AM NOTT PREGNANT&quot; &amp;amp; BITCHHH GUESS WHAT https://t.co/HL3XS7j57M 
 I was. I was pregnant. REMEMBER WHEN I SAID I WAS PLOTTIN? Like before I was pregnant??! Sooooo, my man was on the SAME PAGE as me https://t.co/XUWefDz6rM 
 So, MY MASTER PLAN. It&apos;s Thursday. I fucked #2. I fucked #3. He had a part time, GOOD paying job. I texted #1 &amp;amp; asked to come over later &amp;amp; you know, I GAVE IT UP. Sooo. That next Saturday, I texted the 2, told them I was pregnant, sent them the pic of the test &amp;amp; asked for 8,000. 
 $8,000 + $8,000 = $16,000 = a lot of damn money They sent that shit within 2 days. My man &amp;amp; I were set. I went to the doctor the next day for a follow up on my pregnancy &amp;amp; the doctor told me: &quot;I&apos;m sorry, ma&apos;am. You&apos;re not pregnant&quot; https://t.co/lnVUBeqW5M 
 I WALKED OUT THAT BITCH SO FAST!!! Deadass like — BITCHHHHHH !!!!!!!! I was sooooo fuckin relieved. Pregnancy ain&apos;t no joke!!!! Even tho I ain&apos;t go through that shit https://t.co/JyeanZf1xZ 
 Moral of the story, idek 💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀💀 THIS SHIT SAD tbh &amp;amp; I have NOTHING else to say but, BITCH GET YO COINS!!! 😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊😊 THE END😊😊 https://t.co/ByM0WF8J1D</texto><total_retweets type="int">186</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1538</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">47</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">951174252354514944</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">6741</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">0</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">1751</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">3.828788748184953</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>