<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">121</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) #MKULTRA is misunderstood. The #ConspiracyTheories have merit, but #weaponization goes well beyond #hollywood movies into the realm of things that are hard to imagine we&apos;d do. When resources are unlimited, you get the best weapons. This is a story about the CIA. #QAnon 
 2) You corrupt congress into submission, get ultimate secrecy, and then collectively head down the rabbit hole. The #CIA has almost limitless power, and we were dumb enough to give it to them 
 3) The original intention of #MKULTRA may have been understanding mind control, and was to prevent other world powers from using it, but then it evolved into something different. Wildly different. #conspiracy 
 4) This story has 2 prongs, and I am openly admitting that I both have no verifiable basis in fact, but that it seem to ring true when you develop a sophisticated enough world view to understand how #thematrix operates, and how it interweaves geopolitical events. #control 
 5) Prong 1a If #MKULTRA still exists, what stops a deranged, rogue organization from training kids into depraved behavior. As discussed, it seems quite feasible that #pedophiles are intentionally planted in positions of power so they can easily be blackmailed and controlled. 
 6) Prong 1b, gulp. What if abducting kids was not a good way to implement 1a. What if you needed to be bred from birth, conscripted into this life. Not knowing another world. No identity. You’re trained to perform. Private planes there and back to &quot;home&quot;. Scary, no? 
 7) Strangely the original episode cannot be found, but here is a snippet https://t.co/Ho8fLRNm1Q Find other snippets. 
 8) Imagine a world in which an organization was so rogue that the wheels of culture &amp;amp; power could operate in this way with impunity because stopping it would lead to mass #chaos and even the demise of a nation. #Nuclearwar is mutually assured destruction. Wouldn’t this be also? 
 9) Prong 2, mass fear. What if #MKULTRA was weaponized against a population to keep them clinging to the state in fear, because they were helpless otherwise? This is the story of mass killings, and why they “appeared.” 
 10) What if #MKULTRA was behind the endless stream of mass killings in #America? Would a rogue agency of government have so little value for families &amp;amp; life to take on such a sick endeavor? What are the stakes? What is the easiest ways to control a population? Fear. #FalseFlag 
 11) Once you have a population that suddenly feels dependent on its state apparatus for #Security, you can easily abuse the levers. Think #PatriotAct A population that accepts a perceived threat becomes easy to pacify. #NWO 
 12) What if &quot;leaders&quot; didn’t have your best interests in mind? What if enough actors were conscripted into the narrative with undue rewards and false senses of power to act on behalf of extremely powerful interests, making a deal with the #devil in the process? 
 14) What if the #CIA wasn’t the source of this power? What if they were corrupted by a more powerful set of actors that use it, against our will as #Americans, for their own means? What if it meant destroying the fabric of a nation for the #NewWorldOrder? #UnitedNations 
 15) What if the people that ran the world are psychopaths? #QAnon #logic #ClintonCrimeFamily #Hezbollah #Rothschild #CORRUPTION #TheGreatAwakening #Soros #Wikileaks #thematrix #RedPill #ChildTrafficking #NWO #OpenBorders #Antifa #OpioidCrisis #Trump #Military #ShadowGovernment</texto><total_retweets type="int">22</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">68</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">20</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">37</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1623794972</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">11222</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">39</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">10786</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.5565009939878032</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>