<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">61</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ #Bitcoin Stages - Price momentum can always be divided into 4 stages -@markminervini -S1 accumulation range (no media/max opportunity) -S2 directionnal trend (&amp;lt;&amp;lt;-- THIS IS WHERE YOU SHOULD TRADE) -S3 huge volatility (media are nuts/min opportunity) -S4 final mark down/crash https://t.co/Dnoli4R6Q0 
 2/ I told you to look into this article, that was the key for a great trade to do: - Leave S2 behind - Act during S3 that&apos;s going nowhere (22nd dec -40% day was the clue for S3) - So you had plenty of time to avoid S4 by beeing invested in it. https://t.co/STlRXRh8Oe 
 3/ #Bitcoin is the key leader and barometer of $CRYPTO sector. Hate it or not. This is just rationnal and reality. As long it&apos;s not trending up (S2), $CRYPTO will mostly not trending up. Your goal is to survive/make minimum mistakes not beeing right every move so avoid S1/S3/S4 
 4/ #Bitcoin ($CRYPTO) stages 2013 - 2015 https://t.co/zf1ggD6nNE 
 5/ #Bitcoin ($CRYPTO) stages 2015 - 2018 (in the making) https://t.co/SUhDrsGZgM 
 -You&apos;ll make 90% of your profits &amp;amp; best trades during S2 -Spend less time during S1/S3/S4, be liquid -S1/S3/S4 lead to small mistakes that grow and become FATAL -Trade less so you&apos;ll be more profitable -Survive to experience hundred&apos;s S2 in your career https://t.co/3TjYAAt9hy 
 8/ can you spot S3/S4 on gold $XAUUSD ? https://t.co/jmpw8ayCbI https://t.co/Pon4qJEXC9 
 9/ these are obviously general guidelines, but it&apos;s primordial to do this work to know where you are on the map, what you are trading, what&apos;s the plan &amp;amp; how to behave accordingly. Insight biais is easy (draw the chart after) but at least for now we&apos;re almost sure it&apos;s not S2. 
 10/ Can you spot the stages on DOGEBTC? highlight S1 (2) https://t.co/AUidn0bepX 
 11/ Can you spot S4 and S1 on $URA(nium) ?🤔 https://t.co/XQg2NfksDs</texto><total_retweets type="int">347</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1111</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">35</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1389203360</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">33786</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">292</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">5437</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.3062943635976725</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>