<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">60</hilo><total_tweets type="int">5</total_tweets><texto type="str">Jeff Sessions had no choice in the matter of firing McCabe, because of the Inspector General&apos;s report. I would caution everybody into reading too much into this. Russia wants @JeffSessions gone. 
 If Andy McCabe opened a criminal investigation into Jeff Sessions but Mueller told Sessions lawyer that it had been closed, it was closed ***for a reason*** folks. And the reason wasn&apos;t &quot;McCabe got it wrong, Sessions was transparent with Congress&quot; 
 Everybody stop and think for a moment. Compartmentalization is real. @Comey compartmentalized like a champ. I don&apos;t think McCabe was read in on Sessions. Hence McCabe&apos;s opening of a probe, and its being closed again by Bobby III Sticks. SAIC Charlie Kable didn&apos;t open a probe :) 
 You haven&apos;t seen @Comey complain about the firing of Andy McCabe because he knows perfectly well that the IG report tied Sessions&apos; hands. Anybody looking to drag down Sessions is doing Putin&apos;s work for him. Complain to and about Horowitz, if you want to; not Sessions. #McCabe 
 PS: just to confuse you guys even more, I have zero time for Jeff Sessions, but the man was pictured dining with Rosenstein for a reason, gang. Steady as she goes, chaps. Hold your fire. We&apos;re getting to the end of this terrible period of US history now. Stay frosty. ;) https://t.co/nPehD1UiFb</texto><total_retweets type="int">900</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">3225</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">94</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">19346439</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">288502</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">23404</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">146343</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0169186936463472</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>