<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">381</hilo><total_tweets type="int">26</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1008 #QAnon says POTUS is not under criminal investigation, not yet. Also talks about a massive intel sweep, #SethRich, and America for Sale. Lots in this post! @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/cWUyXDPNcK 
 2. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1009 #Qanon responds to his post and talks about troops to boarder, CIA Black ops with prvt funds. Explain D&apos;s involved. MS-13 road block, sex trafficking road block and talks about Jeff Flake is AZ roadblock. and MORE! @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WG https://t.co/NaSiQqJ3rn 
 3. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1010 #Q talks about MONEY POWER and CONTROL and how people are in the way. Mass Extinctions, Gun Control and our VOICE does not matter and Roths are mentioned. UK/GER [5 days]. REVELATIONS. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/ckN31WRegu 
 4. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1011 #Q responds to his last post and says: NK DEFUSE. RUSSIA TESTING NEW MISSILES. RUSSIA NEW THREAT. COINCIDENCE? THEY MUST MAINTAIN THREAT TO RETAIN POWER/INFLUENCE. ARE YOU AWAKE? @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/aFzUkwwTUI 
 5. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1012 #Q pays respect to the 4 Marines that list their lives in CA. Their sacrifice will never be forgotten. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/kirmtN2wKa 
 6. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1013 TWITTER. CLOWNS. Operation Q-T2810C. False drops. Bot push. Future &quot;Conspiracy&quot; push to norms. Bad mixed w/ good. Taint. They are scared. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/Osvqdni2Xd 
 7. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1014 MZ to step down as Chairman. MZ out of US. @Jack Good luck. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/bNUl0ywKZi 
 8. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1015 Example. Gateway Bridge Project. $1.8mm Cory Booker - Singapore. $3.5mm Chuck Schumer - Israel. $400k Chris Christie - Mary Pat US. …….. Omnibus Bill. The gift that keeps on giving. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom #Q https://t.co/jwf2kB17wr 
 9. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1016 Q wants us to track Hussein timeline from 1/20/17 - today. Cross against POTUS’ schedule and Cross against WH visitor log 11/22-1/18/17. Q tells us that this will become very relevant very soon. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom #Q https://t.co/V2GOeRsevY 
 10. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1017 Q wants us to look up The Analysis Corporation (TAC). @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom #Q https://t.co/QjyEQAumLF 
 11. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1018 Anon looked it up and saw that is was FOUNDED by BRENNAN! Q tells Anons to Track edits and watch for ‘TheMagikBOT’. 🌀https://t.co/jxMQ4jSUG1 @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom #Q https://t.co/0spv7MtCVZ 
 12. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1019 An Anon states &quot;Now we know why #YouTube is linking to #Wikipedia to verify.&quot; Q responds, &quot;Learning. Follow the LOOP.&quot; LOOP CAPITAL? @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom #Q https://t.co/cIwQC3c8iA 
 13. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1020 Anon posts about @seanhannity&apos;s article &quot;CRISIS CANCELED: ‘Caravan’ CALLED OFF After Trump’s TOUGH TALK&quot; Q &quot;Used against them. NG now active. Refer to old drops re: SA / NG. The WAVE.&quot; 🌀https://t.co/OSpJLLRaHl @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA https://t.co/E9WMyANWor 
 14. #Q 🚨 4/4/18 SA is South America and NG National Guard attached are relevant #QAnon posts as Q instructed. RE READ @POTUS #MAGA #WWG1WGA #QAnon #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/w1TV7M3f1i 
 15. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1021 List the estimated wealth of religious organizations. Billions. Vatican bank. $229B. Board of Superintendence. Supervisory Commission of Cardinals. Clown connection. 1832 Rothschild loan to the Holy See. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA https://t.co/3144BCx1DQ 
 16. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1022 We don’t say his name. Adios. The protected flow into AZ is no more. Under the cover of his health, he will not be seeking another term. @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/7qKtjRa7uR 
 17. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1023 Anon asks, &quot;The Wall can&apos;t just be for stopping drugs, assassins, and child traffickers - which other nations were/are planning to use Mexico as an attack vector in the event of war?&quot;Check out #Q&apos;s response BELOW! 👇🏼 @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA https://t.co/TjUwWYuz4f 
 18. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 8 minutes between #Q post and #POTUS tweet! @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #KAG #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/0wVAbYkp5b 
 1. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Anons have a theory to check #Q Posts 111 days prior to fresh posts.... this was 111 days ago! Incredible! John McCain&apos;s middle name is Sidney. (Pics Related) @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #KAG #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/DVDaODZrej 
 20. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1024 #Q mentions Jared Cohen who is CFR, GOOG and founder of Google Ideas. Now known as Jigsaw. Then states, &quot;Coming to a theater near you.&quot; @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom https://t.co/59mh2rCfMr 
 21. Jared Cohen North KOREA! Finally, the other purple tie guy in the NK trip post drop from months ago comes to the forefront! @POTUS #MAGA #QAnon #WWG1WGA #WednesdayWisdom #MakeItRain https://t.co/H0JGvS2J8L 
 22. #Q is on FIRE today! #MakeItRain @POTUS #WWG1WGA #QAnon #MAGA #WednesdayWisdom #Trump #KAG https://t.co/6QMeC9iODI 
 23. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Post 1024 #Q giving Anons some love for their kind words and appreciation. #Q said they read each one. States that we are in this together #WWG1WGA and 2018 will be glorious! Sends blessings. @POTUS #WWG1WGA #QAnon #MAGA #WednesdayWisdom #Trump #KAG https://t.co/lAnO9tHBIW 
 24. #QAlert🚨 4/4/18 Posts 1026-1027 Anon bets @POTUS has already talked to Putin. @QAnon responds peace through strength. Then posts that DJT will be up all night and to watch the news tomorrow. #WWG1WGA #MAGA #NationalHugANewsPersonDay #MLKJr #MakeItRain https://t.co/XckPkB8LMu 
 25. #QAlert🚨 4/4/18 #QAnon said that @POTUS would not be getting any sleep last night. Something happened. Check out @POTUS schedule updates last night. #WWG1WGA #MAGA #MakeAmericaGreatAgain #pray #MLKJr #MakeItRain #Q https://t.co/4S7CBixoSn 
 26. #QAlert 🚨 4/4/18 Anons did a great job digging up info on JARED COHEN. Adding to 4/4 post. #WWG1WGA #MAGA #MakeAmericaGreatAgain #pray #QAnon #DeepState https://t.co/zquq06rEKs</texto><total_retweets type="int">2023</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">3044</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">176</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">20</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">940430173517811714</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">89896</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">30746</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">22093</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9026828088610835</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>