<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">348</hilo><total_tweets type="int">29</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) A review of where we are and what the different theories of what&apos;s happening with Mulehead are. Realize that some of these cross ideological lines, and Rob Reiner and Rush Limbaugh can agree on the &quot;facts&quot; of what&apos;s happening, one supporting, one lamenting. 
 2) so, here we go. THEORY #1, and clearly the most popular theory. MULEHEAD is a blackhat working to impeach Trump or &quot;find something&quot; that can be used to remove him. Support for this view cites *So far it &quot;appears&quot; he had only indicted or interviewed &quot;Trump-related&quot; ppl 
 2) contd. *He has charged Flynn with lying *He has charge The Funnel with everything from tax fraud to operating a hot dog stand without a license. *The Fake News Media supports this view cuz they really think Trump &quot;colluded&quot; and this plays into their scenario 
 2) contd. *Much, if not almost all, of the conservative media likewise accepts this because they all think the Deep State is out to impeach Trump *In this view Sessions is a weak doddering fool, who if not controlled by Rod Rosenstein, is manipulated by him. 
 3) VIEW #2 MULEHEAD is a black hat actor who nevertheless was either pressured or threatened to &quot;do the right thing&quot; Evidence for this is: *TRUMP interviewed him a few days before RR appointed him. Trump interviewed him for &quot;FBI director&apos;s&quot; job---which Mulehead couldn&apos;t hold. 
 3) contd. *Trump at the time knew all the details of U1 and (supposedly) Mulehead&apos;s involvement in it and gave him an out. Do the right thing, go down as a patriot, get a pardon. *NOT popular with Fake News cuz obviously they think Trump is guilty and Mulehead a paragon of virtue 
 3) contd I will address some of Mulehead&apos;s actions below, as his actions in this scenario wouldn&apos;t be different from VIEW #3. 4) VIEW #3 MULEHEAD is working for Trump *This view begins with the same as #2, namely Trump hired Mulehead after the interview. 
 4) contd. *Trump knew what he was getting with Mulehead, and knew either he was a &quot;white hat&quot; or they had enough on him to make him &quot;do the right thing.&quot; *In this view, it is a theory that Mulehead has already been guaranteed a pardon or immunity. No proof of this--just a theory 
 4) contd. *Sessions, Horowitz, and RR are in on the scheme. So, if theory #2 or #3 are correct, what the hell is Mulehead doing? 5) Actively gathering evidence. This theory holds that Mulehead is, under the guise of looking at, say, Manafort, really gathering evidence on . . 
 5) contd. Tony Two-toes, Pedo, and ultimately Cankles. *Evidence for this comes from a Politico story months ago that &quot;FBI investigators&quot; associated with Mulehead (think about that!) were looking into The Funnel&apos;s connections to Tony Two-Toes 
 5) contd. Evidence, contd. *Tony Two-Toes and Pedo immediately shut down their business and began shredding stuff the moment this story leaked. *To my knowledge, no one has seen Tony Two-Toes since that report. *Mulehead keeps dancing with charges against The Funnel &amp;amp; Gates 
 5) contd. Evidence, contd. *It&apos;s almost as though Mulehead really doesn&apos;t want to go to court with these guys. If this theory is true, it would be because he DOESN&apos;T. It&apos;s a show while he investigates the real criminals. *It&apos;s important to understand that except for . . . 
 5) contd. Evidence, contd. * . . . slip ups like the Politico report, the fake news media not only won&apos;t report these facts, but wouldn&apos;t even think to INVESTIGATE *So all revelations have to come from &quot;alternative&quot; journalists like Chillum, @drawandstrike @TheLastRefuge2 etc. 
 6) There is an important variation to the #3 interpretation. *Mulehead was never intended to bring charges against these bad actors himself, rather to hand over all his findings to Sessions/Horowitz and let them prosecute. That view assumes he IS gathering some key evidence. 
 6) contd. *A different version of that same interpretation is that Mulehead has NOT been gathering any &quot;real&quot; evidence, and that his goal has been quite different: to provide an ongoing smokescreen/&quot;demonstration&quot; to occupy both DemoKKKrats &amp;amp; the fake news media. 
 6) contd. *In such a scenario, Mulehead is marching back and forth, attracting attention but not really doing anything, while Horowitz and Sessions prepare cases. *Moreover, in such a take, Mulehead could well be feeding information to Sessions &amp;amp; Horowitz. HOWEVER, you say . . . 
 6) contd. &quot;What about Gen. Flynn? His life is ruined. Is that just a &quot;distraction?&quot; Depends. @ThomasWictor has argued that Flynn, a lifelong spy, has orchestrated much of this--that he knew what he was doing &amp;amp; was ready to pay the price. 
 6) contd. Further under the Flynn-directed-his-fate view, few would doubt that Trump would make Flynn whole at the first moment that became possible. 7) Leave aside Flynn and whether he is a victim or super-spy, what evidence is there that Mulehead is engaged in a demonstration? 
 7) contd. *Contrary to the view that Sessions is &quot;doing nothing,&quot; in fact (and, yes Virginia, these are facts) --It was announced months ago that DOJ was already investigating U1 and had been . . . &quot;for months&quot; 
 7) contd. ---It was announced months ago that DOJ was already investigating Cankles e-mails and had been . . . &quot;for months.&quot; ---It was announced months ago that DOJ was already investigating the Clinton Crime Family Foundation and had been . . . &quot;for months.&quot; 
 7) contd. ---It was announced last week that on top of these three investigations DOJ was &quot;considering&quot; a separate FISA investigation. So, regardless of which theory one accepts, it is NOT true that Sessions is just &quot;sitting there.&quot; 
 7) contd. For at least FIVE MONTHS, maybe seven, DOJ has been engaged in three Cankles related investigations. These are separate and apart from Horowitz&apos;s Inspector General investigation. 
 8) I have hypothesized that most of what Nunes, Grassley, Goodlatte, and Johnson are getting are being given them by Horowitz, Sessions, and/or Mulehead. The paperwork is so massive, I think, even Congressional staffs would have to have directions. 
 9) So there you are. Those who think Mulehead is out to &quot;get Trump&quot; (again, excluding Flynn who may be a separate issue) have about 2 dozen nothing indictments against Russkies and/or the Funnel. However given what has appeared in Congress it seems likely NO charges will stick 
 10) Once the FISAs unwind, it is likely that ANY person prosecuted using a FISA will demand a new trial. Not saying they&apos;ll get one, but those papers will be filed. 11) I subscribe to the smokescreen. Mulehead gives every evidence of a guy just spinning his wheels very publicly 
 11) contd. . . to attract attention while either he, or someone else, is doing the heavy lifting. 12) Ror the &quot;Where are the indictments?&quot; crowd I will remind you that the AIRTIGHT case against Robert Hanssen took TWO years &amp;amp; even with wiretaps it took FIVE years to get Gotti 
 13) So, I think each side has points to address. The black hat/Mulehead bad crowd has to answer why he doesn&apos;t seem to be doing anything; why Trump hired him; why Trump has NEVER given him a nickname; and why RR &amp;amp; Sessions express support. 
 14) The &quot;smokescreen&quot;/white hat view has to explain why Flynn was indicted; why NO indictments so far have come vs Cankles et al, &amp;amp; what the connection is between Mulehead, RR, Sessions, Horowitz, &amp;amp; Congress. 
 15) The latest wildcard is the fake news report that Mulehead is investigating a murder related to the investigation--but not the Shawn guy. Obviously this is Seth Rich. 16) Already we have seen a move by the fake news to suggest Rich was a Russkie agent. That is coming.</texto><total_retweets type="int">1171</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">3015</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">140</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">562255311</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">55822</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">3731</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">95995</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0382488560022758</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>