<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">7</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ Foreign governments are NOT the only ones looking closely at @ClintonFdn public filings as @FBI @IRS and @TheJusticeDept dig in...@csthetruth 
 2/ Join me on a brief tour---we start in CA where &quot;folks&quot; need to look here: https://t.co/2VrQxXVilt 
 3/ Punch in 271414646 into FEIN field and then take a close look at RRF for 2015, and first delnquency letter...due date for RRF was 15 November 2016--filed WAY late and does not disclose required details of FOREIGN GOVERNMENT GRANTS!... 
 4/ Then punch in 311580204 and note that parent entity has an incomplete report for 2016 that was REJECTED....@csthetruth 
 5/ Please note that @SenKamalaHarris WAS AG and that @AGBecerra IS California AG--so for how long has that state been investigating @ClintonFdn and @ClintonHealth ? Clinton entities have run roughshod over (willinmgly? duped donors in high income tax rate states--with dficits WHY 
 6/ Now we fly over to NY where there is a similar site (punch both FEINs, using dashes after first 2 numbers) here: https://t.co/bNQKOrUWwM 
 7/ NY laws ALSO require specifics concerning ALL government grants--why are there still no amended disclosures from 2004 onwards, especially concerning FOREIGN government grants--oh wait, because @AGSchneiderman is a HACK in thrall to the Clintons? @FBI @csthetruth @POTUS ? 
 8/ Then look carefully @ AMENDED BYLAWS filed ALMOST FOUR YEARS LATE on 27 June 2017 in NY--Clinton family ILLEGALLY gutted &quot;public charity&quot; status on 2 November 2013 as they DUPED @NewYorkTimesGHS and incoming &quot;directors, then hid this massive error past the 2016 election in NY! 
 9/ On @csthetruth we have provided a link to the 18 November 2004 agreement with National Archives where @ClintonFdn swore to mainitain forever its status as a &quot;public charity&quot;--ONE FAMILY CANNOT CONTROL SUCH ENTITIES LAWFULLY--why didn&apos;t @IRS catch this LONG AGO? CORRUPT? 
 10/ The @IRS and @TheJusticeDept must STEP UP THEIR GAMES--FRAUD is NOT the main question at @ClintonFdn--WHY DID @FBI and @IRS and MANY OTHERS MISS OBVIOUS FRAUDS FOR SO LONG, ever since February 2001?--key figure @Comey tell @realDonaldTrump @csthetruth PLEASE all 10 tweets!</texto><total_retweets type="int">879</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1137</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">51</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">30244119</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">35370</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1982</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">20782</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0584840005653757</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>