<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">389</hilo><total_tweets type="int">28</total_tweets><texto type="str">COMEY MEMOS: (THREAD) Working my way through the 15 pages of #ComeyMemos. Here are the most important and/or shocking revelations: 1/ 
 During #Comey&apos;s 1/6/17 at Trump Tower, @Comey told Trump that the Russians allegedly had tapes involving Trump &amp;amp; prostitutes at a Moscow hotel in 2013. Could these be the infamous #PeeTapes? #ComeyMemos 2/ 
 Trump also praised #Comey on 1/6/17 for his handling of the #ClintonEmails investigation. @realDonaldTrump lavished praise on @Comey, indicating that Comey had conducted himself &quot;honorably&quot; and had a great reputation. #ComeyMemos 3/ 
 When Comey mentioned that #Russia had tapes showing Trump &amp;amp; prostitutes, Trump interjected &quot;there were no prostitutes,&quot; and them claimed to be the kind of guy who didn&apos;t need to &quot;go there.&quot; #WRONG! #ComeyMemos 4/ https://t.co/vp6zgQLwI4 
 Without prompting, Trump launched into a tirade against some of those accusing him of sexual assault, specifically referencing a particular stripper. Comey told him the FBI wasn&apos;t investigating him. #ComeyMemos 5/ https://t.co/oP3rFEbsNK 
 On 1/28/17, Trump held a private meeting with #Comey in the WH. Trump never asked Comey an open-ended question or let him choose the topic of conversation. Shouldn&apos;t a new POTUS seek guidance from a seasoned FBI Director on nat sec affairs?? #ComeyMemos 6/ 
 Instead, Trump spent his hour w/ the FBI Director talking about his Inauguration crowd size, White House vs Mar-a-lago accommodations, the 2016 campaign, his son&apos;s height, and (again) defended himself against allegations of sexual assault. #ComeyMemos 7/ 
 After #Comey emphasized that he was &quot;not on anybody&apos;s side politically and could not be counted on in that traditional political sense,&quot; Trump stated that he &quot;needed loyalty and expected loyalty.&quot; Comey did not reply &quot;or even nod.&quot; #ComeyMemos 8/ 
 During that first WH meeting, Trump continued to obsess over #HillarysEmails, going over the sequence of associated events in great detail. After Comey indicated that &quot;the investigators ALL agreed that there was no case,&quot; Trump said he disagreed. #ComeyMemos 9/ 
 Trump once again brought up the #GoldenShowers &quot;thing&quot; and emphasized that it was fake news. Trump obsessed over whether @FLOTUS thought it was true, &amp;amp; then (falsely) claimed that he did not stay overnight for the Miss Universe trip. #ComeyMemos 10/ 
 Trump directly asked Comey to have the @FBI &quot;investigate the whole thing [#PeePeeTape &amp;amp; prostitutes] to prove it was a lie.&quot; (Given Trump&apos;s obsession w/ everything gold, it wouldn&apos;t be surprising that Trump has a fetish for #GoldenShowers. #AmIRite?) #ComeyMemos 11/ 
 1/28/17 #ComeyMemos: &quot;[Trump] then returned to loyalty, saying &quot;I need loyalty.&quot; I replied that he would always get honesty from me. He paused and said that&apos;s what he wants, &quot;honest loyalty.&quot; I replied &quot;you will get that from me.&quot;&quot; 12/ 
 Comey clarified in his memo that they may have understood the phrase &quot;honest loyalty&quot; differently. Comey meant loyalty to the office, the country, and the truth. &quot;I decided it would not be productive to push the subject further.&quot; #ComeyMemos 13/ 
 During the 1/28/17 meeting, Trump told Comey that he had serious reservations about #MichaelFlynn&apos;s judgement. However, Trump continued to keep Flynn on as his National Security Advisor until the media forced his hand. #ComeyMemos 14/ 
 During an undated meeting with Trump COS Reince Priebus, Priebus improperly inquired about FBI&apos;s investigation into #MichaelFlynn. Comey told COS that these inquiries should go through DOJ to avoid accusations of improper WH influence over ongoing investigations. #ComeyMemos 15/ 
 In @Comey&apos;s memos, he obfuscates any personal responsibility in playing politics w/ the FBI &amp;amp; influencing the election, telling Priebus that &quot;it also wasn&apos;t my fault that #HumaAbedin forwarded emails to #AnthonyWeiner.&quot; #ComeyMemos 16/ 
 Back to the #PeePeeTape: Remarkably, @realDonaldTrump brought up the #GoldenShowers in a 3rd meeting w/ @Comey, this time in the Oval Office. Trump again obsessed that @FLOTUS might believe the allegation. #ComeyMemos 17/ 
 Once again denying #GoldenShowersGate, Trump nonsensically added that #Putin had told him that Russia has &quot;some of the most beautiful hookers in the world.&quot; #ComeyMemos Hey @Franklin_Graham &amp;amp; other #FakeChristians, why was your @POTUS talking about prostitutes w/ Putin? 18/ 
 Trump asked whether #Comey agreed w/ his reply during a TV interview that he &quot;respected&quot; Putin. Comey criticized Trump for comparing the US to Russia &quot;b/c we aren&apos;t the kind of killers that Putin is.&quot; Trump didn&apos;t take too well to the criticism. #ComeyMemos 19/ https://t.co/AkYA7eUyFO 
 After dismissing AG, COS &amp;amp; others from the Oval, Trump once again met privately w/ Comey, this time to talk abt #Flynn. Trump emphasized Flynn didn&apos;t do anything wrong vis a vis Russia, but had lied to @VP. #ComeyMemos 20/ 
 When lamenting to #Comey about leaks of his phone calls w/ foreign leaders, Trump observed how the leaked transcripts included things he didn&apos;t remember saying. He then said &quot;they say I have one of the world&apos;s greatest memories.&quot; #ComeyMemos 21/ 
 During his rant about leakers, Trump instructed #Comey to talk to AG Sessions about pursuing prosecution of reporters. (Trump is a clear and present danger to our #1A rights.) #ComeyMemos 22/ 
 In a bold-faced attempt to obstruct justice, Trump, referring to the #Flynn investigation, told #Comey &quot;I hope you can see your way clear to letting this go, to letting Flynn go. He is a good guy. I hope you can let this go.&quot; #ComeyMemos 23/ 
 3/30/17 phone call: Trump said &quot;the cloud of this Russia business&quot; was making it difficult to run the country. He claimed to have letter from large DC law firm confirming he&apos;d received no income from Russia. (Why not just release #TrumpTaxReturns to prove it?) #ComeyMemos 24/ 
 For a 4th time, Trump brought up the prostitutes subject w/ #Comey, denying meeting w/ any in Russia. &quot;Can you imagine me, hookers?&quot; (Uhm, #YESWECAN!) &quot;I have a beautiful wife and it has been very painful. #ComeyMemos 25/ 
 On 3/30/17, Trump once again clearly attempted to obstruct justice. He explicitly asked what #Comey could do to &quot;lift the cloud&quot; of the Russia investigation. He encouraged @Comey to publicize the fact that Trump was not under investigation. #ComeyMemos 26/ 
 Finally, on 4/11/17, Trump complained that the #RussiaInvestigation was making things difficult for him &amp;amp; emphasized he needed Comey&apos;s help &quot;b/c I have been very loyal to you, very loyal, we had that thing, you know.&quot; This is more evidence of #ObstructionOfJustice #ComeyMemos 27/ 
 unroll @threadreaderapp</texto><total_retweets type="int">175</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">430</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">34</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">22</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">294991606</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">50321</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">35443</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">43951</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.847233389118008</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>