<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">336</hilo><total_tweets type="int">27</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ I have Muslim family members from Iran. This thread is for them, in view of what appears to be a transformative revolution taking place. Iran is home to one of the world&apos;s oldest continuous major civilizations, with historical and urban settlements dating back to 7000 BC. https://t.co/qMfWOWL86v 
 2/ The Persian Empire is a series of imperial dynasties centered in Persia/Iran since the 6th century BC in the Achaemenid era, to the 20th century AD in the Qajar era. The first dynasty of the Persian Empire was created by Achaemenids, established by Cyrus the Great in 550 BC. 
 3/ with the conquest of Median, Lydian and Babylonian empires. It covered much of the Ancient world and controlled the largest percentage of the earths population in history when it was conquered by Alexander the Great. 
 4/ From 247 BC to 224 AD, Persia was ruled by the Parthian Empire, which supplanted the Hellenistic Seleucid Empire, and then by the Sassanian Empire, which ruled up until the mid-7th century. 
 5/ The Persian Empire in was interrupted by the Arab conquest in 651 AD, establishing the even larger Islamic caliphate, and later by the Mongol invasion. The main religion of ancient Persia was the native Zoroastrianism, but after the 7th century, it was replaced by Islam. 
 7/ The Safavid Empire was the great Persian Empire established after Arab conquest by Shah Ismail I. Literature, art and architecture flourished in Safavid era. Safavids made Shia Islam the official religion in the empire versus the Sunni Islam in the neighbouring Ottoman Empire. 
 8/ Achaemenid Empire (550–330 BC) Sasanian Empire (224–651) Safavid dynasty (1501–1736) Afsharid dynasty (1736–1796) Qajar dynasty (1785–1925) 
 9/ Once a major empire, Iran has endured invasions by the Greeks, Arabs, Turks, and the Mongols. Iran has continually reasserted its national identity throughout the centuries and has developed as a distinct political and cultural entity. 
 10/ Iran suffered during the late Middle Ages and early modern period. Invasions of nomadic tribes, whose leaders became rulers, affected it negatively. Baten, Jörg (2016). A History of the Global Economy. From 1500 to the Present. Cambridge University Press. p. 214. 
 11/ In the first half of the 19th century, Iran lost territories in the Caucasus (parts of Iran for centuries) comprising modern-day Eastern Georgia, Dagestan, Azerbaijan &amp;amp; Armenia, to the Russian Empire, following Russo-Persian Wars bt 1804–13 &amp;amp; 1826–8. https://t.co/9C7ziuM9u4 
 12/ The Great Persian Famine of 1870–1871 is caused the death of 2 million persons. A new era in the history of Persia dawned w the Persian Constitutional Revolution against the Shah in the late 19th and early 20th centuries. 
 13/ The Shah managed to remain in power, granting a limited constitution in 1906 (making the country a constitutional monarchy). The first Majlis (parliament) was convened on October 7, 1906. 
 14/ The discovery of oil in 1908 by the British in Khuzestan spawned renewed interest in Persia by the British Empire. Control of Persia remained contested bt the UK &amp;amp; Russia, in what became known as The Great Game. 
 15/ Persia was divvied up and codified in the Anglo-Russian Convention of 1907, which divided Persia into spheres of influence, regardless of her national sovereignty. 
 16/ During World War I, the country was occupied by British, Ottoman and Russian forces but was essentially neutral. In 1919, after the Russian revolution and their withdrawal, Britain attempted to establish a protectorate in Persia, which was unsuccessful. 
 17/ In 1925, after being prime minister for two years, Reza Khan became the first shah of the Pahlavi dynasty. He ruled for almost 16 years until September 16, 1941, when he was forced to abdicate by the Anglo-Soviet invasion of Iran. 
 18/ With German armies highly successful against Russia, the Iranian government rejected British &amp;amp; Russian demands to expel the Germans. In response the Allies invaded in August 1941, and easily overwhelmed the weak Iranian army. 
 19/ Iran was the conduit of Allied Lend-Lease aid to the Soviet Union. The purpose was to secure Iranian oil fields &amp;amp; ensure Allied supply lines. Iran was officially neutral. Its monarch Rezā Shāh was deposed during the occupation &amp;amp; replaced w his young son Mohammad Reza Pahlavi. https://t.co/PuoAM9d5Yc 
 20/ At the Tehran Conference of 1943, Allies issued the Tehran Declaration which guaranteed post-war independence &amp;amp; boundaries of Iran. Soviet troops stationed in NW Iran refused to withdraw &amp;amp; backed revolts that established pro-Soviet separatist national states 
 21/ in the northern regions of Azerbaijan and Iranian Kurdistan, the Azerbaijan People&apos;s Government and the Republic of Kurdistan in late 1945. Soviet troops did not withdraw from Iran proper until May 1946 after receiving a promise of oil concessions. 
 22/ On August 19, 1953, a successful coup was headed by retired army general Fazlollah Zahedi, organized by the CIA, w the active support of the British (MI6). The coup—with a black propaganda campaign designed to turn the population against Mosaddeq—forced Mosaddeq from office. https://t.co/THCdzspVet 
 23/ The Iranian Revolution transformed Iran from a monarchy under Shah Mohammad Reza Pahlavi, to an Islamic republic under Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini. Ayatollah Khomeini became Supreme Leader of the country—in December 1979, until June 1989. 
 24/ On his deathbed in 1989, Khomeini appointed a 25-man Constitutional Reform Council which named president Ali Khamenei as the next Supreme Leader. Succeeding Khamenei as president was conservative Ali-Akbar Hashemi Rafsanjani, who served two four-year terms. 
 25/ In 1997, independent candidate Mohammad Khatami received 69% of the vote &amp;amp; enjoyed support from women/youth. In 1999 massive anti-government protests erupted in Tehran. Khatami was re-elected in June 2001 but his efforts were repeatedly blocked by conservatives in parliament. 
 26/ Conservative elements undermined the reformist movement, banning liberal newspapers &amp;amp; disqualifying candidates for parliamentary elections. In June 2003, anti-govt protests by several thousand students took place in Tehran. Several human rights protests occurred in 2006. 
 27/ In 2009, Ahmadinejad&apos;s reelection was disputed and marred by large protests The resulting social unrest is widely known as the Iranian Green Movement. https://t.co/9pO6uVurrJ 
 28/ On June 15, 2013, Hassan Rouhani won the presidential election in Iran. In his press conference one day after election day, Rouhani reiterated his promise to recalibrate Iran&apos;s relations with the world.</texto><total_retweets type="int">49</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">487</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">35</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">731855934675255297</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">45231</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">22279</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">74525</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8705160102194475</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>