<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">322</hilo><total_tweets type="int">23</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ Thread about useful Twitter Tools and Tips from @SallyAlbright and @CapWaterfront - Please retweet. 
 2/ Starting with threads, @WriteRack is essential. You can compose in the program or copy and paste your essay. It formats your text into a thread of tweets then you clean them up so the breaks are where you want them. Then you set them to go out on a timer. 
 3/ I use Twitter Moments to preserve threads. I used to use Tweetdeck but this is a lot easier. Sometimes I don&apos;t even publish them - they require a photo - because I can grab the top tweet straight from the draft when I need it. 
 4/ If you want to see an entire thread, or see which tweet or which user someone is replying to, click the time stamp. This works in Facebook too. Here&apos;s another tip: https://t.co/tiAySQd5p5 
 5/ @Buffer is a great tool for scheduling tweets. There are tons of apps that let you post to multiple platforms but with Buffer the posts don&apos;t go out at the same time. You can also schedule tweets at optimum times based on your when your followers are online. 
 6/ @Tweepi is great for new accounts. You identify accounts similar to yours and follow who follows them. So it&apos;s people with the same interests who are more likely to follow back. It doesn&apos;t happen that fast, and it&apos;s tedious, but reading bios can be kind of fun. 
 7/ @Tweepi also does a lot of useful analytics. It shows you what dormant accounts you follow so you can unfollow them. It&apos;s great for adding people to lists - one of the few tools out there to manage lists that actually works well. 
 8/ @Roundteam - This is how you keep accounts from going dormant or keep a presence if you aren&apos;t on Twitter much. You can set it RT tweets with keywords or tweets from people on a list- that&apos;s what I usually do. It will RT at intervals you set up. 
 9/ @Favstar shows you your most popular tweets. @IFTTT (If This Then That, rhymes with gift) does a lot of automation but doesn&apos;t do much for twitter beyond putting people on lists and emailing you digests but it&apos;s worth checking out. 
 10/ OK they make fun of me for this, I guess it&apos;s &quot;out of style&quot; but so what. Chrome ext. @Klout puts a little number next to someone&apos;s handle to show what kind of engagement &amp;amp; authority their acct has. Anything under 40 is likely a bot or brand new acct. A lifesaver. 
 11/ A lot of people don&apos;t know Twitter has a robust advanced search feature. It&apos;s annoying that it only searches the exact spelling not plurals etc, but it searches a lot of different ways. This is how the Berners are so good at finding our old tweets. https://t.co/2bxaqzgdqk 
 12/ There&apos;s no need to thank people for RTs, Likes &amp;amp; Follows. You can, but there&apos;s no need. You definitely do not need to be paying for this service. On the other hand, thanking people for their CONTENT is always appreciated and encouraged. 
 13/ Don&apos;t use auto DMs for new followers. No judgement, I know everyone does it, but don&apos;t. Exception: Events. I&apos;ve seen it work for getting details &amp;amp; updates out about your event. I&apos;ve seen bars reply &quot;Thanks for following! Text this number for a free beer.&quot; I approve. 
 14/ Don&apos;t buy followers. They don&apos;t interact with you and it&apos;s obvious they&apos;re fake. Bernie&apos;s Women&apos;s Conference had to buy followers to cover the fact that they lost so many real ones. Not a TERRIBLE idea, PR wise, but it was easy to spot. 
 15/ Never automate anything, not Likes, not RTs, especially not Follows. They will know, they always know, and you will lose your account forever. It&apos;s okay to schedule your own stuff but automation is verboten. If I did half the stuff they say I did, I&apos;d be long gone. 
 16/ I had a client once, in 2010 when things were still kinda new. He bought a service called TweetAttacks that would follow people for you. I told him not to use it, he did it anyway, called like 2 days later, he&apos;d been banned. Here&apos;s where the story gets good. 
 17/ So I go into the account and file an appeal. After some back and forth, Twitter says, Fine, type this sentence and send it to us. So I typed &quot;I [person&apos;s name] confess that I used automation on X and I understand it is against Twitter&apos;s TOS&quot; 
 18/ So the response from Twitter was basically &quot;Automation is against our TOS and since you have admitted to using automation this account is permanently closed.&quot; They played us. Pretty hilarious imo. And that was that. It was his company name. 
 19/ The best way to get your content shared is through reciprocity. RT people who RT you. I&apos;m in a ton of DM groups where we all RT each other&apos;s content. Think about forming a few of those. Usually if you want someone to RT something specific all you have to do is ask. 
 20/ Apparently &quot;Please retweet&quot; gets more shares than &quot;Please RT&quot; and posts with photos get exponentially more shares. I&apos;m told 3 hashtags is the sweet spot for the most shares but I have no idea why, just passing it along. 
 21/ We tell everyone, leave your own tweets at the top when you log off. Not just your pinned tweet, your current stuff. I usually hit the top two in my mentions. This is free advertising. Even if it&apos;s just you, why not put your best face forward? 
 22/ So there you go. Nothing black hat or automated or &quot;fake&quot; about any of it. Please let me know if you have any questions. 
 23/ Two more things. When you have someone muted but want to see their side of a conversation, follow them, then unfollow to mute them again when you&apos;re finished. Also @Favstar shows you who interacts with you the most so you can reciprocate.</texto><total_retweets type="int">114</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">290</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">42</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">11395432</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">82403</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">46916</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">217641</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8668069201212875</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>