<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">402</hilo><total_tweets type="int">28</total_tweets><texto type="str">(1) Hey howdy! I’m a member of the @NRA Apparently some unhinged, emotional children are saying my mere membership to the NRA = I have “blood on my hands”. Hmmmm https://t.co/lCrnWM370F 
 (2) Apparently this is meant to shame &amp;amp; intimidate me into: 1. Renouncing my NRA membership 2. Giving up my guns 3. Joining their &quot;cause&quot; of banning others guns Let&apos;s see if that&apos;ll work. What do you think? I have a couple thoughts. 
 (3) I lived decades in &quot;the city/suburbs/towns&quot;. As the slow creep of crime &amp;amp; unabated illegal immigration invaded each neighborhood, I moved to keep my family safe. 
 (4) I want nothing but a clean, safe place to live, work &amp;amp; be part of a decent society. But OTHERS were making that impossible. OTHERS were causing safety problems. I could tell those stories, but it would take forever. SO, I moved out to the country. 
 (5) Living out in the middle of nowhere doesn&apos;t mean one is completely safe though. There&apos;s these things called roads. People use them. 
 (6) So despite my childish &amp;amp; irrational desire to ban a tool (roads), I had to accept their existence. Oh well! Anyway... 
 (7) The first year I lived out in the country, I realized very quickly that even though I&apos;m isolated, there can still be danger AND it&apos;s up to ME to protect my family from that danger. 
 (8) One morning, on her way to work, my wife called me on her cell phone, &quot;Down our road, there&apos;s some guy hiding in the bushes. Keep an eye on things&quot; 
 (9) I didn&apos;t really think much of it. I figured maybe it was a hiker taking a break in the shade. But I kept it in the back of my mind. 
 (10) An hour later, I have to drive down the mountain to run some errands and sure enough, about a mile down our road is some dude hiding in the bushes. Weird. Bah, shake it off. I have things to do. Drive. drive. 
 (11) I spend a few hours down in the valley, taking care of business, and I drive back up the mountain. As I arrive up our road, there&apos;s the same dude, only this time he&apos;s standing in the middle of the road, blocking my path. 
 (12) Now, mind you, it&apos;s been at least 6 hours since my wife&apos;s first report that there&apos;s a guy hiding in the bushes. So my creepy-radar is pegged. Wtf, right? 
 (13) So I slowly pull up and stop. He&apos;s shirtless, waving his arms &amp;amp; has wild eyes. My immediate assessment is the dude is on drugs. 
 (14) I stop, and before I can ask him what&apos;s going on, he runs to my door &amp;amp; yells, &quot;GOT ANY FOOD????!!!&quot; What? &quot;No, hi, I&apos;m stuck. This is my situation&quot; just yelling &amp;amp; waving arms at me? 
 (15) I&apos;m no cold hearted asshole. I don&apos;t mind helping people. But after years of living in the city, I&apos;ve learned to stay away from the drug users, especially when they&apos;re tripping out. They&apos;re dangerous. Period. To themselves and others. 
 (16) I replied simply &quot;NO&quot; and quickly drove away to get home an call the authorities. He wasn&apos;t going to die of starvation before proper people came to help him. 
 (17) When I got home, I immediately grabbed my phone &amp;amp; my binoculars. Called the sheriff&apos;s dept and notified them of the crazy person hiding in the bushes. At the same time I was able to watch him a mile down the road with my binoculars 
 (18) He pulled a bicycle out of the bushes and in a fit of rage, threw it in the middle of the road. Then started jumping up and down. 
 (19) What? Why was he hiding in the bushes if he had a bike to ride to safety or food? Weird. Anyway, he started riding up the road towards our house. 
 (20) I couldn&apos;t see him any longer, so I walked outside to get a better look. That&apos;s when I noticed fresh bicycle tire tracks on my property. WTF? The dude was already at MY HOUSE while I was away? Damn. 
 (21) So that&apos;s when I went back inside, loaded my .45 &amp;amp; put it in my holster. If some wacko was gonna freak out on me, at least I had an equalizer at hand. Were the cops there yet? Nope. Not even close.... 
 (22) Now, some may argue there&apos;s no need for a gun. Maybe not. Maybe I should just be a victim. Fair enough. My wife wasn&apos;t there. BUT... 
 (23) I consider it my morale obligation to protect her. Part of protecting her, is protecting MYSELF so I can still be around for her. So dammit, I&apos;m going to do just that. 
 (24) This story is taking much longer than I anticipated, so let&apos;s cut to the ending. The guy wandered up around our neighborhood and fortunately he didn&apos;t come to my house again. He then rode back down the road and finally left our area- HOURS LATER. 
 (25) Did the police ever come? NO But they did call back about 4 hours later. &quot;We have a deputy that could come up to the area...&quot; I replied, &quot;Don&apos;t bother the crazy guy is gone&quot; 
 (26) So basically, unless somebody is ALREADY hurt or a crime is ALREADY committed, the police will never come to our remote area. That&apos;s reality kids. 
 (27) In my world, the police is only there to mop up the mess. 
 (28) So, do you think I&apos;m going to give up my RIGHT to protect my family because an emotional teenager is shaming me? Telling me I have &quot;blood on my hands&quot; ? No. It&apos;s absurd. Completely absurd. /end storytime</texto><total_retweets type="int">110</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">470</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">48</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">710738910725275648</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">8886</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1435</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">74373</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9498697335519943</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>