<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">52</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">Thread of resources! A friend just asked me to give him some links on articles on why women are underrepresented in tech which are written for a popular audience. Here&apos;s a roundup of articles I sent him. #womenintech #womeninSTEM (1/n) 
 First off, one should know that CS was once female dominated in the West: https://t.co/poSOWVUL0B (2/n) 
 One should also know that CS is female dominated in some countries today, like Malaysia and Qatar, and that many non-Western countries have near-parity in their CS majors. https://t.co/dF5E9KAtrj (3/n) 
 There are structural reasons why there are fewer women in CS in the West. For example, how CS departments responded to enrolment booms in the late-80s and dot-com era resulted in gatekeeping practices that disproportionately pushed women out: https://t.co/LXTbAGNLev (4/n) 
 Women are still getting into tech jobs but they&apos;re arriving at them from &quot;alternate pathways&quot; rather than the traditional &quot;pipeline&quot;, and these jobs are more likely to be lower paid and have fewer opportunities for advancement: https://t.co/VZhtp2g7q7 (5/n) 
 The whole pipeline metaphor is problematic and should be abandoned: https://t.co/IAxBSnIiBL (6/n) 
 Returning to those &quot;alternate&quot; pathways --- pathways such as coding bootcamps could have negative effects long-term since they can increase the amount of vertical segregation in tech: https://t.co/yNiTRXDM58 (7/n) 
 Then there&apos;s this idea that we need to &quot;fix&quot; the women so they can succeed in tech, rather than change tech itself. Women are stuck doing double-duty in tech: not only do we need to prove ourselves but also have to do diversity work: https://t.co/uzDhLWCdWi (8/n) 
 The idea you need an innate ability to do computing contributes to keeping women out of tech: https://t.co/D9Ob9eOXBw and racial minorities: https://t.co/CEgsviDyOA (9/n) 
 TLDR of all these articles: there are structural reasons for why there aren&apos;t more women in tech now. It isn&apos;t about the individual actions or &quot;choices&quot; of women, this is a sociological phenomenon and needs to be understood as such. Feel free to add articles to the list! (10/10)</texto><total_retweets type="int">24</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">74</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">11</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1670813678</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">1182</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1146</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">5459</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7569741935985363</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>