<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">93</hilo><total_tweets type="int">11</total_tweets><texto type="str">This morning, I want you to indulge me by reading two articles in sequence. The first is by @MarkMazzettiNYT. It starts with this (very true) statement: &quot;The release of the memo mattered less than #releasethememo.&quot; https://t.co/LnisYCxT0D 
 &quot;the campaign, captured in the hashtag #releasethememo, which was trending on Twitter for days, may have a far more significant impact than the memo’s contents. It was a choreographed effort by House Republicans and top White House officials to push a highly contentious theme...&quot; 
 Now, read this, from @DissentMag on the &quot;new conspiracists&quot;, by @RussellMuirhead and Nancy Rosenblum. &quot;The conspiracist mindset moved into the White House with the election of Donald Trump as president of the United States.&quot; https://t.co/XjjMF1eNvJ 
 &quot;Conspiracism is not new of course, but the conspiracism we see today does introduce something new—conspiracy without the theory. And it betrays a new destructive impulse: to delegitimate the government. Often the aim is merely to deligitimate an individual or a specific office.&quot; 
 Back to the end of @MarkMazzettiNYT&apos;s piece: &quot;But, he said, there could be significantly more harm if people begin looking for political motives in every action the F.B.I. takes. &apos;&apos;People across the country are going to say, ‘Can I trust the F.B.I.?&apos; he said.&quot; 
 Donald Trump is more than happy- he is hungry- to advance conspiracy theories. He would not hesitate to torch any person or institution that stands in his way, and to use conspiracy theories, whispers and suspicions to do so, to a degree no President has ever done. 
 The facts of the memo actually HURT the President&apos;s position. But once again, we fail to accept the reality of our situation: it&apos;s not about the facts. 
 And it works. Stunning, sad poll for @Axios by @surveymonkey: Donald Trump had turned the GOP against the FBI: https://t.co/ZjwGS4AZdL 
 The circle is complete. https://t.co/6Q32ZZLoHq 
 And the headlines help- Donald&apos;s conspiracies exploit flaws in journalism and the presentation of information that exacerbate the problem: https://t.co/hamCYd7EFg 
 The #ReleaseTheMemo campaign, neatly summarized by @MollyMcKew: https://t.co/idRjeqrWlz</texto><total_retweets type="int">483</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">993</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">65</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">19750159</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">74276</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">5401</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">27402</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0292230701968113</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>