<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">281</hilo><total_tweets type="int">21</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) Um Maggie, [@maggieNYT ] hate to undercut your *explosive story* on origin of Russia Probe. But George Papadopoulos talking in May 2016, is likely about this *open and public information* from April 2016. https://t.co/t9qtqDoLdQ 
 @maggieNYT 2.) Additionally, worth noting @maggieNYT is nowhere in the Joint Analysis Report [Comey, Brennan and Clapper construct] is anything about George Papadopoulos even hinted or alluded to. 
 @maggieNYT 3.) [@maggieNYT ] ABC in Australia is reporting it was Alexander Downer (Australian High Commissioner to UK) who then let counterparts in US know that George Papadopolous was talking about the Sidney Blumental hack via Clinton Emails. 
 @maggieNYT 4.) The @maggieNYT is also nonsense based on common sense. Papadopoulos was so important that: July 15th 2016 Comey opens counterintel investigation into Russian collusion. January 15th 2017 FBI visits Papadopoulos for first time. FBI waited for six months to talk to him? 
 @maggieNYT 5. @maggieNYT If George Papadopoulos was so important to the FBI “investigation” why did all “intelligence” agencies released their final JAR report without ever speaking to him? Not even once? 
 @maggieNYT 6. No @maggieNYT what you have in your article is a well constructed and brutally familiar pattern of what journalism looks like when the IC use reporters to cover their tracks and create a justification based on a false premise. 
 @maggieNYT 7. The Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson, Mary Jacoby, Nellie Ohr etc. and subsequent Christopher Steele origin of the FISA application source material is a risk to the former leadership within the DOJ National Security Division and FBI Counterintelligence Division. 
 @maggieNYT 8. @maggieNYT That&apos;s why both FBI and DOJ sides of this intelligence operation need to create a false origin. The actual FISA application content is a much more explosive risk. Use your common sense logic hat and see when you are being played. 
 @maggieNYT 9. @maggieNYT USE COMMON SENSE: If a Papadopolous conversation in May 2016 was the origin, the source material, of the FBI counterintelligence operation, then why were they denied a FISA application in June/July 2016 ? 
 @maggieNYT 10. @maggieNYT The wife of Glenn Simpson (Fusion GPS), Mary B. Jacoby, with years of Russia-angled reporting –including Donald Trump– visits the White House on April 19th 2016. https://t.co/2dqBvDPWYw https://t.co/j90bqiF4X7 
 @maggieNYT 11. @maggieNYT Mary B Jacoby is a deep part of Clinton&apos;s political camp going all the way back to the Rose Law Firm. You know that because you know her. After the April 19, 2016, WH visit, the DNC and Clinton campaign hire Mary and Glenn (Fusion GPS) for the &quot;trump project&quot;. https://t.co/q22kOWXqB6 
 @maggieNYT 12. @maggieNYT Immediately after Fusion was paid, Glenn Simpson and Mary Jacoby (Fusion GPS Patriarchs), hire Nellie Ohr. https://t.co/L8jrjyDCh4 
 @maggieNYT 13. @maggieNYT As you know, Nellie Ohr is the wife of DOJ Deputy Bruce Ohr. The same Bruce Ohr who was demoted for meeting with Glenn Simpson and Christopher Steele, along with FBI agent Peter Strzok, w/out telling DOJ leadership. https://t.co/aDsieAWMzd 
 @maggieNYT 14. @maggieNYT Again, you know this stuff. Nellie Ohr, Bruce Ohr and Glenn Simpson have known each other for years; and have worked on CIA *open source* projects together for a long time. https://t.co/8Gp93KYMc4 
 @maggieNYT 15 @maggieNYT As you know all of these people are SME&apos;s on everything Russia and everything Russia intelligence. It is all of this activity in April and May, not innocuous George Papadopolous reading newspapers, that assembled data and eventually led to the &quot;Russia Probe&quot;. 
 @maggieNYT 16. @maggieNYT on June 24th 2017 Mary Jacoby even publicly stated on her facebook that her work with Glenn is what specifically led to the FBI beginning the &quot;Russia Probe&quot;. https://t.co/Zkg0EjpOXE 
 @maggieNYT 17. @maggieNYT After the initial July 2016 FISA Court denial, the FBI and DOJ team leaned heavily on the external team of Jacoby, Simpson, Ohr, Steele etc. who created the &quot;dossier&quot; that enhanced the application that gained the FISA warrant in Oct. https://t.co/24uYStbtZt 
 @maggieNYT 18. @maggieNYT as you know, because of the legal framework around them, FISA warrants can be applied retroactively. Wiretaping and monitoring can technically begin while evidence is gathered to justify a DOJ-NSD warrant application later. https://t.co/Kg7GaTEown 
 @maggieNYT 19. @maggieNYT Which is exactly what former DOJ Attorney General John P. Carlin, National Security Division head, admitted to the FISA Court (October 2016) right before he quit his job. https://t.co/SvQRK9hzjv 
 @maggieNYT 20. So @maggieNYT the question I have for you is: Did you write that nonsense about George Papadopolous because the IC (FBI/DOJ) tricked you into it?..... OR were you a willing participant in helping transmit political disinformation in an effort to help them cover their tracks? https://t.co/3ZA7XihoVT 
 @maggieNYT 21. Happy New Year @maggieNYT !!</texto><total_retweets type="int">6279</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">10921</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">315</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">594886554</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">117199</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2014</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">85635</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1776495582270425</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>