<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">392</hilo><total_tweets type="int">28</total_tweets><texto type="str">~ Thread ~ How to become a better writer… In 7 simple, straightforward steps. 
 One thing… I’m not the world’s best writer. Just a dude that&apos;s been crafting content online for 4+ years. And luckily, I’ve learned a thing or three. Pues, vamos! 
 #1. Practice Makes Perfect If you want to become a better writer, you have to write more. No shit, Sherlock. Common sense, but the more you write... The better content you’ll craft. 
 If improving your content and copy is a priority, then set a daily word count goal… And hit it. Every. Damn. Day. 
 #2. Read More Again, we’re not reinventing the wheel here. 30 minutes of reading a day keeps the mental cobwebs away. And improves your ability to write killer content. 
 Reading literally rewires your brain. And that’s backed by science, fam: https://t.co/aMiJLfl897 
 Self-help, non-fiction, novels, etc. It doesn’t matter what you read. Just. Read. Anything. 
 Not sure where to start? Wondering what books give you the best bang for your mental buck? Well, I’d start here: https://t.co/4rJVnKmI5d 
 #3. Using Your Hands Well, kind of. To improve your copywriting ability, it’s essential to handwrite old-school sales letters. Sounds lame, but it works. 
 Sit down. Grab a notebook and a pen. And then head over to: https://t.co/9IsGWywbFL 
 If the 400+ pieces of content are overwhelming, I’ll make it easy for you. This dude is one of the greats. Start here: https://t.co/MlYVUj6lEi 
 Copy it down by hand. 20-30 minutes a day for a month or two. That’s it. Nothing complex. 
 You can even take things one step further... That dude @StartSellingSSS also recommends handwriting the content from greats within your niche. For example, as an email marketer, he likes to use the content from @BenSettle as an example and copy it down by hand. 
 #4. Study This Stuff Just like anything in life, a little studying goes a long way. Read about copywriting. Learn about content creation. Look at what other writers, bloggers, and content creators are doing. Then figure out how to emulate it. 
 I won&apos;t dive too deep into this one, but... The book recommended above is ideal for anyone looking to make cash online. This is another great one to study: https://t.co/Cu2OpE24du 
 P.S: Always go with hard copies with these books. You’ll want to mark pages, take notes, etc. 
 #5. Formatting Lives Matters If you’re reading this, then there’s a 99% chance you’re writing on the interwebs. That means you MUST format properly - if you want people to read your stuff. 
 NO ONE READS ONLINE. People skim. If your shit is interesting, they’ll dig deeper. 
 If you write block text in 2018, your content won’t get read online. Punto. Blanco. Periodo. 
 Break your content up. Use headlines, sub-headers, and short paragraphs. In every single piece of content. Whether it be sales copy or a blog post. 
 Oh, and learn how to craft the perfect headline, too: https://t.co/wsxYtd9AHi 
 #6. Features Vs. Benefits I won’t get too much into this one here. But the gist of it is this… Focus on benefits more than features. 
 What does this mean? It can be niche specific and related to the type of content, but… Basically, it means most humans need to understand why something would benefit them or why they should buy it. Not exactly why it works. 
 For example: You have a minor injury. You’ve heard about peptides like TB500 for wound healing. You don’t need to understand the mechanisms behind how they work. How they heal. You only care about if they’ll benefit you. If TB500 will help you get rid of your injury quicker. 
 And if the product causes cancer or not ;( 
 #7. Well… That’s the secret sauce. The easiest way to use process and improve your writing ability. A system to finding your voice and making shit sound suave. 
 Ok, maybe it&apos;s not so secret - or even that saucy. Just a process I&apos;m working on when crafting content. 
 If that’s of interest to ya, sign up below. Email going out on dialing in your content creation process in 30 minutes: https://t.co/IdruXe570s</texto><total_retweets type="int">86</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">549</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">35</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">742780196948824064</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">10140</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">423</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">11196</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1044049431724807</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>