<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">114</hilo><total_tweets type="int">12</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ I think I&apos;ve figured out the significance of Snow White and Godfather III signatures in the real #qanon&apos;s posts and why they were posted together so often. https://t.co/D2TneofQnG 
 2/ We have confirmation that Snow White refers to the Clowns supercomputers from #qanon directly. But he also says: Go deeper. Signatures are IMPORTANT. 
 3/ The two &apos;signatures&apos; - Snow White and Godfather III - were posted together by Q over a dozen times. Godfather III could refer to something like the Pope giving up control of the Vatican to a mafioso in exchange for financial help. But I believe the key is in a quote. 
 4/ This is one of the first lines in Godfather III: &quot;The only wealth in this world is children; more than all the money, power on earth, you are my treasure.&quot; - Michael Corleone I think this is what we&apos;re supposed to focus on. #qanon 
 5/ Child trafficking must require enormous logistics and tracking capability, especially because it has to be ultra secret. What if #qanon was telling us that the Clowns&apos; supercomputers actually did all the tracking? 
 6/ The puppet masters (+++ and ++) financed and brokered the trafficking, the puppets (BHO, HRC and others) made sure the distribution happened and the Clowns In Action took care of all the global tracking and logistics. #qanon 
 7/ #qanon also connects Deep Dream, a thinly disguised Facebook in the 2016 Jason Bourne movie, to Snow White as well as Hillary and SA directly to it as well. POTUS also hinted the other day that the Jason Bourne reference was Amazon - which hosts the Clown&apos;s computers. https://t.co/Dcav7bCvYN 
 8/ And there&apos;s also this horrifying drop that lends some support to my interpretation: ... Who is the &apos;broker&apos; for underage sex? Think SA. How does FB &amp;amp; Instagram play a role in capture? Think &apos;Taken&apos;. Fantasy right? Yeah, obviously it isn&apos;t. #qanon 
 9/ #qanon seems to make all these connections between social media and child trafficking explicit in this post here. https://t.co/5QxN5kYWJd 
 10/ To summarize: major social media orgs feed product into the global child trafficking networks BY DESIGN and with help from the Clowns. The Clownstream media won&apos;t report any of this properly. Oh yeah, and A Cooper is a pedo. But we knew that already. #qanon https://t.co/aVSE88AQEk 
 11/ Little wonder that #pizzagate was instantly and universally derided across the MSM or that Reddit shut down /r/pizzagate and /r/cbts_stream or that YouTube has done nothing about #elsagate or Twitter #twittergate. It&apos;s all part of the same giant web. #qanon 
 12/ The ramifications of all this will be cataclysmic on the media as a whole, both digital and traditional. From @realDonaldTrump&apos;s Dec 21 2017 EO: All property and interests in property that are in the United States... of the following persons are BLOCKED ... #qanon</texto><total_retweets type="int">45</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">129</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">25</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">4</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">56649139</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">6242</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1374</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">11592</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9171376798060378</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>