<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">15</hilo><total_tweets type="int">9</total_tweets><texto type="str">Hmmm...Q is on the hunt for @Snowden. This looks like it could be Hong Kong. I lived there from 1976-1980. A lot has changed, no doubt, but it sure looks that way. The guy in the center of the crowd could be him? https://t.co/Wh29gBoHmQ 
 2. Q appears to want us to push this hash tag: #internetbillofrights. https://t.co/3QiuaWQ2G0 
 3. Q tells us the #internetbillofrights has nothing to do with AT&amp;amp;T. This scares the Clowns more than anything because they will no longer control the msg. Yes, we have the 1st Amendment &amp;amp; yes, these are private companies BUT they are censoring conservative voices. That&apos;s not OK. https://t.co/ZA921vgplV 
 4. Just a theory here but IF Snowden has flipped because he is now, according to Q, a &quot;liability&quot; to Clowns (like JP Barlow, who was 187&apos;ed, became), is Q Team, w/China&apos;s assistance helping him clear customs? Is Snowden evading capture by Clowns? https://t.co/nLDiYEdO7K 
 5. It seems pretty clear CLOWNS control social media. Eric Schmidt (former Google CEO) likely wrote the code to censor across platforms. I&apos;m guessing Russia, China, &amp;amp; HK probably were sold this code by ES (or via HRC selling access to her unclass server?). https://t.co/rHiuN6p8JZ 
 6. An anon responding to Q&apos;s question &quot;Who performs in a circus?&quot; (I thought the answer was CLOWNS), mentioned Snowden&apos;s girlfriend. Q asks who the father is. His name is Jonathan Mills (need to dig into his background). https://t.co/YtGVENCGCu https://t.co/nzrJ6MZ7e7 
 7. Q responds to an anon who had concerns about IBOR. Q clarifies 1st Amendment can&apos;t be enforced upon private companies. Yes, they risk losing cash but Clowns make up for it (e.g. OUR TAX PAYER DOLLARS!). There must be a way to prove that if WE are funding, we should control! https://t.co/A0P2C8gWl1 
 8. This anon did a great breakdown of a potential timeline for Q&apos;s use of &quot;BOOM&quot; in multiple drops. Sounds plausible. We shall see what happens in the news tomorrow if the ref to &quot;-24&quot; is some kind of op (Snowden extraction from HK?) and only IF the MSM (maybe only FNC?) reports. https://t.co/L193DepFS0 
 @threadreaderapp please unroll.</texto><total_retweets type="int">1644</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2556</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">291</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">9427572</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">133320</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14423</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">39842</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.993373408952516</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>