<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">79</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">I&apos;m a &quot;Hollywood Liberal&quot; Ted. I like to put my hard earned $$ behind candidates who unlike you, do not take 11 MILLION $$ into your Super PAC from the Mercers or use Cambridge Analytica&apos;s stolen data to influence the outcome of your campaign #BetoForTexas @Rosie @chelseahandler https://t.co/8h7tHqwq6u 
 When the Mercers were backing #NeverTrump candidate @tedcruz-- &quot;the Cruz camp dropped $5.8 million with the Cambridge Analytica -- spending $3 million with the company as early as February. &quot; 5.8 Million for Stolen Data... #BetoForTexas https://t.co/F2wsIKlHC4 
 3. As a &quot;Hollywood Liberal&quot; @tedcruz I prefer to give my $$ and support to candidates who do not foment hate and virulent Islamophobia like you and associate with hate groups like Pamela Geller&apos;s who is banned from entering the UK. #BetoForTexas https://t.co/tqtVv6zKBv 
 4. As a &quot;Hollywood Liberal&quot; @tedcruz I prefer to support candidates like @BetoORourke who unlike you don&apos;t have Senior Advisors like Nick Muzin who was hired by Russian-Linked Shell Company to Boost Albania’s Right-Wing Party in DC https://t.co/EekkIE2zYB 
 5. As a &quot;Hollywood Liberal&quot; Ted, I like candidates like @BetoORourke who doesn&apos;t party with and invite Russian linked Albanian politicians accused of corruption like Lulzim Basha and Fatmir Mediu to the inauguration in Jan. https://t.co/hsIxnGWOS7 
 6. As a &quot;Hollywood Liberal&quot; Ted I prefer candidates like #BetoORourke who don&apos;t make &quot;hating Muslims mainstream&quot; like you do. You are part of a global Islamophobia racket along with virulent xenophobes, Frank Gaffney and John Bolton who you&apos;ve endorsed to replace Flynn https://t.co/MAXIr3eDJ4 
 We now know from @washingtonpost Mercers &amp;amp; Bannon were in discussion with #SCL/#CambridgeAnalytica/#AlexanderNix in 2014, so this Apr. 2015 article &quot;Securing the backing of the Mercers is huge for Ted Cruz&quot; puts his #NeverTrump candidacy in a new light. https://t.co/V5jhQNpbEV</texto><total_retweets type="int">1147</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2362</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">85</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Disgust</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">464419646</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">16544</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1086</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">29369</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0451999137851007</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>