<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">58</hilo><total_tweets type="int">6</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ Understanding gun laws: The #DefaultProceed or &quot;Charleston Loophole&quot; The #NRA killed Brady Bill&apos;s provision buyers complete full background check before getting the gun. With NRAs &quot;instant&quot; background check system, if FBI can&apos;t complete review within 3 days, you get the gun! https://t.co/pPf9FzMgM2 
 2/ Understanding gun laws: &quot;Gun show loophole&quot; Only licensed sellers have to run a background check. Per federal law, private sellers do not. Only 9 states and DC require background checks on private sales of all types of guns. #GunReformNow #MarchForOurLives https://t.co/obyTBWci2k 
 3/ Understanding gun laws: CAP Laws (Child Access Protection) In 2015 &amp;amp; 2016, more toddlers killed Americans than terrorists. Kids accessed parents&apos; guns &amp;amp; pulled the trigger, killing themselves or family. 21 states have no CAP laws to prosecute negligent parents. #GunReformNow https://t.co/jhqEuUWoa4 
 4/ Understanding gun laws: Immunity for Gun Manufacturers 33 states protect manufacturers from liability. Unlike many products which have reduced deaths through safety improvements, guns are still produced without a manual safety latch to prevent a child from pulling a trigger https://t.co/qPFcV130gF 
 5/ Understanding gun laws: Federal Age Requirements School shootings by AR-15 rifles are now commonplace. Few know, however, that federal law provides no minimum age for the possession of long rifles and ammunition. #GunReformNow #MarchForOurLives #GunControlNow https://t.co/Czh4YDrut9 
 6/ Understanding Gun Laws: &quot;Straw Purchase&quot; Buying a gun for someone else. Illegal because they help criminals circumvent background checks. The San Bernardino shooter got guns this way. The NRA fought to overturn the ban on straw purchases, but narrowly lost 5-4 #GunReformNow https://t.co/McnFu6YwoE</texto><total_retweets type="int">7282</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">10290</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">96</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">5</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">997682274</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">79012</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">51828</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">39155</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8570541836945618</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>