<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">241</hilo><total_tweets type="int">18</total_tweets><texto type="str">So it&apos;s very common for writers to ask why agents don&apos;t give feedback. The answer, usually, is that we&apos;re busy--but that&apos;s hard to grasp on a concrete level. Today, the lovely and talented @BenFaulknerEd mentioned reading tons, and out of curiosity, I did the math to compare. 
 So we get (I did the math awhile ago) an average of 39.98 queries a workday times 5 days = 2,158 pages/month from queries. I probably read an average of 2/10 of the included pages, so that&apos;s 1 query + 2 pages times 2,158 = 6,474 pages/month. 
 For the 2/10, keep in mind that there are a LOT of &quot;Dear Sirs&quot; and &quot;I have published the next bestseller please take it on or else here&apos;s my number&quot; queries. At time of tweeting, I have 6 &quot;Dear Sir/Madam,&quot; 2 &quot;Next bestseller,&quot; and 1 &quot;Next JK Rowling&quot; queries waiting. So. 
 With a 7.5% request rate (2.99/day times 5 (M-F) times 4 (weeks in month) = 59.97 manuscripts. If I read 20 pages each on average (keep in mind many are picture books), that&apos;s 1,199.4 pages of requested material/month + 6,474 unrequested = 7,673.4 pages a month of submissions. 
 Now, I strongly suspect the 7.5 percent is high (this was calculated maybe two years ago?). But even say it&apos;s 3 percent now, that&apos;s 1.1994 requests a day, times 5 (M-F), times 4 (weeks) times 20 (average pages read) = 479.76 requested pages read/month. 
 So, yes, we are busy. No, we are not sitting here cackling like &quot;Haha, I know exactly how to fix her manuscript, and I&apos;m not telling her! Why? Because! Bwahahahaa!&quot; Much as I receive a lot of correspondence to this effect. 
 Do I try to keep up? Yes! Do I achieve inbox zero? No! Inbox 100? No. Do I try to keep in touch about delays? Yes! Do I always manage to check in with everyone when things take a long time? Sadly, no. Am I constantly feeling guilt about making so many people wait? Yes. Yes, I am. 
 I suspect a lot of agents have similar inboxes (I&apos;ve heard everywhere from 10-50 average queries a day). Many probably have lower request rates (perhaps closer to 1-2%). Many have assistants, interns, teams. However, I suspect that 0% of agents enjoy making writers wait. 
 Keep in mind that I don&apos;t get all day to read submissions. I actually spend more time on clients, meetings, my own submissions, contracts, and the like. I&apos;m pretty much reading during downtime--evenings, weekends, subway, train trips, plane trips, waiting in line. 
 Things I could do to be faster (of course I&apos;ve considered them!): 1) Not respond to queries. This would save about 30 seconds from each, times 39.98 times 5 (M-F) times 4 (weeks) divided by 60 (convert to minutes) = 399.8 minutes a month, or 6.6633 hours. 
 2) Let readers make all of the query requesting decisions for me. Now, if you know me at all, you know I am waaaaayyyyyy too much of a control freak to let that happen. I read all queries myself. 3) Manuscripts--same. 
 4) Drink more coffee, sleep less. I&apos;m up to two coffees a day, one tea. Just tried the Starbucks app for the first time today (it was weird--too easy). I think that&apos;s enough. Otherwise I&apos;ll just run around all day. And bad things happen fast if I don&apos;t sleep. 
 5) Give Up Everything Fun And Just Be An Efficient Human, Dammit: Believe me, I&apos;ve tried. Strangely, this makes me miserable and worse at my job. I do need some degree of happiness in my life to be able to function as a creative person--which an agent is. Always. So. That&apos;s out. 
 So, that&apos;s where I&apos;m at. Do I still expect lots of &quot;Agents are so mean because they don&apos;t give feedback&quot; emails? Yes. And the check-ins at three weeks? And the &quot;I am so tired of agents being SO UNPROFESSIONAL and NOT GIVING ANY FEEDBACK&quot; tweets? Yes. 
 And there&apos;s one now. Cool. 
 You may be asking, &quot;Jessica! Why in the world are you doing side projects when you have all of this happening?&quot; The answer is that, for me, it&apos;s easier to keep moving. A change, for me, even if just a setting (office vs coworking space vs home) is more restorative than a rest. 
 And I get genuine energy and pleasure out of connecting people. I think all agents do. Makes me feel like what I do is meaningful. And that means so much more than numbers could. 
 Do I suspect some agents just manage to be faster through...magic? Better systems? Better coffee? Not sleeping? Working harder? Being better at life? Yes. Definitely. This is just where I&apos;m at, now. Catch me in a few years, and things may be very different.</texto><total_retweets type="int">206</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">1635</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">108</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">288260844</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">25970</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">6564</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">58194</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9163947615745573</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>