<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">152</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">TECHNOLOGY INTELLIGENCE MEDIA This concept was touched on in my last thread of #DrainTheSwampUK but since listening to #EricRWeinstein discuss this on the #RubinReport I feel it needs a thread to explain it properly. See link from 90mins onwards. https://t.co/DvqdaNTqiG #TIM 
 The battle for our futures will be fought over who controls the information that we see rather than on any battlefield in the traditional sense, but make no mistake this battle has been going on for years and will continue to be fought for years too this is the #Swamp. #TIM 
 In Europe the #Swamp is the #EU working with big corporations to maintain control over the population. In the #US the #Swamp is also the giant technology companies working in conjunction with the #MSM &amp;amp; the Intelligence Community to spy on us. #TIM #DrainTheSwampUK #DrainTheSwamp 
 Exactly how much information about each and every one of us is stored on servers held by the big technology companies with or without our knowledge, consent or even permission? If anyone has ideas contrary to the group think of Silicon Valley they are to be destroyed by MSM. #TIM 
 #Milo #BretWeinstein #JamesDamore #JordanBPeterson #NewWorldHominin have been recent victims of this attack on free speech &amp;amp; the #RegressiveLeft despite massive pressure put on them especially by the media what has set these people apart has been their ability not to cave to #TIM 
 At the same time who will be the next victim of #TIM we hear about because they do not cave in, this is something we should all be watching out for &amp;amp; protecting. These are the people who are standing up against so-called #ResistingHate or who dare to challenge the #TIM narrative. 
 However, how many people have either been cowed or intimidated by the #TIM cabal, people who have had their lives destroyed because they were not able to cope with the pressure of the #SPLC, #ResistingHate or the #MSM and their hate-fuelled followers? We will simply never know. 
 #Antifa #BLM &amp;amp; #Momentum have all been given the chance to spew their divisive, regressive propaganda &amp;amp; yet the silent majority has decided to stay silent or ignorant &amp;amp; are not prepared to fight against #TIM #TRobinsonNewEra &amp;amp; #KTHopkins are great examples of this push back. 
 What scares #TIM the most are people who can&apos;t be intimidated into silence &amp;amp; new media outlets they are unable to control or gather information on. These new media platforms need to be supported &amp;amp; encouraged as much as possible to avoid the lies &amp;amp; control by the #Swamp and #TIM 
 Culture&apos;s always upstream from politics &amp;amp; the #RegressiveLeft are dominating the culture war &amp;amp; are being assisted by the Left wing media coupled with the giant technology companies, this has to be countered as much as possible in order to destroy the stranglehold of #TIM &amp;amp; #Swamp 
 @Breitbart @PrisonPlanet @AltNewsMedia @TheRebelTV are all shining lights in the culture war which needs to be won, if we want to live in a world where the #RegressiveLeft and #TIM can be defeated by better ideas and access to information which is not for sale but more is needed. 
 The first thing the #RegressiveLeft do with #TIM is to label these sites as #FarRight in a blatant attempt to close them down or frighten people from following them, the guilt by association tactic, then unsubstantiated hit-pieces are written by agenda driven ‘journalists.’ 
 People have thought #TheMemo was the big story but in actual fact, this is the real one in terms of who can have access to your information, how easily they are able to gain it &amp;amp; the damage they can do with it. #TIM must first be challenged &amp;amp; then destroyed completely. 
 Please read &amp;amp; RT this thread as it can&apos;t be stressed how important the battle for the control of information actually is. The side who controls the information, controls the narrative &amp;amp; in essence #TIM &amp;amp; the ability to prevent #DrainTheSwampUK &amp;amp; #DrainTheSwamp it is that simple.</texto><total_retweets type="int">43</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">47</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">15</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">24</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Anger</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">856184187057057797</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">5400</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">751</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">64997</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9629165157321219</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>