<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">229</hilo><total_tweets type="int">17</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. David J Kramer: The guy who is the key in linking John McCain to the Trump-Russia &quot;Dossier&quot;. By now if you are not familiar with the dossier or the &quot;Circle of Filth&quot; you are welcome to partake of my voluminous and somewhat odium inducing works. https://t.co/uTx82h3UzU 
 2. Devin Nunes issued subpoena to David Kramer, who, in late November 2016, traveled to London to receive briefing and a copy of the dossier from its author, British spy Christopher Steele. Kramer returned to U.S. to give the document to Sen. John McCain.https://t.co/GWmgEUEM04 
 3. McCain later took copy of the dossier to James Comey. But FBI already had the document; Steele himself gave the dossier to FBI in installments, reportedly beginning in early July 2016. Kramer has already been interviewed once by the House Intelligence Committee on Dec. 19. 
 4. During that interview Kramer told House investigators he knew identities of Russian sources for the allegations in dossier. But when investigators pressed Kramer to reveal names, he declined to do so. McCain, thus far has refused to detail his actions regarding the dossier. 
 5. Knowing the sources of the Dossier is critical, but we do not even know if there is ANY thing factually correct about the dossier. So now Kramer has a subpoena to appear on Jan 11th 2018. Everyone wants to know what Kramer knows. 
 6. Kramer is Affiliated Senior Fellow at McCain Institute for International Leadership at Arizona State University. Kramer joined McCain Institute as senior November 2014. Before that he served as president of Freedom House. &amp;amp; Transatlantic Fellow at German Marshall Fund 
 7. Yes.... The McCain Institute for international leadership. Can you say oxymoron? All moron, no oxygen. https://t.co/m8PqWyBMf3 
 8. Kramer served eight years in the U.S. Department of State, including Assistant Secretary of State for Democracy, Human Rights, Labor; Deputy Assistant Secretary of State for European and Eurasian Affairs responsible for Russia, Ukraine, Moldova and Belarus affairs 
 9. Russia? Did you say Russia? Yes I said Russia. Read his bio in #7 please! What the hell! What did he do before joining the US government? 
 10. Before joining U.S. Government, Kramer was Senior Fellow, New American Century, Associate Director of Russian and Eurasian Program at Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Assistant Director of Russian and Eurasian Studies at Center for Strategic International Studies 
 11. Wait so he was a &quot;Russia Expert&quot; even before he entered the US Dept of Statre? Yes, its in his bio, why don&apos;t you just read it instead of asking again. https://t.co/kNtxuTroKD 
 12. If you are so inclined here is The Association of Diplomatic Studies and Training interview in its entirety. Its truly hypnagogic so read at your own peril. https://t.co/9lY4lHZGLd 
 13. But I know you the reader prefer the short version: So here are the screen shots of all &quot;Russia&quot; pages: https://t.co/s1Zcxeg2NB 
 14. Here are some more: To Recap: Kramer is a Russia expert of Sorts. the fact that he is involved with the Trump-Russia Dossier is not some accident. There are no accidents in the &quot;Circle of Filth. He knows and holds some key information that should be stunning when revealed. https://t.co/GJ5M1RM8j9 
 15. Why does John McCain appear to have independently alerted the FBI via Kramer to the Dossier? And the FBI already knew about the dossier through Steele but Rod Rosenstein will not answer if FBI paid for it. How peculiar! https://t.co/TjIOJWdsP9 
 16. McCain famously said: “Upon examination of contents, unable to make judgment about their accuracy, I delivered information to the director of the FBI, That has been the extent of my contact with FBI or any other government agency regarding this issue&quot; https://t.co/Xm5JbQZRQi 
 17. John McCain and David Kramer are now inducted into the ever burgeoning ranks of the &quot;Circle of Filth&quot; - &quot;One cannot blame an organization that picks up an occasional black sheep, one only takes exception if it retains an accumulation of them&quot; -Dion fortune</texto><total_retweets type="int">1430</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2626</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">83</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">879548970082721792</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">51217</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2940</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">38261</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0539169429458746</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>