<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">139</hilo><total_tweets type="int">11</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) It dawned on me w the last #Q post dropped overnight. It&apos;s a new phase: something wonderful happening in our little world, #FollowTheWhiteRabbit. #QAnon #MAGA #Crumbs #TheGreatAwakening #QAnon #InternetBillofRights #DeepStateinPanic #WeThePeople #TheStormIsHere @POTUS #IBOR https://t.co/FFbGp2mdUa 
 2) #Q posted a link to a show called &quot;The Opposition w/ Jordan Klepper&quot; in which our little secret was given the #leftist treatment, whereby we&apos;re ridiculed heavily, and all our work labelled &quot;the sum of all conspiracy theories. It was framed in the theme of the film #TheMatrix. https://t.co/1GMuWH2q2s 
 3) Watch it. For anyone that considers this demoralizing, do not! It&apos;s brilliant! Not only did we get a bunch of potential new eyes for being #RedPilled, but #QAnon messages were shown, and #TheStorm mentioned. https://t.co/XgnWubvZJe—of-montreal-season-1-ep-1080 #QAnon #MAGA https://t.co/8gdbCwn8wv 
 4) Why shouldn&apos;t it be demoralizing? &quot;First they ignore you, then they ridicule you, then they fight you, then you win.&quot; We&apos;re past the ignore phase. We&apos;re at the beginning of the ridicule phase. #Crumbs #TheGreatAwakening #QAnon #InternetBillofRights #DeepStateinPanic 
 5) In the ridicule phase, we need to steady confidence of all the evidence #Anons have piled up: - Calm and well written comments &amp;amp; response - Leave out most extreme stuff - No 40 emoji usernames - No religious jargon - Facts, facts, facts - Links, attribution &amp;amp;source documents 
 6) What has @POTUS done all this time as #president? He&apos;s allowed himself to be the target of endless ridicule. It&apos;s been intentional. He looks weak in the eyes of his enemies, when in reality he is surrounding them. We&apos;re a part of that. #DeepStateinPanic #WeThePeople #TheStorm https://t.co/Vm4Hf6S8Yj 
 7) We&apos;re being drawn into this battle using the same tactics, and we need to be armed with our tools. Everyone one of you knows how this battle is being one, how brilliantly this is being executed. #TrustThePlan. The cognitive dissonance on the horizon is going to be epic fun. https://t.co/1040on82vU 
 8) Remember all the quiet #winning that has been happening. All by stealth. 4D chess. Slowly all these #SwampCreatures are being reeled in. https://t.co/HiJoFyXIrx https://t.co/IQqArW1nS6 
 9) Look at #Facebookgate, they&apos;re falling right into our hands. What better poster child do we need for an #InternetBillOfRights than #Facebook? It&apos;s their own behavior, their own symbolism, and their own arrogance that will be their downfall. #WeThePeople #BigData @POTUS #IBOR https://t.co/LgzrPtPeqN 
 10) I anticipate the #DeepState &amp;amp; #MSM #FakeNewsMedia will have a field day with us. Welcome it. It will be a huge sign of progress. I believe this dance with #QAnon and @POTUS requires the #left to blast away, because the deeper they ridicule, the more impactful the aftermath. 
 11) Once the wreckage is clear, this is ours to mold into a more perfect world. Don&apos;t forget all the other nations that need to have their own #GreatAwakening. We&apos;re starting this, but it&apos;s a #GreatAwakeningWorldwide. #QAnon #MAGA #TheStormIsHere #DeepStateinPanic #WeThePeople https://t.co/5ke1PQZbMv</texto><total_retweets type="int">56</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">135</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">12</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">30</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1623794972</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">11222</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">39</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">10786</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.5565009939878032</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>