<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">10</hilo><total_tweets type="int">5</total_tweets><texto type="str">This is wrong. The judge can/will make a condition of/clause in any probation, suspended sentence, deferred sentence, or sentencing order that Papadopoulos comply with all prior orders and/or agreements regarding his cooperation with the Trump-Russia probe. A very bad take here. https://t.co/78Gltwf6Q6 
 2/ Papadopoulos failing to live by his agreements with the feds/the court could lead to charges being brought forward that were previously withheld and/or contempt charges and/or reopening investigations otherwise on hold. None of the conditions Joyce said could be present exist. 
 3/ The idea Mueller would dump Papadopoulos as a witness just because his sentencing—which will have conditions attached to it—can&apos;t be forestalled forever is ridiculous, and has nothing to do with any reality within the criminal justice system federally or at the state level. 
 4/ I should also add, as I accidentally left it out of Tweet #2, that should Papadopoulos have a suspended or deferred sentence, or probation of any kind, any violation of any conditions of those statuses could lead to immediate imposition of some or all of a prison sentence. 
 5/ The chances Papadopoulos will be under court supervision for some period of time approach 100%, and prosecutors will ensure it&apos;s longer than the Trump-Russia probe. His sentencing will also acknowledge that the feds are withholding charges in consideration of his cooperation.</texto><total_retweets type="int">589</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">2386</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">58</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">3223426134</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">670013</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">37</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">51875</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">2.258361470728224</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>