<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">360</hilo><total_tweets type="int">30</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) A few people predicted that Trump would be elected, some at his first announcement, others later (like myself, May &apos;16). But who predicted the storm? Exhibit A: https://t.co/mJNqDeYkgh @EntheosShines @SaRaAshcraft @Annakhait @Kupi_Zak @LisaMei62 #TheStormIsHere #MAGA #QAnon 
 @EntheosShines @SaRaAshcraft @Annakhait @Kupi_Zak @LisaMei62 2) Hold with me here. I know even Trump supporters have been skeptical about Trump-related prophecies. I was too, &amp;amp; thought they were all hokey; I didn&apos;t even touch this one until someone insisted shortly after the election that it was 100% accurate. I listened, and was stunned. 
 @EntheosShines @SaRaAshcraft @Annakhait @Kupi_Zak @LisaMei62 3) Keep in mind that the author, Mark Taylor, says he wrote this down in 4/28/11, after seeing Trump talk about running. There&apos;s no evidential proof of this, but the fulfillments since the broadcast above dating 4/18/16 are astounding enough. https://t.co/NJ1u6PuFjq 
 4) He was just a retired fireman, doing his thing, when suddenly he started having these eye-opening experiences. https://t.co/WrJe4mc7Fk 
 5) (On a personal note, I remember being moved at the time by the idea of Trump running, given that he understands business from the inside out, in the wake of Ron Paul losing the race, thinking he was at least second best, and could sweep the field even in mid-2012.) 
 6) (I also initiated a fervent prayer in the wake of that loss in a Ron Paul group that God would raise up somebody... or do something... to alleviate our distress!) 
 7) Now I think our prayers have to some measure finally been answered. I&apos;ll just go line by line here and chime in where I think the fulfillments thus far can be further elaborated on. 
 8) &quot;The Spirit of God says, I have chosen this man, DT, for such a time as this.&quot; Think if Trump really had run in &apos;12. SJW nonsense was not at fever pitch, &amp;amp; the opposition would not have looked as ridiculous as in &apos;16. Nor were people as desperate even then as this last cycle. 
 9) Not only that, but many have suspected that HRC would&apos;ve tipped the scales into full-scale totalitarianism. They&apos;ve dominated the DNC for decades and pull the most strings out of any other politicians in the world. Think the revolutions under Obama x10. https://t.co/vztyLW99x9 
 10) &quot;For as Benjamin Netanyahu is to lsrael, so shall this man be to the United States of America!&quot; This is beyond my depth to speak on, but I&apos;m sure others can chime in here. However, it brings to mind the new relationship of the US to Israel, which we&apos;ll dive into later. https://t.co/QX9Q0iqnSw 
 11) &quot;For I will use this man to bring honor, respect and restoration to America.&quot; Despite what t/ shrieking media propagandists have proclaimed, Trump has brought NATO to their knees, &amp;amp; won t/ adulation &amp;amp; collaboration of East Asia. Compare to China making Obama bend the knee. https://t.co/xenwnXWq5z 
 12) &quot;America will be respected once again as the most powerful and prosperous nation on earth, (other than lsrael).&quot; This is already taking shape as t/ swamp is drained. Not sure what&apos;s meant by &quot;other than Israel&quot; but perhaps simply means Israel similarly powerful &amp;amp; prosperous. 
 13) &quot;The dollar will be the strongest it has ever been in the history of the United States, and will once again be the currency by which all others are judged.&quot; Now this one&apos;s interesting. I subscribe to the Austrian school which predicts a big market crash in the future. https://t.co/yarAb6XCLI 
 14) However if real economic value is created at ground level thru small business esp with massive tax/spending cuts, this could conceivably be counteracted &amp;amp; a cushion created to bounce back by. As we can see, t/stock market rises &amp;amp; falls with the possibility of Trump&apos;s success. https://t.co/y0zT5HdDN1 
 15) &quot;The Spirit of God says, the enemy will quake and shake and fear this man I have anointed. They will even quake and shake when he announces he is running for president, it will be like the shot heard across the world.&quot; Hillary quote source: https://t.co/dcnVkSMWnD https://t.co/jsfe0sUaLf 
 16) &quot;The enemy will say what shall we do now? This man knows all our tricks and schemes. We have been robbing America for decades, what shall we do to stop this?&quot; This is one of the first @Imperator_Rex3 threads I ever read. 100% relevant: https://t.co/Qy5BsIf1RJ 
 17) The last quoted line is pretty interesting, too, given that Taylor knew almost nothing of Trump. 
 18) &quot;The Spirit says HA! No one shall stop this that l have started! For t/ Enemy has stolen from America for decades &amp;amp; it stops now! For I will use this man to reap t/ harvest that t/ US has sown for and plunder from t/ Enemy what he has stolen &amp;amp; return it 7 fold back to t/ US.&quot; 
 19) I mean, the new corporate tax cuts alone... 
 20) &quot;The Enemy will say... what @ Israel? For Israel will be protected by America once again... America will once again stand hand &amp;amp; hand w Israel, &amp;amp; the 2 shall be as one. For t/ ties between Israel &amp;amp; America will be stronger than ever, &amp;amp; Israel will flourish like never before.&quot; https://t.co/UHCel9jNmX 
 21) &quot;The Spirit of God says, I will protect America and lsrael, for this next president will be a man of his word, when he speaks the world will listen and know that there is something greater in him than all the others before him.&quot; https://t.co/Ho7OLAG2bY 
 22) &quot;This man&apos;s word is his bond and the world and America will know this and the enemy will fear this, for this man will be fearless.&quot; &quot;Fearless.&quot; Remember this? There was a gun threat &amp;amp; DJT just stood cold staring right into danger. They had to pry him away against his will. https://t.co/GVD4VL6NuM 
 23) &quot;The Spirit says, when the financial harvest begins so shall it parallel in the spiritual for America.&quot; &quot;Spiritual&quot; can mean many things to many people. But at the very least there&apos;s been a steady rise in optimism &amp;amp; hope. As @ScottAdamsSays, there&apos;s talk of a new Golden Age. 
 24) &quot;The Spirit of God says, in this next election they will spend billions to keep this president in; it will be like flushing their money down the toilet. Let them waste their money...&quot; (It woulda basically been a continuation of Obama. But more is explained in the broadcast.) https://t.co/OiGOjo2LLz 
 25) &quot;...for it comes from and it is being used by evil forces at work...&quot; https://t.co/cQX5YdGWOA 
 26) &quot;...but they will not succeed, for this next election will be a clean sweep for the man I have chosen.&quot; Sure, some of us foresaw this, but just *look* at it... &quot;clean sweep&quot; is the word practically *everyone* was using... https://t.co/ALETg62e3i 
 27) &quot;They will say things about this man (the enemy), but it will not affect him, and they shall say it rolls off of him like the duck, for as the feathers of a duck protect it, so shall my feathers protect this next president.&quot; Ha ha... ha ha ha ha ha... https://t.co/lgteLTVKLk 
 28) &quot;Even the [MSM] will be captivated by this man &amp;amp; t/ abilities I&apos;ve gifted him with, &amp;amp; they&apos;ll even begin to agree w him, says t/ Spirit of God.&quot; Hmmmm... yeah, I&apos;d say they&apos;re pretty obsessed. 😉😂 Rarely is there agreement (yet), but there&apos;s growing recognition of success! 
 29) That&apos;s it for the prophecy, but there&apos;s more commentary to analyze, when I get more time (late in the morning here). Hint: the storm that&apos;s occurring right now is leading up to something epic... which is why I&apos;ve never really lapsed in faith that it&apos;d all turn out alright. 
 30) Oh, and just one more thing... the woman who&apos;s been passing this prophecy along to not only @TruNews but others, @AuthorMColbert, is a part of Trump&apos;s faith adviser team... so he surely knows about all this, including the (sneak preview) divinely promised military tribunals. https://t.co/hl8wGZxT9h</texto><total_retweets type="int">88</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">312</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">38</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">81676838</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">1225</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1518</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">20516</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7385980625419769</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>