<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">321</hilo><total_tweets type="int">25</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. #QAnon drops some real inside baseball tonight pertaining to #Q&apos;s foretold D5 Avalanche which began today. #Q #CrossfireHurricane https://t.co/tUF6XNWEY7 
 2. #QAnon&apos;s drop begins with reference to the meeting held in the White House today. #Q https://t.co/qWhQcagxYA https://t.co/hNvnAKzrNk 
 3. The meeting #QAnon cites was pre-planned, though not on the public schedule (saving more students&apos; lives that way?), planned to take place IMMEDIATELY after new CIA director sworn. Kelly added as surprise? FBI Dir Wray, DOJ Rosenstein, &amp;amp; Dan Coats&apos;re there. &quot;Think timing #Q&quot; https://t.co/hKv3SiOv0H 
 4. Compared to #QAnon&apos;s &quot;Full Disclosure. General Statement&quot;, the White House issued public statement about the meeting: IG&apos;s now tasked to expand investigation to include any irregularities w FBI’s or DOJ’s tactics concerning the Trump Campaign&quot;. #Q #CrossfireHurricane https://t.co/cdlgMY1RJZ 
 5. #QAnon&apos;s drop in a sense expands from the public statement the White House issued about the meeting, but first Q characterizes it as a &quot;Military OP. [Green] General K [JFK] #Q&quot; https://t.co/AbJyO4jgUU 
 6. #QAnon says we are engaged in a Military Operation (OP). Military oversight is needed because the corrupt aspects of the Hussein structured civilian intel agencies have committed the criminal acts that are being investigated. #Q https://t.co/J8diT4Hn8y 
 7. #Qanon reveals a [Green] light for General Kelly [JFK] to spearhead full disclosure of the truth of our country&apos;s (and foreign country&apos;s) intel op against Donald Trump. #Q 
 8. Some&apos;ve suggested that &quot;[Green]&quot; could refer to #QAnon&apos;s earlier post on Capt Mike Green who&apos;s killed in a plane crash during a military op concerning the Rothschilds. But whether this arcane notion is spurious awaits further confirmation. #Q https://t.co/pGEXGuxxO3 
 9. In response to #QAnon&apos;s drop, one anon notes that the IG is authorized to require the production of information by subpoena. #Q https://t.co/RWsal9NQIZ 
 10. Compred to the public statement released on today&apos;s White House meeting, this is the #Qanon one: &quot;Once the &apos;extremely guarded &amp;amp; highly classified&apos; information is finally revealed to House investigators, DNI, public etc., RR must recuse or [be] forcefully terminated.&quot; #Q https://t.co/YJStQtK0aK 
 11. #QAnon&apos;s been telling us of &quot;RR Problems&quot; for a while now. What was Rod Rosenstein&apos;s Senate Conf Vote? He was confirmed by a vote of 94-6, compared to Sessions&apos; very narrow margin. The #DeepState swamp trusts Rosenstein. #Q https://t.co/1CMSP3XYK0 
 12. #QAnon: &quot;WRAY reports to RR [important fact].&quot; FBI Director Wray reports to the Deputy AG (Rosenstein). A man we trust reports to a man we can&apos;t trust. #Q https://t.co/k3GdptOMVS 
 13. #QAnon asks if &quot;[RR] recuse/fired who has direct oversight of Mueller? Sessions un-recuse or #3 [until refill]? Who is Rachel Brand? Why was Rachel Brand dismissed? Think timing. #Q https://t.co/05I67LlInE 
 14. Rachel Brand was on #QAnon&apos;s recent house-cleaning list. #ClownMedia said she left for an offer too good to pass at WalMart. #Q said she was forced out. #Q https://t.co/tlgy2XPZEj 
 15. #QAnon quotes article noting that the President may choose someone else already Senate-confirmed in the exec branch (e.g. Pruitt) or Sr DOJ lawyer to serve as “acting” AAG in Brand&apos;s place &amp;amp; so to act in RR&apos;s place on temp basis for up to 210 days. https://t.co/e0OtPV6MwT #Q https://t.co/PDIJnSR9rD 
 17. #QAnon: &quot;210 days&quot;? The 2018 mid-term elections are 168 days from now. &quot;Think timing. &quot;Acting&quot; These people are stupid. #Q&quot; 
 18. #QAnon links to the DOJ page for our current Acting Associate Attorney General, Jesse Panuccio, but (cf above link) &quot;because Panuccio is not Senate-confirmed, he would not act as attorney general (or deputy attorney general) if those offices were also to become vacant.&quot; #Q https://t.co/8SwwLvxwpF 
 19. #QAnon&apos;s link to DOJ page: https://t.co/ZNQz1wcsF8 #Q 
 20. So, bottom line seems to be that #QAnon is noting that @POTUS hasplenty of time left to appoint an acting replacement for Rachel Brand, someone Senate confirmed who could act in RR&apos;s place. #Q 
 21. #QAnon: &quot;Why is Schneiderman&apos;s removal is &apos;extremely&apos; relevant? TRUST (name). #Q https://t.co/GRrl5YEtR9 
 22. #QAnon &quot;D5. #Q&quot; Dan 1. C 2. o 3. a 4. t 5. s ? https://t.co/d0M1zfnIZh 
 23. Most recent thread unroll is here: https://t.co/fURDPvtZgr 
 24. Prior #QAnon thread is unrolled here: https://t.co/wkq3MXuiHx 
 25. @threadreaderapp please unroll this latest #QAnon thread here: #Q #CrossfireHurricane https://t.co/xoz7uIccbC 
 26. #QAnon: Why&apos;d #Q refer to John F Kelly, &amp;amp; put the initials [JFK] into target brackets, when &quot;JFK&quot;, obviously, implies something else? More meaning? Is #Q not saying that military has green light for Op to thwart the #DeepState coup attempt? General Knowledge. Full Disclosure. https://t.co/7zBxtnLCSE</texto><total_retweets type="int">232</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">297</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">38</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">146456142</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">34111</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">14202</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">48494</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8797695640516863</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>