<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">108</hilo><total_tweets type="int">14</total_tweets><texto type="str">According to the Stasi GDR File, Hitler&apos;s daughter is now holding the same office as her father, Chancellor of Germany...said to be the most powerful human on Earth since she&apos;s also President of European Union &amp;amp; head of the Western Economic Block known as the G-8 #thestorm #qanon https://t.co/HOkvaxaCD6 
 In 1954, a baby girl was born, whom the Stasi File identifies as Angela Merkel, today’s Chancellor of Germany. Her official birthday is July 17, 1954. However, the Stasi file which is currently in the Soviet KGB archives, records her birth as April 20, 1954. https://t.co/7v8oHlQcKV 
 Hitler’s father, who took the name Hitler, was the illegitimate son of Solomon Rothschild’s mistress Anna Maria Schicklgruber. 
 Upon receipt of the Nazi files on artificial insemination, along with Hitler’s frozen sperm, the Soviet Politicheskoye Buro (Politburo) authorized the experiments to ‘resurrect’, ‘if possible’, a child bearing the ‘genetic markers’ of Adolph Hitler. https://t.co/V3R9rZof7P 
 Soon after the birth of Hitler’s baby girl, an agreement between the Soviets, the Americans and the Vatican was arranged. Hitler’s baby was placed under the ‘control’ of the Catholic Church through its ‘connections’ with the GDR Lutheran Church which took custody of the baby. 
 She was given a false date of birth, July 17, and the name Angela Dorothea Kasner, daughter of Horst Kasner, a Lutheran pastor, and his wife, Herlind – an English and Latin teacher. https://t.co/97ZZbhDDmP 
 There in the countryside at Templin in East Germany, Angela Merkel was raised about 50 miles north of Berlin, the capital of the socialist German Democratic Republic (GDR). https://t.co/sepLurB2Z3 
 The “agreement” of the Western Allied Powers, the Vatican, and the Soviets was that Hitler’s daughter would be elevated to international power…but her ascendancy to power would not come until “the Vatican also brought to power a German Pope”. https://t.co/opsBvzETXv 
 After the death of Pope John Paul II, the former German Nazi Joseph Ratzinger was nominated. He took the name of Pope Benedict XVI on April 20, 2005, as Vicar of Rome. Is it a coincidence that this date was the anniversary of Adolf Hitler’s birthday? https://t.co/ByJDQsnXng 
 In 1977, Angela Dorothea Kasner became Angela Merkel with her marriage to physicist Ulrich Merkel, but the marriage ended in divorce in 1982 🇩🇪She was elected Chancellor of Germany shortly after Pope Ratzinger assumed the Leadership of the Roman Church ... on Hitler’s birthday https://t.co/n16cYRvFTA 
 If the Soviet record is true, and the evidence is strong, it opens up some amazing possibilities. The undeniable fact is that Angela Merkel came from obscurity to triumviral power as German Chancellor, President of the European Union, and head of the powerful G-8 economic cartel. https://t.co/kqGmztq7Jj 
 Except for the little moustache, Merkel has a striking resemblance to Adolph Hitler. She is also a dead ringer for her mother – Gretl Braun Credit to: https://t.co/7eW0ks5bpJ https://t.co/OkmQIMJQgS 
 #Qanon Alludes to this fact pattern in Post 928 #TheStorm #TheGreatAwakening #SundayMorning https://t.co/vxBmXl8DBG https://t.co/Ts9lb6yAhy 
 POTUS’ recent Tweet relevant here. EU. Enough is enough. She was warned. Q #qanon #TheStorm #TheGreatAwakening https://t.co/OzjKAXfXcd</texto><total_retweets type="int">201</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">206</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">42</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">6</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">48499287</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">7099</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">7788</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">37331</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7873398250055945</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>