<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">74</hilo><total_tweets type="int">7</total_tweets><texto type="str">BOOM! Zuckerberg interview by @nxthompson is more substantial than CNN TV interview. Gets into #CambridgeAnalytica #CambridgeAnalytics https://t.co/CB1Y99qmm3 
 “And the other thing I’d say is that we have temporarily paused the audit to cede to the UK regulator, the @ICOnews, so that they can do a government investigation—I think it might be a criminal investigation, but it’s a government investigation at a minimum.” -Zuck 
 As far as I can tell, CA/SCL is not cooperating with @ICOnews. They are being defiant scoundrels. I do not understand why Zuck was dumb enough to hire Stroz Friedberg who did the whitewash AlfaBank/TrumptTower report for Trump appointee. 
 I&apos;m still waiting for Zuck to be asked why he allowed CA/SCL to upload their data into Facebook using Custom Audiences during the summer of 2016. He sent in embedded employees (interviewed by Mueller) to work alongside CA/SCL sharing data. 
 I&apos;m still waiting for Zuck to be asked by he hired Joseph Chancellor from GSR, Kogan&apos;s partner. How can he justify the above? 
 I&apos;m still waiting for Zuck to acknowledge that I&apos;ve accomplished more than him and I have no resources and he has virtually unlimited resources. 
 Zuck should sponsor my personal (cyber)defense force to take these bastards on. https://t.co/eRSQ5QvT08</texto><total_retweets type="int">356</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">704</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">33</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">15384720</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">38663</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">4112</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">37503</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9941805366765967</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>