<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">16</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">Startup funding shouldn&apos;t just go to white Ivy League Bay Area bros, so I&apos;m sharing the top fundraising tips from Atrium&apos;s fundraising workshop. Most important: Cry, pivot, but don&apos;t quit. 1/ https://t.co/1BxiPULtMb 
 The best startup pitches identify a big problem, show why your product is the solution, and then prove your potential to be huge with the right team, traction, growth plan, unit economics, and adjacent markets you&apos;ll conquer. 2/ 
 Practicing your startup pitch is critical because it A/B tests narratives, unearths hard questions, and breeds confidence. No on will fund you unless you&apos;re so passionate they know you won&apos;t quit. 3/ 
 The unintuitive secret to startup fundraising isn&apos;t the pitch where everyone has their own style, but the process of lining up a ton of investor meetings back-to-back so you can play them off each other. It&apos;s not the song, it&apos;s the dance. 4/ 
 Startups should assume they&apos;ll get a ton of NOs from investors before a Yes. Identify partners with expertise &amp;amp; track record in your industry, not just big names, and schedule meetings 3-4 weeks out. VCs are always on &quot;vacation&quot;. 5/ 
 If you don&apos;t hear back from an investor in 1-2 days, they don&apos;t like you. If they don&apos;t ask questions, they don&apos;t like you. Find one VC partner to be your champion and find out what their colleagues will want to know. 6/ 
 Don&apos;t write off lesser-known investors. A mid-tier fund&apos;s YES beats a top dog&apos;s No any day. Once you get a term sheet, don&apos;t say who it&apos;s from but leverage it to get offers or better deals from other investors. Don&apos;t be a jerk about it. 7/ 
 Startups can die waiting for an investor&apos;s due diligence to finish before they get the cash. The median wait after a soft YES is 41 days. Make sure you have enough runway to survive that long. 8/ 
 Startup burn rates balloon to the size of your bank account if you&apos;re not careful. Be thrifty. Cash should last 12-18 months until you&apos;ve hit milestones that de-risk your business for a new round of funding. 9/ 
 The best startup tip is still &quot;don&apos;t quit&quot;. When investors says no, employees leave, competitors emerge, and you want to hide: have grit, pivot, survive. Here are some more strategies from Atrium. https://t.co/kMWBaUPUlr What are your best fundraising tricks? 10/10</texto><total_retweets type="int">105</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">522</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">25</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">19563366</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">66227</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2217</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">33520</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.1093153019714812</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>