<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">171</hilo><total_tweets type="int">18</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) WE HAVE A BREAKING FREAKING STORY HERE FROM THE CONSERVATIVE UNDERGROUND NEWS OF TWITTER https://t.co/SjzJKhFRQ0 
 2) I AM SO EXCITE I MIGHT NOT EVEN SWEAR OR GO BACK TO CORRECT EXCITE TO EXCITED 
 3) CNN, AP, and MSNBC.... 
 4) HAVE JUST BEEN RAIDED BY THE FCC https://t.co/cIm0Utm6Tg 
 5) My one source inside one of these networks has informed me that the FCC has arrived and has seized all kinds of document as part of their investigation, including all of the source data the networks were using for their stories. 
 6) The allegations are about violating press guidelines, apparently. 
 7) This includes, according to my source inside a certain fake news network, the printing of blatant lies, the publishing and promotion of stories which require immediate retractions while not promoting the retractions 
 8) I am going to try to find independent confirmation of this. I&apos;m just getting this news now and got permission from my source before posting it. 
 9) Until then.... https://t.co/RjRU3lHpqy 
 CONTINUED 10) Still working on finding any documented or independent verification on this, but here&apos;s what I&apos;ve found on the FCC site that is tangentially related https://t.co/eYqoq7tBp6 
 11) &apos;Broadcasters may not intentionally distort the news. The FCC states that &quot;rigging or slanting the news is a most heinous act against the public interest.&quot;&apos; 
 12) &apos;The FCC may act only when it has received documented evidence, such as testimony from persons who have direct personal knowledge of an intentional falsification of the news. Without such documented evidence, the FCC generally cannot intervene.&apos; 
 13) Assuming the news I received is true, it would appear that either there is a whistleblower, or the FCC may be acting in regards to this story from earlier https://t.co/39y2ALs7bj 
 14) Also happened today, this one documented: Pruitt kicked the AP and CNN out of an EPA conference. https://t.co/gFuAMMne1n 
 15) Thanks Truth for linking this to me. https://t.co/kk04i24SU6 &quot;Rounding out our June meeting will be an enforcement item, which I can’t currently disclose. Think of it as the surprise teaser at the conclusion of every Marvel movie.&quot; GODDAMN YOU @AjitPaiFCC BLUEBALLING ME 
 16) June 7th. FUUUUUUCK. https://t.co/r7QK1PQXfd 
 17) I am still working to try to confirm this everyone! 
 18) NOTE: I have NO IDEA if the FCC meeting has ANYTHING TO DO WITH THIS. Ajit Pai may be puffing up the meeting because its Ajit Pai. The dude is the trolliest troll to ever troll an ocean of trolls.</texto><total_retweets type="int">2216</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">6200</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">342</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">890634935438118912</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">21327</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">110</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">33002</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.421507722571535</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>