<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">106</hilo><total_tweets type="int">12</total_tweets><texto type="str">This is Emily and Alicia Sucher. They are victims from Stoneman Douglas. This is not the first time their family has been in the middle of a gun scandal. https://t.co/R3eJfNGd45 #Qanon https://t.co/SG9tTM5U4g 
 Let&apos;s establish who they are related to. Here are Phyllis and William Sucher, they have a son named Michael. William built Century World Enterprises, one of world&apos;s largest in import/export of civilian/military equipment. #Qanon https://t.co/o5AiWk9eTV 
 When Phyllis passed away in 2007 Emily and Alicia are listed as grandchildren. So Michael is either their father or uncle. We are going to focus on him. #Qanon https://t.co/ocrKmBbmoC 
 Michael Sucher is president of [C]entury ([I]nternational) [A]rms among other businesses. #Qanon https://t.co/GFTtycRdo9 
 At the time of this article, more than 500 of the WASR-10s (Romanian made variant of the AK) imported by Century Arms were recovered in Mexico after being purchased in the U.S. That means Century&apos;s WASR-10 accounts for more than 17% of the total guns recovered in Mexico since 06. 
 https://t.co/CDUBLBjlvc 
 A gun linked to the Paris terror attacks that left 130 people dead and wounded 368 others has been traced back to a Century Arms. #Qanon https://t.co/dGW7w9emKB 
 Century Arms also sold arms to the Contras of Nicaragua at the time the 1980s Iran-Contra scandal. #Qanon https://t.co/3gHKiGJQZH 
 Century Arms breaks the law. #wikileaks. #Qanon https://t.co/oIVt2hY5kJ https://t.co/f3Di3ULCUS 
 So, what shall we say about all these things? To quote Emily Sucher, &quot;Um, I&apos;m not sure actually. It&apos;s just all very shocking.&quot; #Qanon https://t.co/yKrnSQ0gJA 
 @threadreaderapp unroll 
 BREAKING: Bald man spotted near Parkland school close to the time of shooting on video imaging with Tavor firearm...Century Arms link? #qanon https://t.co/uonHJS0BFZ</texto><total_retweets type="int">595</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">753</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">58</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">3</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">798626712892350464</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">5287</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">5603</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">28789</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.7840987502153125</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>