<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">65</hilo><total_tweets type="int">8</total_tweets><texto type="str">1/ My theory on why @rogerkver acts the way he does. I think the root cause is that he doesn&apos;t understand #Bitcoin on a sufficient technical level 
 2/ Any politician can make grand promises of solutions to problems, and expect others to make them happen. But building and delivering is what counts 
 3/ If Bitcoin is to become a foundation for human and machine peer-to-peer interaction that nobody can control or censor, each user needs to easily be able to run a full node 
 4/ To make it possible for all users of Bitcoin to run a full node, the resource requirements regarding CPU, memory and bandwidth must be kept low 
 5/ Users that don&apos;t run a full node are not &quot;peers&quot; in a peer-to-peer network, but must instead rely on trusted third parties as intermediaries 
 6/ Running a full node is the only way to send bitcoins and check that you have been payed, without having to rely on someone else. Completely trustless 
 7/ Increasing resource requirements for running a full node, e.g. by increasing the blocksize, jeopardizes the opportunity to be a &quot;peer&quot; in the network, while simultaneously jeopardizing decentralization 
 8/ Decentralization, and that everyone can use Bitcoin completely trustless as a &quot;peer&quot; in the network is paramount, and must under no circumstances be compromised</texto><total_retweets type="int">34</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">210</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">21</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">1</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Anger</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">116154256</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">4206</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">956</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">15593</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9103372716254604</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>