<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">193</hilo><total_tweets type="int">16</total_tweets><texto type="str">US needs low yield nuclear weapons, @US_Stratcom Cmdr @usairforce Gen John Hyten tells #SASC hearing - &quot;That capability&apos;s a deterrence weapon to respond the threat that #Russia in particular is portraying&quot; https://t.co/qZoUjDRBZE 
 &quot;The #Russia|n doctrine will be to use a low-yield nuclear weapon on the battlefield in case of a conventional over-match with an adversary&quot; per Gen Hyten, citing Vladimir Putin&apos;s own words 
 &quot;Our defense is deterrent capability&quot; per @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen Hyten, when asked about threat from #Russia #China #hypersonic missiles &quot;We don&apos;t have any defense that could deny the deployment of such a weapon against us&quot; 
 &quot;#Russia&apos;s going to have, at least in the unclassified world, at least 11 different delivery platforms for low yield nuclear weapons that they can use in different places at different times - right now we have one&quot; per Gen Hyten on why need sub-launched low yield nukes 
 &quot;When I have my intel..,translate the #Russia|n for me it is not &apos;escalate to deescalate,&apos; it is &apos;escalate to win&apos; and we have to deter that kind of response, That cannot be allowed&quot; @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen Hyten says of #Russia|n doctrine &amp;amp; threat https://t.co/Y4j0RHcuYg 
 US Space Force - &quot;I think that someday we&apos;ll have a space corps, space force in this country. But I don&apos;t think the time is right for that right now,&quot; per @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen John Hyten &quot;But I love the fact that the president talked about space as a warfighting domain&quot; https://t.co/2CMkNFYSzT 
 &quot;I see good signs&quot; that US moving faster to keep qualitative edge, per STRATCOM&apos;s Gen Hyten &quot;We can do it again but we need to get out of our own way&quot; 
 &quot;As I sit hear today, #Iran is in compliance with #JCPOA&quot; per @US_Stratcom Cmdr Gen John Hyten, asked asked about nuclear deal &quot;But it doesn&apos;t say anything about Iran as a global sponsor of terrorism or Iran building huge numbers of ballistic missiles&quot; https://t.co/Gi7t7nKVwQ 
 Impact of potentially pulling out of #JCPOA on #DPRK - &quot;Any action the #UnitedStates makes sends a message to everybody on the planet&quot; per Gen Hyten &quot;It will sends a message to #NorthKorea. It will send messages to #Russia #China, our allies... everybody is impacted&quot; https://t.co/VvuQSbxAHc 
 &quot;That&apos;s one of the differences in deterrence in the 21st century is that it&apos;s not longer a single country problem &amp;amp; a single issue proble, - it impacts everybody&quot; per STRATCOM&apos;s Gen Hyten 
 Not just nukes- #cyber a concern, too &quot;We need to have specific rules of engagement in cyber that match the other domains&quot; per @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen Hyten &quot;Then we need to delegate that authority all the way down so we can deal w/threats that exist that challenge the #UnitedStates&quot; https://t.co/epXP6aCQH9 
 STRATCOM&apos;s Gen Hyten says #cyber should be treated like space has been treated - talked about/viewed/considered as a warfighting domain 
 &quot;War, conflict, deterrence, is against an adversary, not against a place&quot; @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen Hyten says of #cyber &quot;You have to take the place out of it &amp;amp; focus on the adversary. What is the adversary doing? How do I deter that adversary?&quot; 
 &quot;Hopefully, that allows room for our diplomats to sit down with our adversary and say, &apos;Is this the world you really want to live in?&apos;&quot; per @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen Hyten 
 #Russia &amp;amp; nukes - &quot;They&apos;ve decided that that&apos;s the most important investment they have to make as a nation &amp;amp; they&apos;ve put the vast majority of the resources they have left into that&quot; per @US_Stratcom&apos;s Hyten at #SASC, adds... &quot;Oh, by the way, #NorthKorea&apos;s done the same thing&quot; 
 &quot;We have to make a decision in the near term,&quot; warns @US_Stratcom&apos;s Gen Hyten re question about #Russia &amp;amp; the #INF &quot;If they [Russia] don&apos;t come into compliance w/the INF, how long will we continue to, as you said, tie our hands&quot; https://t.co/0Btg6sRq32</texto><total_retweets type="int">93</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">85</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">29</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">11</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">583821006</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">9128</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1385</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">32752</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9562167093781738</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>