<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">373</hilo><total_tweets type="int">26</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) Devin Nunes January 4th, 2018 Letter to Rod Rosenstein documenting their conversation and agreement. #SteeleDossier https://t.co/pH22Lb9QWy 
 2) Nunes secured the critical FD-302&apos;s and FD-1023&apos;s that relate to the #SteelDossier! https://t.co/qADX14Jafg 
 3) FD-302 is an FBI form that is used to document interviews/interrogations. It details questions asked and answers given as well as who was present during the interview. Here is a sample https://t.co/wFQsYpKVQJ 
 4) FD-1023 is an FBI form that is uses to document meetings between FBI and sources. It does not necessarily discuss what was said. It is also called a CHS Report. (Confidential Human Source) Here is a sample. https://t.co/U0umTD0rP8 
 5) If you notice the 1023 sample I provided it gives out extensive detail about the informant and what is to be asked as well as by whom and where and when. But it does not give the informants answers or details of the meeting. That is where the 302 comes in. 
 6) The 302 reveals the content of interview as well as identify ALL PARTICIPANTS. The 1023 outlines who met who, where, when, and why. 
 7) The #SteeleDossier is the Achilles heel of the Russian Hoax. The 302&apos;s and 1023&apos;s will identify people involved on BOTH SIDES. The informants and THE DOJ/FBI PERSONNEL! 
 8) Nunes also secured interviews with FBI/DOJ personnel. With some surprising additions! https://t.co/SuDhsmLjj2 
 9) #BillPriestap Bill Priestap is the head of the FBI Counterintelligence operation. He was FBI Agent #PeterStrozk’s direct boss. He is at the epicenter of the counter intelligence operation against Donald Trump. Details here&amp;gt;https://t.co/FmNX2C1SnI 
 10) After lying about the DNI Comey fingers Bill Priestap as the one who made the decision to withhold information from Congress: &quot;It&apos;s usually the decision of the head of our counter intelligence division.&quot; #JamesComey #BillPriestap https://t.co/RHwgCg86Go 
 11) Comey was creating a fall guy. https://t.co/WaqvYHIFva 
 12) The risk of creating a fall guy like Preistap is enormous. He simply knows too much. https://t.co/8NgOB5SCn7 
 13) One does not get to be the FBI head of counter intelligence without being able to identify risk and see all the angles. I could be wrong, but it is hard to imagine Priestap doing anything illegal without having proof of authorization. This is the danger that Priestap presents https://t.co/V0iSuUvlLn 
 14) James &quot;Jim&quot; Rybicki was Comey&apos;s Chief of Staff. He also knows a lot. Like Priestap, not much is known about him. https://t.co/x2ybgeWDwa 
 15) We do know that both #Rybicki and #Priestap were both involved in the crafting of James Comey&apos;s infamous statement that exonerated Hillary Clinton. (Note the other recipients #Strzok #McCabe #Baker and others including several names redacted) https://t.co/VoMPJXTNV2 https://t.co/wntnYpA4nA 
 16) I located this quote that I find rather interesting. It could mean nothing, but then again, it could mean everything. https://t.co/QTH7Ty0TDE https://t.co/BYB4zpts9k 
 17) IF true, it suggests that multiple FBI execs viewed him as WEAK and not very committed to Comey. If I were running an investigation I would zero in on this guy as a possible weak link to exploit. 
 18) Rybicki is still listed as FBI COS working for Wray. I think it is significant that he has not (yet) been pushed out. (Unlike Page, McCabe, Ohr, and Baker) 
 19) Nunes also secured the rest of #Strzok texts. 9500 of them! (Due January 11th, 2018) https://t.co/uag2AQjIcj 
 20) Also due on January 11th, 2018, is information on Mueller top deputy #AndrewWeissmann with regards to a meeting with the media. Information that Nunes tells us the FBI is currently collecting. (This tells us that he is under investigation) https://t.co/1X4nV0aPGz 
 21) Weissmann came under scrutiny due to the email found by @JudicialWatch of him praising Sally Yates for defying Donald Trump&apos;s legal travel ban EO. A refusal for which she was fired. https://t.co/jUBJGI9wC7 https://t.co/6KvsH13zuQ 
 22) 💥THE DOCUMENT!💥 This 302 is so sensitive that Wray is going to show it to ONLY Nunes and his senior investigators! This will occur next week. #SteeleDossier https://t.co/ZKkB666TzV 
 23) More significant to me than EVERYTHING in this document is the fact that Nunes documented it and released it to the public. Everything in it is per a verbal conversation THAT HE DID NOT HAVE TO DOCUMENT, yet he did. Let that sink in. 
 24) Devin Nunes has taken a lot of lumps to get where he is including a ginned up ethics probe. Now in the clear, he is going to dish out some lumps of his own.... https://t.co/MBi9mH0qLH 
 25) Intel Cmte interviews and information will be controlled due to the multiple investigations taking place. Always consider the source of information and the spin. There will be public disclosures and tactical leaks. Some leaks will be good and some bad. SCRUTINIZE and DISCERN 
 26) Conclusion: Stay positive and keep an eye on the little details as well as the big picture. @TheLastRefuge2 is keeping track of everything. Go here and read all the links&amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; https://t.co/FmNX2C1SnI https://t.co/OirtivSA5g</texto><total_retweets type="int">5422</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">9798</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">304</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">11</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Surprise</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">714128911823724545</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">30453</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">1873</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">24335</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0493531777403315</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>