<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">23</hilo><total_tweets type="int">10</total_tweets><texto type="str">FBI briefed lawmakers on failures leading up to Florida shooting Why aren’t the students, that have been bashing the NRA, now apologizing and saying something to the FBI? #ParklandSchoolShooting #CNNTownHall #WitchHunt #FBI #NRA /1 https://t.co/fwg5TWL1nC 
 Top House Republicans said Wednesday that a senior FBI official had briefed lawmakers on the agency&apos;s failure to respond to warnings about the teenager accused of carrying out a deadly shooting at a South Florida high school last month. /2 #ResignSheriffIsrael 
 Acting FBI Deputy Director David Bowdich met with lawmakers on the House Oversight and Government Reform and Judiciary committees Tuesday to discuss the missteps, which were revealed in the days after the shooting at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School in Parkland, Fla. /3 
 Bowdich acknowledged that the FBI failed to follow its own protocol after it received a tip in January about the accused shooter, Nikolas Cruz, 19, &amp;amp; vowed to take corrective actions, according to a press release issued by Reps. Trey Gowdy and Bob Goodlatte. /4 https://t.co/Sl1OaEOAZr 
 The FBI admitted just two days after the Feb. 14 shooting that it received a tip from a person close to Cruz the previous month warning about the teen&apos;s gun ownership, desire to kill and erratic behavior. /5 
 That tip &quot;should have been assessed as a potential threat to life,&quot; the FBI said at the time, but the warnings were never investigated further. /6 #ParklandSchoolShooting #FBI 
 Bowdich told lawmakers on Tuesday that the call to a tip line provided enough information to justify an FBI probe into the matter, lawmakers said, though information was not passed on to the agency&apos;s Miami field office. /7 
 The person who took the tip line call spoke with their supervisor afterwards, but that conversation was not documented, according to Gowdy and Goodlatte. Bowdich also said that the employee who took the January phone call was able to connect the warning to /8 
 another tip from September regarding a threatening YouTube comment. That comment, posted under the username &quot;nikolas cruz,&quot; read, &quot;I am going to be a professional school shooter.&quot; Source-Mark Greenwood The Hill /9 
 Since the #ParklandSchoolShooting Liberals have been screaming for #GunControl #GUNREFORM The FBI could have stopped this. Law abiding Americans will not give up our rights because of a criminal act and a rogue/weak FBI. /end #NeverGetOurGuns @DLoesch @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/6Djx1B1yPx</texto><total_retweets type="int">514</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">616</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">78</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">9</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">1249831310</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">57737</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">45195</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">125873</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8419765762236604</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>