<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">119</hilo><total_tweets type="int">11</total_tweets><texto type="str">Oh General Flynn. You knew it was going to cost you your security clearance and pension, so you lied. #TrumpRussia https://t.co/lOxxxwcmmF 
 Flynn&apos;s partners responded partially to @OversightDems request for information, proving he violated federal law. They&apos;ve informed Mueller. https://t.co/rdv6cI8nOu 
 @OversightDems Even worse, Flynn&apos;s partners indicate that the deal is alive today, and he may have pushed it during his 24 days as America&apos;s NatSec Advisor https://t.co/0rAulkvc9j 
 @OversightDems Flynn&apos;s partner ACU haven&apos;t disclosed any lobbying of the Trump administration since the election, but say it&apos;s part of their &quot;toolkit&quot; https://t.co/ouZqj6J3f7 
 @OversightDems Flynn got a $25k check, didn&apos;t cash it for some reason &amp;amp; got paid for travel expenses, didn&apos;t disclose any of the payments on security forms https://t.co/kZAS6mKLew 
 @OversightDems We&apos;ve had proof that Russia paid Flynn since March, which he also materially omitted from security clearances https://t.co/J3g3GQQ7Bn 
 @OversightDems And we found out about Flynn&apos;s $100 billion dollar deal in June, when a Senator said he was cooperating with the FBI https://t.co/x6NcOS6cVK 
 @OversightDems Flynn could lose his military pension because of the Constitution&apos;s emoluments clause, which also applies to Trump. https://t.co/YHXLA7TY1J 
 @OversightDems #Republican ethics lawyer @RWPUSA says Flynn should be stripped of his military rank for violating the constitution https://t.co/REPRSt20Pl 
 @OversightDems @RWPUSA Here&apos;s the letter @OversightDems and @HFACDemocrats sent to Flynn&apos;s business partners https://t.co/CIkP6nIHMe 
 @OversightDems @RWPUSA @HFACDemocrats WSJ reports that Flynn used his NSA job to promote a Russian nuclear deal he was paid to rep inside the White House https://t.co/WpIFMPdQNx</texto><total_retweets type="int">493</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">746</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">29</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">2</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Sadness</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Sadness</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="int">19422491</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">60227</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">9577</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">115581</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.9595532473626968</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">True</user_verificado></root>