<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">310</hilo><total_tweets type="int">23</total_tweets><texto type="str">1. The “Dossier” Fusion GPS is a commercial research/strategic intelligence firm based in D.C. co-founded in 2011 by Glenn Simpson, former reporter for Roll Call and Wall Street Journal. The dossier is the geometric center for the circle of filth. 
 2. Isn&apos;t it most peculiar that deputy AG Rod Rosenstein refused to answer if the FBI paid for the dossier? “I believe I know the answer, but the Intelligence Committee is the appropriate committee…” https://t.co/LrWlzAgG9r 
 3. If you don&apos;t know what I am talking about and would like to, carve out time to explore the complexities of this winding maze of depravity and treason. Be forewarned, its not for the mentally languid. https://t.co/YPvW8fggdl 
 4. Fusion GPS has been active in American politics from it very inception: Back in 2102 Dems hired Fusion for “opposition research” against Mitt Romney. Mother Jones published an article against one of his PAC contributors, Frank VanderSloot. https://t.co/F1EPZtjiAZ 
 5. You know I kept scratching my head: where else had I heard about Mother Jones and Fusion GPS? It tore me up. Aha! I remembered: Christoper Steele who would be hired by Fusion GPS many years later to publish Trump-Russia Dossier passed his findings to Mother Jones October 2016 
 6. You really think that it is mere coincidence that Fusion GPS and Mother Jones’ paths seem to fortuitously cross at the “right moment” ? This association bugged me till I went back to all my previous tweets. Here it is: https://t.co/nVytEfGSGr 
 7. 17 Democrats on House Judiciary Committee sent a letter, July 2017 to Justice Department demanding answers as to why agency dismissed money laundering case earlier involving Kremlin-linked attorney Natalia Veselnitskaya who met with Donald Trump Jr during last year&apos;s campaign 
 8. Almost everybody heard about this instance. The Department agreed to settle this $230 million case for less than $6 million and no admission of wrongdoing. https://t.co/3OuRR8O7Zu 
 9. Digging a little further: the company at the heart of this issue, Prevezon, whose sole shareholder was Russian Denis Katsyv, whose father is Petr Katsyv, vice president of Russia&apos;s state-run rail monopoly. 
 10. Turns out Katsyv’s lawyer was Natalia Veselnitskaya, who was not licensed to practice in the US. So, Katsyv hired the law firm of BakerHostetler to represent Prevezon; BakerHostetler hired FUSION GPS in 2014 to provide research help for the litigation….. 
 11. Yes, its not a typo, a Russian hired Fusion GPS.....Do you think that it is a mere coincidence that the lawyer of the company that hired Fusion GPS in 2014 ended up meeting with Donald Trump Jr during the 2016 campaign? https://t.co/lwF8S7jgzh 
 12. On July 27, 2017, Fusion GPS accused White House of trying to &quot;smear&quot; it for investigating the president&apos;s alleged ties to Russia. This is not a banal statement, but strategy, call out the people you are smearing as being ones who are persecuting you. https://t.co/8wUexvz0r6 
 13. I know because they did it again, today, Dec 13, 2017. Fusion’s lawyer admitted they hired Nellie Ohr, but complained .... 
 14. “Now, I don’t have proof as to how Fox News got that information or how Washington Examiner got the information from the bank, but I’m pretty confident that they didn&apos;t get it from Fusion” https://t.co/h1Gi2Yep7G 
 15. Isn&apos;t it priceless, Fusion GPS is the metastatic cancer that is slowly destroying the country from within, spreading lies, falsehoods and systematic disinformation, but somehow they argue that they are the victims here. Where else do we see “victimhood politics”? 
 16. If you hold the Dossier/Fusion GPS as the focal point of your attention, I suspect you will be way ahead of the average individual, a lot of things will reveal themselves very clearly in the near future. https://t.co/NiLgVhYMst 
 17. McCabe, Strzok, Ohr, Page are all now becoming key individuals curiously connected with the Dossier. Where does Comey fit it? https://t.co/XxxyzQhLjR 
 18. Bruce Ohr’s Wife, Nellie Ohr was paid by Fusion GPS all through summer of 2016, Bruce was also in contact with Christopher Steele.https://t.co/Xk9XyaESv7 
 19. Then Today we learned that Nellie Ohr registered a Ham radio a month after DNC/Hillary retained Fusion GPS to do opposition research on Trump. Why does a middle aged woman suddenly need to register a HAM radio? Unless that helps her communicate undetected? 
 20. The Dossier and Fusion GPS are inextricably connected to the concerted plan to influence American politics and to try to prevent Trump’s presidency. https://t.co/0iAaIw5rOV 
 21. Shifty Adam Schiff, an unctuous peddler of lies is still pushing the Trump Russia connection, why does he look increasing sweaty though? Why has the whole Imran Awan-Debbie Wasserman case gone silent? 
 22. Do you really think that all of what has been going on over the last few years went on without the knowledge of then president Obama and his intelligence people? 
 23. Fusion/Dossier is the “sine qua non” of the circle of filth: pivotal, central and providing centrifugal lifeblood to spokes of this circle of filth. There are three classes of people: those who see, those who see when they are shown, those who do not see - Leonardo da Vinci</texto><total_retweets type="int">4982</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">8096</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">212</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">0</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Surprise</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">879548970082721792</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">51217</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">2940</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">38261</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">1.0539169429458746</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>