<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><hilo type="int">123</hilo><total_tweets type="int">15</total_tweets><texto type="str">1) I was looking forward to see Jim Stone Freelance... http://82.221.129.208/.zi0.html ... to cover this train wreck with the Republicans on it. Stone&apos;s comments are along the lines of my own thoughts on this event. #ReleaseTheMemo #TheGreatAwakening #WeThePeople #TheStorm 
 2) Jim Stone has some shocking information about this event. Stone is an ex-NSA dude, so he&apos;s legit. #QAnon #ItEndsNow #FakeNews #SecretSociety #SOTU #NotABot #FISA #MAGA #TrumpTrain #NoDACA #RedPill #DeepState #LockThemUp #SecondAmendment #AndrewMcCabe #DrainTheSwamp 
 3) Quoting Stone: &quot;CONFIRMED: THE CONGRESSMEN ABOARD THE TRAIN WERE SUPPOSED TO BE IN SESSION. THEY WERE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HEADED TO A &quot;RESORT&quot; THAT DOUBLES AS A DOOMSDAY (COG) FACILITY&quot; &quot;Adding to the credibility of the theory they were fleeing a threat is the fact that ... 
 4) (Stone con&apos;t) ...they had family members aboard the train, including children that should have been in school.&quot; &quot;OVERWHELMINGLY PROBABLE: THEY RECEIVED DEATH THREATS OVER THE MEMO, AND WERE HEADING TO A SAFE PLACE WHEN THEY WERE STOPPED BY A STAGED &apos;ACCIDENT&apos;&quot;... 
 5) (Stone con&apos;t) &quot;UPDATE: CONFIRMED - They did not turn back, they continued on to the safe facility in buses, including the injured. THAT THERE ALONE SAYS IT ALL. Here&apos;s the story, which is all now 100 percent confirmed.&quot; 
 6) (Stone con&apos;t) &quot;A majority of Republican congressmen who voted to release the Fisa memo, which exposes an enormous amount of deep state corruption, were on an escorted train when they were supposed to be in session, with all roads closed ahead of the train...&quot; 
 7) (Stone con&apos;t) &quot;...(for security reasons) and the train receiving helicopter escort. Despite all the roads being closed, the train hit a garbage truck while going 70 mph. The front wheels of the front engine derailed, but the rear wheels stayed on the tracks.&quot; 
 8) (con&apos;t) &quot;With all the roads closed for security reasons, the only way the garbage truck could have gotten in the way of the train would be if it was done intentionally. Even some Congressmen are now saying the accident had to have been staged, and that it was an attempt to... 
 9) (con&apos;t) &quot;...kill a large number of congressmen who voted to release the memo. Large numbers of deaths would have occurred if the train did derail, (as planned) but with the will of God it mostly stayed on the tracks and none of the cars or engines tipped over.&quot; 
 10) (con&apos;t) &quot;If that had happened at 70 MPH the results would have been devastating.&quot; HEADS UP: Rogue factions in the United States government are attempting a violent coup with &quot;plausible deniability. Fortunately only minor injuries happened, but having this end up being...&quot; 
 11) (con&apos;t) &quot;...minor defies all probability, it was supposed to be a disaster and it was definitely, without question, not an accident.&quot; [End quotes] FK&apos;N A-hole Deep State and Shadow Government! THANK GOD that the Republicans survived! It&apos;s WAR. #ReleaseTheDamnMemo! 
 12) It&apos;s WAR. It&apos;s a war between: Deep State (Intelligence) ~ Shadow Gov&apos;t (MIC) ~ Cabal VS. Trump ~ American Military White Hats ~ American People ~ Secret Space Program Alliance The war is being fought online, in the media and in the world of commerce. 
 13) Now this war HAS GONE HOT. First -- the attempts to NUKE Hawaii and Japan. Those events are being &quot;covered&quot; with BS shit about a &quot;wrong button&quot; being pushed. BS! Second -- Now with this train wreck attempt to kill a bunch of Republicans. What can you do about this? 
 14) Spread the word about the TRUTH of what the hell is going on. Print out flyers -- 4 to a 11x14 sheet -- and highlight the kinds of TRUTH that you want to see exposed, issues that YOU feel passionate about. Hand out those flyers to people everywhere. Smile. Chat. 
 15) Handing out flyers -- it&apos;s old school, yes -- may seem silly. But it&apos;s not. The Internet/media is in a massive data overload. Flyers enable one to CONNECT directly with people. Build your ability to debate with @StefanMolyneux&apos;s brilliant book, &quot;The Art of the Argument.&quot;</texto><total_retweets type="int">276</total_retweets><total_favoritos type="int">280</total_favoritos><total_replies type="int">29</total_replies><total_hashtags type="int">21</total_hashtags><emocion_max_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_max_1><emocion_max_2 type="str">Disgust</emocion_max_2><emocion_moda_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_moda_1><emocion_moda_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_moda_2><emocion_media_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_media_1><emocion_media_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_media_2><emocion_presente_1 type="str">Joy</emocion_presente_1><emocion_presente_2 type="str">Fear</emocion_presente_2><usuario type="number">2942765893</usuario><user_total_followers type="int">10213</user_total_followers><user_total_friends type="int">9645</user_total_friends><user_total_status type="int">5853</user_total_status><user_puntaje_sigmo type="float">0.8043572500727707</user_puntaje_sigmo><user_verificado type="bool">False</user_verificado></root>